<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Cryptonews</title>
	<atom:link href="https://cryptonews.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://cryptonews.com/</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 00:05:47 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.4.1</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Arbitrum to Unlock $2.32 Billion in Vested ARB Tokens on March 16</title>
		<link>https://cryptonews.com/news/arbitrum-to-unlock-2-32-billion-in-vested-arb-tokens-on-march-16.htm</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hassan Shittu]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 00:20:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ARB]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Arbitrum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Layer-2]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptonews.com/?p=181188</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Arbitrum, a Layer-2 blockchain network, is gearing up to release $2.32 billion worth of vested Arbitrum ARB tokens on March 16.</span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/arbitrum-to-unlock-2-32-billion-in-vested-arb-tokens-on-march-16.htm">Arbitrum to Unlock $2.32 Billion in Vested ARB Tokens on March 16</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptonews.com">Cryptonews</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Arbitrum, a Layer-2 blockchain network, is gearing up to release $2.32 billion worth of vested Arbitrum (ARB) tokens on March 16, marking a major milestone for the platform.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Token Unlocks highlighted that Arbitrum will do a “Cliff Unlock,” where tokens are released in a lump sum at the deadline.</span></p>
<h2><strong><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Arbitrum Prepares for $2.32 Billion Token Unlock on March 16</span></strong></h2>
<p><span class="replacer"></span><br />
<a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://token.unlocks.app/arbitrum" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">According to data from Token Unlocks</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true">, approximately 1.1 billion locked ARB tokens will be unlocked, constituting roughly 76% of the token&#8217;s circulating supply.<br />
</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Of the unlocked tokens, Arbitrum will allocate 673.5 million tokens, valued at around $1.41 billion at current prices, to its team and advisers. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Additionally, 438.25 million tokens, worth approximately $915 million, will be released for investors. Token Unlocks clarified that this will be a &#8220;Cliff Unlock,&#8221; meaning no tokens are initially released until the specified unlock date, upon which a lump sum will be introduced into the market.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Unlocks are staggered releases of cryptocurrencies that have been frozen to prevent early investors or project team members from selling in large numbers. The Cliff Unlock method allows for unfreezing a certain number of tokens immediately after a predetermined period, after which unfreezing happens in a linear schedule.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Following the March 16 release, Arbitrum will continue to unfreeze a certain amount of tokens every four weeks for four years, <a href="https://twitter.com/Token_Unlocks/status/1691648214553014458">Token Unlocks </a></span><a href="https://twitter.com/Token_Unlocks/status/1691648214553014458"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">noted</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"><a href="https://twitter.com/Token_Unlocks/status/1691648214553014458"> in a tweet</a>.</span></p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr"><img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f4c5.png" alt="📅" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> Mark your calendars<br />$1.1 billion in <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24ARB&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">$ARB</a> unlocks are coming <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/23f3.png" alt="⏳" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /></p>
<p>On March 16th, 2024, get ready for a massive cliff unlock as the Team and Investors unlock their tokens, totaling a staggering $1.26 billion. <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f525.png" alt="🔥" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /></p>
<p>But that&#39;s not all! Starting from that day, every 16th of the… <a href="https://t.co/Ayv4bKXmty">pic.twitter.com/Ayv4bKXmty</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Token Unlocks (@Token_Unlocks) <a href="https://twitter.com/Token_Unlocks/status/1691648214553014458?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">August 16, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Given the huge number of tokens set to be unlocked, crypto community members are anticipating potential price fluctuations for ARB tokens. </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.reddit.com/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/1bbply5/comment/kuaykjy/?utm_source=share&amp;utm_medium=web3x&amp;utm_name=web3xcss&amp;utm_term=1&amp;utm_content=share_button" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Some foresee</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> a rise in short positions against the token on March 16, while others have </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.reddit.com/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/1bbply5/comment/kucdui3/?utm_source=share&amp;utm_medium=web3x&amp;utm_name=web3xcss&amp;utm_term=1&amp;utm_content=share_button" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">already sold</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> their tokens in anticipation of the unlock.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Unlocks free up liquidity and are considered bearish catalysts for the cryptocurrency&#8217;s price. <a href="https://www.thetie.io/insights/news/token-unlock/">A study from crypto analytics firm The Tie</a> shows that unlocks representing more than 100% of the average daily trading volume tend to have a negative impact on the token&#8217;s price.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">However, <a href="https://twitter.com/JJcycles/status/1764356723257549032">crypto influencer JJcycles </a></span><a href="https://twitter.com/JJcycles/status/1764356723257549032"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">shared</span> </a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"><a href="https://twitter.com/JJcycles/status/1764356723257549032">a contrasting viewpoint on social media platform X</a>, drawing parallels to a previous token unlocked by Solana.</span></p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">On the 16th of March, <br />the Arbitrum supply increases dramatically.</p>
<p>Unlocks:<br />1. 674m ARB &#8211; Team<br />2. 438m ARB &#8211; Investors</p>
<p>The last time I saw such a huge supply unlock during a bullmarket of comparatively large cap coin was with Solana during the previous cycle.</p>
<p>It ended up… <a href="https://t.co/HSJG7WXbzu">pic.twitter.com/HSJG7WXbzu</a></p>
<p>&mdash; JJcycles (@JJcycles) <a href="https://twitter.com/JJcycles/status/1764356723257549032?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">March 3, 2024</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The trader noted that Solana&#8217;s SOL token experienced a surge in price following the release of vested tokens, contrary to expectations of a price decline.</span></p>
<h2><strong><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Arbitrum&#8217;s ARB Token Lags Behind Competitors Amidst Market Growth</span></strong></h2>
<p><span class="replacer"></span><br />
<span data-preserver-spaces="true"><a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/arbitrums-total-value-locked-surges-past-2-5-billion-as-token-nears-2.htm">Arbitrum</a>, a prominent layer-2 blockchain network, has observed a decline in the value of its native cryptocurrency, ARB, compared to other leading Layer-2 assets in the past day.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Despite a positive trend in the sector overall, ARB emerged as the weakest performer among the top five L2 tokens, experiencing a decrease of over 2% during the reporting period, while the sector showcased an average gain of 3.8%.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true"><a href="https://x.com/spotonchain/status/1766630108347969779?s=20">SpotOnchain&#8217;s analysis reveals substantial sell-offs by whales</a>, with approximately 3 million ARB tokens offloaded for $6 million just ahead of the event. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Despite this, Arbitrum maintains its position as the largest Ethereum-based layer-2 network, with DeFillama data indicating a total locked asset value of $3.6 billion.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">At press time, ARB changed hands at $2.10, a 3.04% decrease in the last 24 hours. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">In addition to Arbitrum, several other projects are gearing up to unlock tokens this week. Aptos is scheduled to release approximately 24 million tokens valued at around $329 million on March 13, constituting a sizable portion of the project&#8217;s circulating supply. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Similarly, projects like ApeCoin, Flow, CyberConnect, Moonbeam, and Euler are about to release vested tokens, collectively amounting to about $53 million in digital assets.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">With approximately $2.7 billion worth of tokens set to be unlocked this week across various projects, the cryptocurrency space is anticipating big developments and potential market shifts in the days ahead.</span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/arbitrum-to-unlock-2-32-billion-in-vested-arb-tokens-on-march-16.htm">Arbitrum to Unlock $2.32 Billion in Vested ARB Tokens on March 16</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptonews.com">Cryptonews</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		<enclosure url="https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/11223656/1710196616-1710196598732_processed.jpg" length="121355" type="image/jpeg" />

			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Michael Saylor Says Bitcoin Is Not Currency &#8211; But Still Plans To HODL For 100 Years</title>
		<link>https://cryptonews.com/news/michael-saylor-says-bitcoin-is-not-currency-but-still-plans-to-hodl-for-100-years.htm</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Andrew Throuvalas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 00:06:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Michael Saylor]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptonews.com/?p=181257</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>MicroStrategy CEO Michael Saylor – whose company now owns 205,000 Bitcoin (BTC) – says people should buy and HODL their coins 100 years.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/michael-saylor-says-bitcoin-is-not-currency-but-still-plans-to-hodl-for-100-years.htm">Michael Saylor Says Bitcoin Is Not Currency &#8211; But Still Plans To HODL For 100 Years</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptonews.com">Cryptonews</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>MicroStrategy CEO Michael Saylor – whose company now owns 205,000 Bitcoin (BTC) – says people should buy and HODL their coins 100 years.</p>
<p>“I would encourage people to think of it as digital property – a billion-dollar building in cyberspace,” Michael Saylor told <a href="https://twitter.com/saylor/status/1767178599390458285">CNBC</a> in an interview on Monday. “Hold it for 100 years.”</p>
<h2>More Bitcoin Bought by Michael Saylor&#8217;s MicroStrategy</h2>
<p><span class="replacer"></span><br />
Earlier that morning, Saylor announced yet another <a href="https://twitter.com/saylor/status/1767158870294605904">seismic Bitcoin purchase</a> of $800 million at an average price of $68,377 per coin.</p>
<p>The new purchase was funded using proceeds from a recently announced <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-25.htm">$700 million convertible note offering</a>, on which the firm is paying a meager 0.625% interest, and is due for repayment in 2030.</p>
<p>His company is now the world’s largest corporate holder of BTC, and nearly holds 1% of the entire BTC supply that will ever exist. His conviction to buy more not only comes from his core beliefs as a Bitcoin maximalist, but also the premise that BTC isn’t meant to be sold – or spent – at all.</p>
<p>“People refer to it as ‘digital currency,’ and that’s an unfortunate historical artifact,” Saylor said, likening the asset to valuable real estate property. “The compelling use case is capital preservation for everyone in the world.”</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr"><a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Bitcoin?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#Bitcoin</a> is Digital Property. It is superior to other investments such as Gold, Equity, or Real Estate because it is digital, available, global, ethical, &amp; useful to millions of companies and billions of people. <a href="https://t.co/738dblB0Zt">pic.twitter.com/738dblB0Zt</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Michael Saylor<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/26a1.png" alt="⚡" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> (@saylor) <a href="https://twitter.com/saylor/status/1767178599390458285?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">March 11, 2024</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>The executive noted that Bitcoin’s total addressable market as a store of value is a whopping $100 trillion, compared to the $1 trillion market for a desirable medium of exchange. Bitcoin’s market cap today is still under $1.5 trillion and slightly over that of silver, leaving ample room for growth.</p>
<h2>Michael Saylor Says Don’t Call Bitcoin A Currency</h2>
<p><span class="replacer"></span><br />
Meanwhile, the asset’s use case as property is far less “controversial” or troubling with regulators than its use as a medium of exchange.</p>
<p>Indeed, many of Bitcoin’s loudest critics, including Elizabeth Warren, Jamie Dimon, and <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/sec-chairman-gensler-comments-on-bitcoin-and-ethereum-avoids-ethereum-security-classification.htm">Gary Gensler</a>, consider money laundering one of Bitcoin’s primary transactional use cases, while much political focus around crypto surrounds the regulation of stablecoins, exchanges, and other facilitators of payments and trade.</p>
<p>“It doesn’t have to be a currency,” Michael Saylor said. “Nobody’s trying to buy a cup of coffee with a fraction of their building on Fifth Avenue.”</p>
<p>The billionaire added that Bitcoin will “eat gold” – whose monetary properties are inferior to Bitcoin, yet whose market cap is still ten times the size. Bitcoin spot ETFs, which first launched in the United States two months ago, are now over half the size of all gold ETFs.</p>
<p>“It’s competing with risk assets as a long-term hold, and it’s competing with you buying an Airbnb as a retirement income source if you’re a middle-class person,” Saylor concluded.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/michael-saylor-says-bitcoin-is-not-currency-but-still-plans-to-hodl-for-100-years.htm">Michael Saylor Says Bitcoin Is Not Currency &#8211; But Still Plans To HODL For 100 Years</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptonews.com">Cryptonews</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		<enclosure url="https://cryptonews.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/12/1701729230-michelsaylrobtc___media_library_original_801_473.jpg" length="28090" type="image/jpeg" />

			</item>
		<item>
		<title>South Korean Law Firm Chief Jailed for Stealing Customer Money to Invest in Crypto</title>
		<link>https://cryptonews.com/news/south-korean-law-firm-chief-jailed-for-stealing-customer-money-to-invest-in-crypto.htm</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tim Alper]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 23:30:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Legal]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[South Korea]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptonews.com/?p=180967</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A South Korean law firm operator was jailed in Busan on March 11 after they were found guilty of stealing clients’ money to spend on crypto investments.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/south-korean-law-firm-chief-jailed-for-stealing-customer-money-to-invest-in-crypto.htm">South Korean Law Firm Chief Jailed for Stealing Customer Money to Invest in Crypto</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptonews.com">Cryptonews</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A South Korean law firm operator was jailed in <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/south-korean-city-busan-names-digital-exchange-preferred-bidder.htm">Busan</a> on March 11 after being found guilty of stealing clients’ money to spend on crypto investments.</p>
<p>The media outlet <a href="https://www.newsis.com/view/?id=NISX20240311_0002655389" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Newsis</a> reported that the case was heard at the Criminal Division of the Busan District Court. The court sentenced an unnamed individual in their 50s to 20 months in jail.</p>
<h2>South Korean Law Firm Boss ‘Embezzled Client Money’</h2>
<p><span class="replacer"></span><br />
The lawyer stole $170,000 on December 27, 2021, the court heard. Prosecutors said the lawyer transferred money from a company account into their personal bank account.</p>
<p>The money came from a corporate client, who had given the money to the firm to complete a real estate deal as part of a trust contract.</p>
<p>However, the court heard, the accused instead “stole the money and used it for personal purposes,” namely crypto investments.</p>
<p>On another occasion, the court heard, the South Korean law firm chief stole a registration fee from a private client worth just under $1,700.</p>
<p>The crypto investments appear to have been ill-fated. Prosecutors said they were unable to retrieve any of the stolen funds.</p>
<p>The presiding judge, Justice Jeong Soon-yeol of the District Court’s 11th Criminal Division, said:</p>
<blockquote><p>“The amount of damage sustained is large. And none of the stolen money has been recovered. Considering these factors, I have no choice but to hand out a severe punishment in this case.”</p></blockquote>
<h2>South Korean City Sees Rise in Crypto-related Crime?</h2>
<p><span class="replacer"></span><br />
Busan judges are no stranger to crypto-related cases. In December last year, police in the southern city <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/south-korean-police-shut-down-gangsters-32m-crypto-scam-ring.htm">swooped on a gang of over 80 suspected crypto scammers</a>.</p>
<figure id="attachment_180972" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-180972" style="width: 546px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><img fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-180972" src="https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/11143423/1710167663-south_korea-busan-svg.png" alt="Busan on a map of South Korea." width="546" height="768" srcset="https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/11143423/1710167663-south_korea-busan-svg.png 546w, https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/11143423/1710167663-south_korea-busan-svg-213x300.png 213w, https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/11143423/1710167663-south_korea-busan-svg-150x211.png 150w" sizes="(max-width: 546px) 100vw, 546px" /><figcaption id="caption-attachment-180972" class="wp-caption-text">Busan on a map of South Korea. (Source: Dmthoth [CC BY-SA 3.0])</figcaption></figure>In January, the same division of the District Court <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/south-korean-crypto-drug-dealer-jailed-for-7-years.htm">jailed a drug dealer, who used crypto as a payment tool, for seven years</a>.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">Korean bankers misrepresented risky China-linked structured products to retail investors, a watchdog says <a href="https://t.co/mLtYadfyqQ">https://t.co/mLtYadfyqQ</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Bloomberg (@business) <a href="https://twitter.com/business/status/1767000730735436277?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">March 11, 2024</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>Also in January, a district court in nearby Changwon <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/south-korean-bogus-crypto-exchange-fraudster-jailed.htm">jailed an individual who gave a bogus crypto exchange illegal bank documents. The court sent the forger to prison for four years</a>.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/south-korean-law-firm-chief-jailed-for-stealing-customer-money-to-invest-in-crypto.htm">South Korean Law Firm Chief Jailed for Stealing Customer Money to Invest in Crypto</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptonews.com">Cryptonews</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		<enclosure url="https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/11143128/1710167488-1710150207755_processed.jpg" length="179353" type="image/jpeg" />

			</item>
		<item>
		<title>President Biden Proposes Crypto Mining Tax and Wash Sale Rule in 2025 Budget Proposal</title>
		<link>https://cryptonews.com/news/president-biden-proposes-crypto-mining-tax-and-wash-sale-rule-in-2025-budget-proposal.htm</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Julia Smith]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 22:54:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto Mining]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto tax]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Election]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptonews.com/?p=181138</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>President Biden's 2025 budget proposal aims to introduce a crypto mining tax and close the wash sale loophole for digital assets. The move faces opposition from House Republicans, who criticize the administration's spending. As the 2024 presidential race heats up, the outcome could shape the future of crypto regulation.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/president-biden-proposes-crypto-mining-tax-and-wash-sale-rule-in-2025-budget-proposal.htm">President Biden Proposes Crypto Mining Tax and Wash Sale Rule in 2025 Budget Proposal</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptonews.com">Cryptonews</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>U.S. President Joe Biden released his 2025 budget proposal on Monday featuring a number of provisions aimed at altering the cryptocurrency industry, including a wash sale rule for digital assets and an excise tax for crypto mining operations.</p>
<h2><strong>Biden&#8217;s Crypto Mining Tax and Crackdown on Wash Sales</strong></h2>
<p><span class="replacer"></span><br />
If approved, <a href="https://www.whitehouse.gov/omb/briefing-room/2024/03/11/fact-sheet-the-presidents-budget-cuts-taxes-for-working-families-and-makes-big-corporations-and-the-wealthy-pay-their-fair-share/">Biden’s $7.3 trillion budget proposal</a> would see the federal government crack down on crypto “wash sales,” wherein a cryptocurrency holder sells an asset at a loss “to reduce their tax burden” just to buy it back shortly thereafter.</p>
<p>The budget proposal states that it will eliminate the tax subsidy by “modernizing the tax code’s anti-abuse rules to apply to crypto assets just like they apply to stocks and other securities.”</p>
<p>“The Budget saves billions of dollars by closing other tax loopholes that overwhelmingly benefit the rich and the largest, most profitable corporations,” the proposal reads, including “closing a loophole that benefits wealthy crypto investors.”</p>
<p>Similarly, the proposed budget would implement a 30% excise tax corresponding to the cost of energy used by crypto mining firms, according to the <a href="https://home.treasury.gov/system/files/131/General-Explanations-FY2025.pdf">U.S. Treasury Department’s</a> annual “greenbook.”</p>
<p>“The increase in energy consumption attributable to the growth of digital asset mining has negative environmental effects and can have environmental justice implications as well as increase energy prices for those that share an electricity grid with digital asset miners,” the Treasury’s explanation states.</p>
<h2><strong>House Republicans Push Back On Budget Proposal</strong></h2>
<p><span class="replacer"></span><br />
Biden’s 2025 budget faces an uphill battle as Congressional Republicans stand to oppose the proposal. <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/president-joe-biden-critiques-wealthy-crypto-investors-twitter.htm">The President</a> attempted to close the wash sale loophole and implement a crypto mining tax in previous years to no avail.</p>
<p>&#8220;The price tag of President Biden&#8217;s proposed budget is yet another glaring reminder of this Administration&#8217;s insatiable appetite for reckless spending and the Democrats&#8217; disregard for fiscal responsibility,” a statement released by Speaker of the House Mike Johnson (R-LA) alongside House Majority Whip Tom Emmer (R-MN), House Majority Leader Steve Scalise (R-LA), and Representative Elise Stefanik (R-NY) reads. “Biden&#8217;s budget doesn&#8217;t just miss the mark &#8211; it is a roadmap to accelerate America&#8217;s decline.”</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">My joint statement with <a href="https://twitter.com/SteveScalise?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@SteveScalise</a>, <a href="https://twitter.com/GOPMajorityWhip?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@GOPMajorityWhip</a>, and <a href="https://twitter.com/RepStefanik?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@RepStefanik</a> on Biden’s budget proposal: <a href="https://t.co/6StD9YAzMe">pic.twitter.com/6StD9YAzMe</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Speaker Mike Johnson (@SpeakerJohnson) <a href="https://twitter.com/SpeakerJohnson/status/1767224516114051240?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">March 11, 2024</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>Political tensions between Democrats and Republicans continue to simmer as the 2024 presidential election heats up following Super Tuesday and Biden&#8217;s State of the Union Address last week.</p>
<h2><strong>Biden Versus Trump Rematch All But Confirmed</strong></h2>
<p><span class="replacer"></span><br />
Republican frontrunner Donald Trump has come out seemingly in support of cryptocurrencies despite admitting he was &#8220;not a fan&#8221; previously, most recently revealing that his newly released sneaker line is <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/trump-flips-stance-on-bitcoin-im-not-sure-if-id-want-to-take-it-away-at-this-point.htm">accepting payments in bitcoin</a>.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, Biden has pushed for <a href="https://cryptonews.com/cryptocurrency/crypto-regulations/">regulatory guidance on the cryptocurrency industry</a>, going so far as to issue an executive order on &#8220;ensuring the responsible development of cryptocurrency investments&#8221; in 2022.</p>
<p>The 2020 presidential candidates are seemingly poised to face off once again in November once both formally secure their party&#8217;s candidacy.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/president-biden-proposes-crypto-mining-tax-and-wash-sale-rule-in-2025-budget-proposal.htm">President Biden Proposes Crypto Mining Tax and Wash Sale Rule in 2025 Budget Proposal</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptonews.com">Cryptonews</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		<enclosure url="https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/11200230/1710187350-julia_63915_congress_going_over_the_new_presidential_fiscal_bud_5e4b7d85-1b7f-41af-b3de-e1e2e8880ce8-2.jpg" length="162367" type="image/jpeg" />

			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Former BlockFi CEO Announces New Career Path – And Settles Lost Bet On His Company’s Bankruptcy</title>
		<link>https://cryptonews.com/news/former-blockfi-ceo-announces-new-career-path-and-settles-lost-bet-on-his-companys-bankruptcy.htm</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Andrew Throuvalas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 22:38:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BlockFi]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Re Cost Seg]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Real estate]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptonews.com/?p=181123</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Zac Prince, the former BlockFi CEO, is breaking into real estate tech now that his defunct crypto lending firm is on a safe path to recovery.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/former-blockfi-ceo-announces-new-career-path-and-settles-lost-bet-on-his-companys-bankruptcy.htm">Former BlockFi CEO Announces New Career Path – And Settles Lost Bet On His Company’s Bankruptcy</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptonews.com">Cryptonews</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Zac Prince, the former BlockFi CEO, is breaking into real estate tech now that his defunct crypto lending firm is on a safe path to recovery.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">Excited to announce that I’ve joined the team at RE Cost Seg as CEO!</p>
<p>RE Cost Seg provides cost segregation studies to real estate investors. Cost segregation studies enable real estate investors to take advantage of tax benefits by accelerating depreciation.  </p>
<p>When you hear…</p>
<p>&mdash; Zac Prince (@CostSegZac) <a href="https://twitter.com/CostSegZac/status/1767171382469652757?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">March 11, 2024</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>In a <a href="https://twitter.com/CostSegZac/status/1767171382469652757">statement to X</a> on Monday, Prince revealed that he is now the CEO of Re Cost Seg, a firm that provides cost segregation studies to real estate investors.</p>
<h2>BlockFi CEO Pivots To Real Estate</h2>
<p><span class="replacer"></span><br />
Cost segregation studies survey each element of a property and look for certain things that could benefit from accelerated “depreciation” – the period in which a renovator pays for costs associated with improving a property.</p>
<p>This will allow customers to claim tax benefits for accelerating depreciation on those elements, which could include plumbing fixtures, carpeting, and sidewalks, among other things.</p>
<p>Extolling his company’s benefits against more traditional competition, Prince wrote:</p>
<blockquote><p>“Because of lower price points and streamlined processes, RE Cost Seg is making this valuable tax-saving tool available to a much broader group of real estate investors. Previously it was generally limited to larger, commercial properties.”</p></blockquote>
<p>Prince clarified that his business will still primarily focus on institutional clients, but still work with some single-family clients once “priced out” of the opportunity.</p>
<p>The focus marks a pivot from Prince’s retail-oriented crypto lending firm, which offered average investors a chance to earn a yield on their BTC and to take out loans against their coins.</p>
<p>BlockFi’s business model involved rehypothecating those coins to their institutional clients, where they would earn a slightly higher yield than they offered their retail clients, and profit on the difference.</p>
<p>One of their largest counterparties, however, was <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/blockfi-to-receive-874-5-million-from-settlement-with-ftx-and-alameda-research.htm">Alameda Research – FTX’s sister trading firm that imploded last year</a>, losing BlockFi’s and its customers’ coins in the process.</p>
<p>While focused on the ensuing bankruptcy for over a year afterward, Prince said on Sunday that he’s now comfortable moving on to other things.</p>
<blockquote><p>“With estate distributions in flight, and knowing the FTX estate recoveries are trending in a positive direction… I felt that I finally had an appropriate amount of closure to move on to new professional endeavors,” he said.</p></blockquote>
<h2>Settling One Last Bet</h2>
<p><span class="replacer"></span><br />
Prince’s followers were quick to <a href="https://twitter.com/americanhodl8/status/1766867985199948145">call him out on Sunday</a> for having neglected to honor his side of a public bet he made with popular Bitcoiner @americanhodl8 on X.</p>
<p>In 2021, both men bet 1 BTC on whether BlockFi would remain a functional company over the next 37 years. BlockFi’s collapse one year later left Prince as the loser, owing 1 BTC – now worth over $72,000 – to his Twitter adversary.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">Dm me &#8211; will get it sorted</p>
<p>&mdash; Zac Prince (@CostSegZac) <a href="https://twitter.com/CostSegZac/status/1766924096565080432?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">March 10, 2024</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>On Sunday, the former executive agreed that he would “get it sorted.”</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/former-blockfi-ceo-announces-new-career-path-and-settles-lost-bet-on-his-companys-bankruptcy.htm">Former BlockFi CEO Announces New Career Path – And Settles Lost Bet On His Company’s Bankruptcy</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptonews.com">Cryptonews</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		<enclosure url="https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/07063023/1709793023-1709792999245_processed.jpg" length="108436" type="image/jpeg" />

			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Eclipse Labs Raises $50M for Blockchain Scaling Solution Ahead of Mainnet Launch</title>
		<link>https://cryptonews.com/news/eclipse-labs-raises-50m-for-blockchain-scaling-solution-ahead-of-mainnet-launch.htm</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jimmy Aki]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 22:19:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Eclipse Labs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum network]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Solana Ecosystem]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptonews.com/?p=181116</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Eclipse Labs, a multilayered blockchain builder, has raised $50 million in funding to fuel the launch of its innovative solution for scaling the Ethereum network. The announcement was made on March 11 via the X (formerly Twitter) handle, just weeks before the highly anticipated mainnet launch.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/eclipse-labs-raises-50m-for-blockchain-scaling-solution-ahead-of-mainnet-launch.htm">Eclipse Labs Raises $50M for Blockchain Scaling Solution Ahead of Mainnet Launch</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptonews.com">Cryptonews</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Eclipse Labs, a multilayered blockchain builder, has raised $50 million in funding to fuel the launch of its solution for scaling the Ethereum network.</p>
<p>The <a href="https://x.com/EclipseFND/status/1767212277285969979?s=20">announcement was made on March 11 via the X</a> (formerly Twitter) handle, just weeks before the mainnet launch.</p>
<h2>Eclipse Labs’ Developer-First Focus Approach</h2>
<p><span class="replacer"></span><br />
Eclipse Labs offers a <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/best-layer-2-blockchain-tokens.htm">flexible Layer-2 solution</a> (rollup) for blockchain developers. It lets them choose from different virtual machines, like Sealevel, to build custom blockchains that benefit from the security of established networks like Ethereum and Polygon.</p>
<p>Last month, they launched the Sealevel virtual machine (SVM) Layer 2 <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/polygon-introduces-agglayer-aims-to-simplify-blockchain-integration-across-platforms.htm">blockchain for Polygon</a> to ease migration from Solana to Polygon.</p>
<p>This newly funded release will emulate the Polygon SVM but with a focus on Ethereum, leveraging a blend of modern technologies from established blockchains. The multi-layered blend will combine <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/new-cryptocurrency.htm">Ethereum, Solana, Celestia, and RISC Zero elements</a>.</p>
<p>The ultimate goal is to achieve faster transaction speeds on Solana without compromising Ethereum&#8217;s security.</p>
<p>Regarding the potential impact on both ecosystems, <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/ex-terra-developer-raises-funds-for-this-new-project.htm">Neel Somani</a>, CEO of Eclipse Labs, stated that the solution will be a “net additive for both ecosystems.”</p>
<p>He emphasized this significance, stating that from an ETH perspective, the development is an important way for Ethereum to scale.</p>
<p>“For Solana, we&#8217;re bringing more people into the Solana Virtual Machine,” he said.</p>
<p>In December 2023, Eclipse launched the test net with the intention of prioritizing developers. Opening the mainnet to developers in the coming weeks gives them a platform to build applications that benefit from the project&#8217;s architecture.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">Eclipse Testnet is live.</p>
<p>This marks a significant step towards bringing the Solana Virtual Machine (SVM) to Ethereum L2. <a href="https://t.co/4VAZh2W5A0">pic.twitter.com/4VAZh2W5A0</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Eclipse (@EclipseFND) <a href="https://twitter.com/EclipseFND/status/1734966671457329478?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">December 13, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>While a user-friendly bridge for regular cryptocurrency users may come later, this developer-centric approach is meant to be a foundation before wider adoption.</p>
<p>Eclipse Labs also prioritizes decentralization by planning to hand over control to its stakeholders gradually. This likely means a future shift towards a community-driven governance model.</p>
<p>The company has not yet publicized its specifics, but a potential token airdrop might be coming. This approach is similar to that decentralized projects adopt to facilitate community involvement.</p>
<h2>Building Bridges Between Ecosystems</h2>
<p><span class="replacer"></span><br />
Eclipse Labs is essentially attempting to foster collaboration and interoperability between the Ethereum and <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/solana-february-2024-report-sol-price-analysis.htm">Solana ecosystems</a>. This approach allows applications built for Solana to run on Eclipse with minimal modifications.</p>
<p>Additionally, <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/will-this-new-0-01-cryptocurrency-be-the-next-solana-sol.htm">SOL tokens</a> will remain the primary currency within the Eclipse ecosystem, further bridging the gap between the two major blockchain players.</p>
<p>While the initial launch caters to developers, the project has garnered interest from established players in the Decentralized Finance (DeFi) space.</p>
<p>Major Solana protocols like Solend have expressed their intent to deploy on Eclipse, highlighting its potential to streamline DeFi operations.</p>
<p>Rooter, the developer of Solend, expressed his enthusiasm about the potential benefits of deploying on Eclipse, stating that it was a good bet.</p>
<p>Like similar projects with exciting promises, its success lies in delivering on these promises of faster, secure, and interoperable transactions.</p>
<p>If successful, it could become a key player in bridging the gap between existing blockchains and fostering a more connected future for decentralized applications.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/eclipse-labs-raises-50m-for-blockchain-scaling-solution-ahead-of-mainnet-launch.htm">Eclipse Labs Raises $50M for Blockchain Scaling Solution Ahead of Mainnet Launch</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptonews.com">Cryptonews</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		<enclosure url="https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/11190944/1710184184-1710181502282_processed.webp" length="35660" type="image/webp" />

			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Top Crypto Gainers Today on DEX Screener – OPC, Husky, CETI</title>
		<link>https://cryptonews.com/news/top-crypto-gainers-today-on-dex-screener-opc-husky-ceti.htm</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Joel Frank]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 22:15:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DEXTools]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Shitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[top crypto gainers today]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptonews.com/?p=181178</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>As Bitcoin (BTC) pushed towards $73,000 on Monday and Ether (ETH) above $4,000, the crypto market rally broadened in favor of recent laggards, with the likes of XRP (XRP) and Litecoin (LTC) experiencing notable pumps--though these coins were far from the top crypto gainers today.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/top-crypto-gainers-today-on-dex-screener-opc-husky-ceti.htm">Top Crypto Gainers Today on DEX Screener – OPC, Husky, CETI</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptonews.com">Cryptonews</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>As Bitcoin (BTC) pushed towards $73,000 on Monday and Ether (ETH) above $4,000, the crypto market rally has broadened in favor of recent laggards, with the likes of XRP (XRP) and Litecoin (LTC) experiencing notable pumps&#8211;though these coins were far from the top crypto gainers today.</p>
<p>XRP rallied 16% and Litecoin 20% in the past 24 hours, <a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/">CoinMarketCap data shows</a>.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptonews.com/coins/bitcoin/">Bitcoin (BTC)</a> and <a href="https://cryptonews.com/guides/ethereum/">Ether (ETH)</a>, meanwhile, were each up in the region of 4% over the same time period.</p>
<p>The market continues to derive strong support from <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/blackrock-spot-bitcoin-etf-aum-hits-10b-overtaking-the-ishares-silver-trust.htm">spot Bitcoin ETF inflows</a>, which come ahead of next month’s halving.</p>
<p>Ethereum is also set to undergo a major upgrade this week that should give a particular boost for <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/ethereum-layer-2-platforms-now-manage-over-36-7-billion-a-record-high.htm">layer-2 protocols</a>.</p>
<p>While the outlook for the broader market remains positive, <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/best-low-cap-crypto.htm">crypto traders looking for quick gains continue to hunt low-cap coins</a>.</p>
<p>And the undoubtedly best, though also riskiest, place to find such coins is in the <a href="https://cryptonews.com/cryptocurrency/best-shitcoins-buy/">on-chain shitcoin markets</a>.</p>
<p>On-chain markets refer to the market for assets (like <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/nft-news/">NFTs</a> or <a href="https://cryptonews.com/guides/best-erc20-wallets.htm">ERC-20</a> tokens) that have been issued on another <a href="https://cryptonews.com/cryptocurrency/blockchain-technology/">blockchain</a>.</p>
<p>For example, the <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/shiba-inu-price-prediction-as-shib-reaches-20-billion-market-cap-10-shib-possible.htm">Shiba Inu (SHIB)</a> token lives on the Ethereum blockchain as an ERC-20 token.</p>
<p>The thing with on-chain markets is that almost anyone can launch any coin at any time.</p>
<p>On-chain markets are thus a swamp of shitcoins, the majority of which are either <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/approval-phishing-scams-see-explosive-growth.htm">scams</a> or <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/ksi-faces-pump-and-dump-allegations-after-reopening-crypto-focused-x-account.htm">pump-and-dump schemes</a>.</p>
<p>Still, thanks to their low liquidity and tiny market caps, shitcoin markets are the only market where an investors can 10x (or more) their initial investment in under 24 hours.</p>
<p>Here are some of the top crypto gainers today in the shitcoin market that traders will be watching.</p>
<h2><strong>Top Crypto Gainers Today</strong></h2>
<p><span class="replacer"></span></p>
<h3><strong>OpClouds ($OPC)</strong></h3>
<p>A just-launched shitcoin called OpClouds ($OPC) which claims to be transforming <a href="https://cryptonews.com/cryptocurrency/best-depin-coins/">decentralized physical infrastructure (DePIN)</a> with decentralized computing resources as a service has seen a big 21,500% pump on its first day of trade, <a href="https://www.dextools.io/app/en/ether/pair-explorer/0xc046b2e3542427d07f511a3a014cda9d471eda3a?t=1710193411969">as per DEXTools</a>.</p>
<p>That has seen its market cap rise to $1.97 million, and liquidity reach $250,000.</p>
<p>It’s worth noting that liquidity is locked, reducing the risk of a rug pull.</p>
<p>But Quick Intel’s audit of its smart contract shows there is a hefty 20.9% sell tax.</p>
<p>Investors should always do their due diligence when investing in shitcoins.</p>
<h3><strong>HuskyInu ($HUSKY)</strong></h3>
<p>Husky-themed meme coin HuskyInu ($HUSKY) is up nearly 22,000% since launching on Monday, <a href="https://www.dextools.io/app/en/ether/pair-explorer/0x4539044f1fbcb9b05d0f9105bf73981c7b30ce1c?t=1710193413700">as per DEXTools</a>.</p>
<p>That has seen the token’s market cap rise to $876,000 and liquidity to around $270,000.</p>
<p>The token also has close to 300 holders, with $150,000 in volume having changed hands.</p>
<p>DEXTools’ security audit reveals no concerning aspects to the token’s smart contract.</p>
<p>But that doesn’t mean the token isn&#8217;t a pump-and-dump scheme for sure.</p>
<p>Again, always do your own research before getting involved in shitcoin markets.</p>
<h3><strong>Tao Ceti ($CETI)</strong></h3>
<p>Another DePIN shitcoin called Tao Ceti ($CETI) has pumped over 4,500% on Monday, hitting a market cap near $11 million.</p>
<p>The shitcoin has nearly $2.7 million in liquidity and has seen volumes of $1.65 million since launch.</p>
<p>It has a 5% tax but, concerningly, this is modifiable.</p>
<p>Traders should thus be very cautious as the token’s issuer could easily jack this up to 100%.</p>
<p><strong>Alternatives to Consider – Smog (SMOG)</strong></p>
<p>Shitcoins are highly risky. Most are either outright scams or, at the very least, pump-and-dump schemes designed to leave unsuspecting investors holding the bag.</p>
<p>A much better strategy is to look for more established meme coins that already have a presence but haven’t seen a massive pump just yet.</p>
<p>One such meme coin is a recently launched Solana coin called Smog (SMOG).</p>
<p>Its price has pumped nearly 8x since late February to reach a market cap of $270 million, <a href="https://www.dextools.io/app/en/solana/pair-explorer/G6oNRyjP2WAVDUTYFPZsgBBxxMetyQEi2AYbmzRNe7Mc?t=1709910872407">as per DEXTools</a>.</p>
<p><iframe title="Smog Coin: Skyrocketing Past 30 Cents - Is $1 Just a Breath Away?" width="640" height="360" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/ZSTm5z1ysuE?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" allowfullscreen></iframe></p>
<p>The dragon-themed token markets itself as offering Solana’s greatest airdrop of all time.</p>
<p>Traders can qualify for the airdrop by buying and holding SMOG on Solana, or staking the token on Ethereum.</p>
<p>Even though its market cap remains modest, SMOG already boasts a strong community.</p>
<p>Indeed, <a href="https://birdeye.so/token/FS66v5XYtJAFo14LiPz5HT93EUMAHmYipCfQhLpU4ss8?chain=solana">as per birdeye.so</a>, it already has over 60,000 holders.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptonews.com/cryptocurrency/solana-airdrops/">Given all the excitement about Solana airdrops in recent months</a>, SMOG could gain significant interest in the coming weeks.</p>
<p>SMOG could deliver at least 10x gains to investors, hence its rank in the best crypto meme coins to buy now.</p>
<p>Traders should note that they can clinch a 10% discount when buying SMOG directly through the project’s website.</p>
<p>They can also stake their tokens for a 42% APY.</p>
<p><strong><a href="https://www.cryptonews.com/ext/smog/en">Buy SMOG Here</a></strong></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/top-crypto-gainers-today-on-dex-screener-opc-husky-ceti.htm">Top Crypto Gainers Today on DEX Screener – OPC, Husky, CETI</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptonews.com">Cryptonews</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		<enclosure url="https://cryptonews.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/12/1703898503-dextools.jpg" length="151779" type="image/jpeg" />

			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Asset Protocol BRC-20 Enhances Governance with New Maintainers</title>
		<link>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-asset-protocol-brc-20-enhances-governance-with-new-maintainers.htm</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jimmy Aki]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 20:26:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Asset]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BRC-20]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ordinal Technology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptonews.com/?p=181081</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The BRC-20 protocol, a well-known standard for creating tokens on the Bitcoin blockchain, underwent a major overhaul in its governance structure. This strategic move aims to foster a more decentralized and collaborative future for the protocol.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-asset-protocol-brc-20-enhances-governance-with-new-maintainers.htm">Bitcoin Asset Protocol BRC-20 Enhances Governance with New Maintainers</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptonews.com">Cryptonews</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p data-sourcepos="5:1-5:350">The developer of the BRC-20 token standard, known as Domo, revealed a shift in the token&#8217;s governance on Monday. The creator&#8217;s non-profit, the Layer 1 Foundation (L1F), will now oversee the protocol&#8217;s token management.</p>
<p data-sourcepos="5:1-5:350">Domo announced that <a href="https://www.coindesk.com/tech/2024/03/11/brc-20-creator-domo-addresses-thorny-governance-issues-with-new-lead-maintainer-appointments/">L1F will collaborate with UniSat and Best in Slot</a>, key Bitcoin infrastructure providers, to serve as BRC-20&#8217;s lead maintainers.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">Overheard<a href="https://twitter.com/isabelfoxenduke?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@isabelfoxenduke</a> :</p>
<p>“Layer 1 foundation will explore decentralized governance structure for BRC 20 tokens”</p>
<p>&mdash; Cosmos Joe<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f9e9.png" alt="🧩" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> (@CosmosDefi) <a href="https://twitter.com/CosmosDefi/status/1767213942449881111?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">March 11, 2024</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p data-sourcepos="7:1-7:267">BRC-20 operates on the Bitcoin network&#8217;s Ordinals Protocol, enabling the movement of non-BTC digital assets. The technology utilizes &#8220;<a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/solana-nft-sales-drops-80-bybit-introduces-marketplace-for-bitcoin-and-evm-inscriptions-more-top-nft-news.htm">inscriptions</a>&#8221; on satoshis, which are small units of BTC, to track, store data, and facilitate asset transfers on the Bitcoin Network.</p>
<h2 data-sourcepos="9:1-9:33">BRC-20 Partnerships and Advancements</h2>
<p><span class="replacer"></span></p>
<p data-sourcepos="11:1-11:379">Governance for both the protocol and within the broader Bitcoin network has <a href="https://stanford-jblp.pubpub.org/pub/bitcoin-governance">historically been a complex issue</a>.</p>
<p data-sourcepos="11:1-11:379">This was evident earlier in the year with a disagreement between Domo and UniSat, an Ordinals Protocol marketplace. <a href="https://unisat-wallet.medium.com/2024-01-the-story-of-unisats-indexer-e33053f905ae">UniSat supported a protocol upgrade for Ordinals</a> known as &#8220;Jubilee&#8221; which Domo opposed, stating it had the potential to divide the growing environment.</p>
<p data-sourcepos="13:1-13:296">Despite this past conflict, Domo recognized UniSat&#8217;s crucial early role in decentralizing the BRC-20 ecosystem.</p>
<h2 data-sourcepos="19:1-19:31"><strong>Oversight and Future Growth</strong></h2>
<p><span class="replacer"></span></p>
<p data-sourcepos="13:1-13:296">UniSat was the first marketplace to list BRC-20 tokens and collaboration between UniSat and Best in Slot resulted in the creation of a <a href="https://cryptonews.com/exclusives/5-crypto-index-tokens-that-allow-you-buy-market.htm">decentralized indexing</a> product for BRC-20.</p>
<p data-sourcepos="17:1-17:254">&#8220;The goal is to support the growth of Bitcoin metaprotocols on Ordinals and beyond,&#8221; Domo stated. &#8220;BRC-20 was an early experiment—but we’re seeing a wave of standards that need tools, infrastructure, and support to thrive.&#8221;</p>
<p data-sourcepos="21:1-21:309">To support the BRC-20 standard&#8217;s governance framework, Domo created an oversight committee, which includes the <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-billionaire-arthur-hayes-and-brc-20-creator-domo-invest-in-bitcoin-ordinals-wallet-oyls-3m-raise.htm">Bitcoin Ordinals wallet</a>, Oyl (which recently completed a pre-seed funding round with Domo&#8217;s investment), and UXTO Management, part of Bitcoin Magazine&#8217;s parent company, BTC Inc.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-asset-protocol-brc-20-enhances-governance-with-new-maintainers.htm">Bitcoin Asset Protocol BRC-20 Enhances Governance with New Maintainers</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptonews.com">Cryptonews</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		<enclosure url="https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/11173558/1710178557-1710175725931_processed.webp" length="48806" type="image/webp" />

			</item>
		<item>
		<title>UAE Integrates Cardano Blockchain for Enhanced Criminal Investigation Security</title>
		<link>https://cryptonews.com/news/uae-integrates-cardano-blockchain-for-enhanced-criminal-investigation-security.htm</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jimmy Aki]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 20:00:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cardano]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[UAE]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptonews.com/?p=181100</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The United Arab Emirates (UAE) has integrated Cardano blockchain technology to ensure security in criminal investigations. During the World Police Summit in Dubai from March 5 to March 7, 2024, the Dubai police showcased a flagship project based on Cardano.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/uae-integrates-cardano-blockchain-for-enhanced-criminal-investigation-security.htm">UAE Integrates Cardano Blockchain for Enhanced Criminal Investigation Security</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptonews.com">Cryptonews</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>During this year&#8217;s World Police Summit in Dubai on March 5-7, the United Arab Emirates made headlines by adopting Cardano blockchain technology to enhance the security of its criminal investigations. The Dubai Police&#8217;s use of the technology marks a major step towards blockchains integration into the mainstream.</p>
<p><a href="https://twitter.com/TheCardanoTimes/status/1767006988624409071?t=JJ52MnQ9rylncbISISJF7Q&amp;s=19">The showcase with the Cardano-based project</a> evidenced the secure exchange of forensic data with international security agencies like Interpol, spotlighting the technology&#8217;s efficacy in data management security.</p>
<h2>Dubai Police Adopt Cardano Blockchain</h2>
<p><span class="replacer"></span><br />
According to Chris O, the creator of Cardano GhostFund DAO, the Dubai Police&#8217;s <a href="https://cryptonews.com/tags/cardano/">choice to employ Cardano</a> highlights the blockchain&#8217;s potential for safe and unhackable data management.</p>
<p>He also stressed that using the blockchain guarantees that information is unaltered and makes it traceable for the different parties.</p>
<p>For example, technology may make it easier for international parties to share sensitive forensic data safely.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr"><a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Cardano?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#Cardano</a> fam, massive real world adoption update by <a href="https://twitter.com/Cardano_CF?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@Cardano_CF</a>!</p>
<p>One of the wealthiest nations in the world, UAE is employing <a href="https://twitter.com/Cardano?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@Cardano</a> to secure its Criminal investigations!</p>
<p>The Dubai Police presented at the World Police Summit in Dubai a Cardano based pilot project. The… <a href="https://t.co/zjzXOJZCcM">pic.twitter.com/zjzXOJZCcM</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Chris O (@TheOCcryptobro) <a href="https://twitter.com/TheOCcryptobro/status/1766859456221249676?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">March 10, 2024</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>Security expert Omar Shands commented on the Dubai Police’s adoption of the Cardano blockchain, saying blockchain is a valuable tool that is becoming increasingly relevant in the security sector.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">Criminal investigations secured by the Cardano blockchain <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f693.png" alt="🚓" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" />  <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f46e-200d-2642-fe0f.png" alt="👮‍♂️" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> </p>
<p><img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f6a8.png" alt="🚨" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> Today the Dubai Police presented at the World Police Summit in Dubai an exciting blockchain-based pilot project. The project will showcase how sensitive data from criminal investigations can be shared securely…</p>
<p>&mdash; Omar Shands, President &#8211; Skypath Security (@Skypath_Pres) <a href="https://twitter.com/Skypath_Pres/status/1765732380709380434?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">March 7, 2024</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>The adoption of blockchain technology by the UAE&#8217;s law enforcement has the potential to set a global precedent for other countries seeking to <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/how-to-enhance-crypto-security-in-2024.htm">enhance their security</a> infrastructure through advanced solutions as well.</p>
<h2>The Potential of Blockchain in Law Enforcement</h2>
<p><span class="replacer"></span><br />
Blockchain technology holds immense potential to introduce unique and effective law enforcement practices, offering novel solutions to address contemporary criminal investigations and security challenges.</p>
<p>Proactive law enforcement worldwide uses blockchain technology to track criminals and their activities. It has shown huge potential and effectiveness in addressing money laundering, terrorism financing, and more.</p>
<p>Law enforcement organizations also have great potential to deploy blockchain analytics solutions to manage investigative data, policymaking, and compliance.</p>
<p>For instance, <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/china-warms-up-to-blockchain-technology-1329.htm">China leverages blockchain technology</a> to generate tamper-proof data to ensure the security of judicial data.</p>
<p>Additionally, blockchain analytics can be deployed to manage investigative data, formulate policies, and ensure compliance. The <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/uks-national-crime-agency-seeks-to-set-up-specialized-team-to-combat-cryptocurrency-scams-and-fraud.htm">UK&#8217;s National Crime Agency</a> (NCA) has embraced blockchain detectives as part of its strategy to combat crypto crimes, for example.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/uae-integrates-cardano-blockchain-for-enhanced-criminal-investigation-security.htm">UAE Integrates Cardano Blockchain for Enhanced Criminal Investigation Security</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptonews.com">Cryptonews</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		<enclosure url="https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/11180747/1710180467-1710180103681_processed.webp" length="43548" type="image/webp" />

			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Elon Musk to Open-Source AI Chatbot Grok Amid Ongoing OpenAI Lawsuit</title>
		<link>https://cryptonews.com/news/elon-musk-to-open-source-ai-chatbot-grok-amid-ongoing-openai-lawsuit.htm</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jimmy Aki]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 19:45:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Technology News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Elon Musk]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Grok]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[OpenAI]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptonews.com/?p=181051</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Elon Musk, CEO of artificial intelligence (AI) company xAI, has announced the open sourcing of Grok, a ChatGPT competitor. He announced this decision days after Musk filed a lawsuit against OpenAI, a company he co-founded, for allegedly abandoning its original non-profit mission.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/elon-musk-to-open-source-ai-chatbot-grok-amid-ongoing-openai-lawsuit.htm">Elon Musk to Open-Source AI Chatbot Grok Amid Ongoing OpenAI Lawsuit</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptonews.com">Cryptonews</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>xAI CEO Elon Musk is making ChatGPT competitor Grok open-source. His decision comes after Musk filed a lawsuit against OpenAI, a company he co-founded, for allegedly abandoning its original non-profit mission.</p>
<p>Musk&#8217;s intention to open-source Grok was <a href="https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/1752098683024220632">announced on a March 11 X post</a>. This move aligns with Musk&#8217;s long-standing advocacy for responsible AI development, as demonstrated by his call for a &#8220;third-party referee&#8221; in AI development at the UK&#8217;s AI Safety Summit in 2023.</p>
<h2>xAI&#8217;s Grok and Musk&#8217;s Vision</h2>
<p><span class="replacer"></span><br />
Elon Musk&#8217;s departure from OpenAI due to disagreements over the organization&#8217;s direction and strategy led him to launch xAI. The <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/hundreds-of-grok-tokens-launched-days-after-elon-musk-backed-chatgpt-rival-goes-live.htm">launch of Grok in November 2023</a> further highlighted Musk&#8217;s commitment to open-source and non-profit AI initiatives.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">The first human received an implant from <a href="https://twitter.com/neuralink?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@Neuralink</a> yesterday and is recovering well.</p>
<p>Initial results show promising neuron spike detection.</p>
<p>&mdash; Elon Musk (@elonmusk) <a href="https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/1752098683024220632?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">January 29, 2024</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>In a <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=JN3KPFbWCy8">November podcast with Lex Fridman</a>, Musk criticized OpenAI&#8217;s transition from a non-profit, open-source initiative to a profit-driven, closed-source model.</p>
<p>Specifically, Musk is recognized for his opposition to large tech companies profiting from AI development, frequently highlighting concerns about the ethical implications of such practices.</p>
<p>Open-sourcing Grok will align xAI with companies like France&#8217;s Mistral, which advocates for open access to AI models.</p>
<p>This approach allows developers to collaborate and accelerate improvements.</p>
<p>Regardless, tech investors are divided on open-sourcing AI, particularly in light of Musk&#8217;s lawsuit. While some see it as a catalyst for innovation, others are worried about potential misuse.</p>
<h2>Musk&#8217;s Legal Battle with OpenAI</h2>
<p><span class="replacer"></span><br />
Recently, Musk <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/worldcoin-price-dips-as-elon-musk-sues-openai-and-sam-altman.htm">filed a lawsuit</a> against OpenAI, claiming it breached the agreement made when OpenAI was founded as a non-profit organization.</p>
<p>He argued that <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/worldcoins-wld-gains-6-as-sam-altman-joins-microsoft-to-lead-its-new-ai-research-team.htm">OpenAI&#8217;s partnership with Microsoft</a>, reportedly worth nearly $3 billion by 2023, contradicted its original mission of advancing open-source AI for the benefit of humanity.</p>
<p>The lawsuit urged OpenAI to return to its open-source principles and prevent the for-profit exploitation of Artificial General Intelligence (AGI) technology.</p>
<p>In response to the accusations, OpenAI released emails suggesting that Musk had previously agreed to transform the AI company into a for-profit entity. This revelation came a few months after CEO Sam Altman was reinstated to the board following his <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/sam-altmans-departure-from-openai-triggers-a-sharp-decline-in-worldcoins-value-whats-going-on.htm">five-day dismissal</a> in November 2023.</p>
<p>Grok is an AI chatbot similar to OpenAI&#8217;s ChatGPT, but can access real-time information through X and tackle sensitive topics that other AI systems might avoid.</p>
<p>The Grok-1 large language model powers it, and while it is more advanced than GPT-3.5, <a href="https://generativeai.pub/grok-vs-chatgpt-4-a-comprehensive-comparison-dc97ca54f754">Grok reportedly falls short of OpenAI&#8217;s latest GPT-4</a> model in overall performance.</p>
<p>Musk&#8217;s announcement on X has seen mostly positive responses, with many users praising his commitment to open-source AI.</p>
<p>One user on X suggested, &#8220;OpenAI should do the same. If they are &#8216;open,&#8217; that is.&#8221;</p>
<p>Musk <a href="https://x.com/elonmusk/status/1767110461772706062?s=20">responded by stating</a>, &#8220;OpenAI is a lie.”</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/elon-musk-to-open-source-ai-chatbot-grok-amid-ongoing-openai-lawsuit.htm">Elon Musk to Open-Source AI Chatbot Grok Amid Ongoing OpenAI Lawsuit</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptonews.com">Cryptonews</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		<enclosure url="https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/11165641/1710176201-1710160663713_processed.webp" length="52458" type="image/webp" />

			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Price Prediction as BlackRock&#8217;s Spot ETF Holdings Surpass MicroStrategy – Are Institutional Investors Here?</title>
		<link>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-blackrocks-spot-etf-holdings-surpass-microstrategy-are-institutional-investors-here.htm</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Arslan Butt]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 19:35:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin news]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptonews.com/?p=180837</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>As BlackRock's Bitcoin ETF overtakes MicroStrategy, signaling a seismic shift in institutional investment, Bitcoin's price trajectory hints at an exciting future in the crypto realm.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-blackrocks-spot-etf-holdings-surpass-microstrategy-are-institutional-investors-here.htm">Bitcoin Price Prediction as BlackRock&#8217;s Spot ETF Holdings Surpass MicroStrategy – Are Institutional Investors Here?</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptonews.com">Cryptonews</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<figure id="attachment_180841" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-180841" style="width: 1280px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><img decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-180841" src="https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/11125220/1710161539-11-1.jpg" alt="Bitcoin Price Prediction" width="1280" height="720" srcset="https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/11125220/1710161539-11-1.jpg 1280w, https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/11125220/1710161539-11-1-300x169.jpg 300w, https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/11125220/1710161539-11-1-1024x576.jpg 1024w, https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/11125220/1710161539-11-1-768x432.jpg 768w, https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/11125220/1710161539-11-1-150x84.jpg 150w" sizes="(max-width: 1280px) 100vw, 1280px" /><figcaption id="caption-attachment-180841" class="wp-caption-text">Bitcoin Price Prediction</figcaption></figure>
<p>With BlackRock&#8217;s IBIT <a href="https://twitter.com/BitMEXResearch/status/1766359858893262958">amassing 197,943 BTC</a>, valued at over $13.5 billion, the narrative around Bitcoin and its investment allure is undergoing a remarkable transformation.</p>
<p>This shift comes on the heels of the United States Securities and Exchange Commission&#8217;s approval of nine new funds, highlighting the escalating institutional demand propelling Bitcoin&#8217;s value.</p>
<p>As Bitcoin&#8217;s price breached the $72,000 threshold, the spotlight intensifies on the potential trajectory of this leading cryptocurrency.</p>
<h2><strong>BlackRock&#8217;s Spot ETF Holdings Outshine MicroStrategy</strong></h2>
<p><span class="replacer"></span><br />
BlackRock&#8217;s leap into the forefront with its spot <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-27.htm">Bitcoin ETF holdings</a> surpassing those of MicroStrategy signifies a pivotal moment in the cryptocurrency domain.</p>
<p>This development is not just a milestone for BlackRock but signals a broader trend of growing institutional investment in Bitcoin, potentially reshaping market dynamics and price predictions.</p>
<p>With ETFs excluding Grayscale&#8217;s GBTC now holding assets exceeding $28 billion, institutional interest is undeniably a driving force behind Bitcoin&#8217;s ascent.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">[1/4] Bitcoin ETF Flow &#8211; 08 March 2024</p>
<p>All data in. $223m positive net flow for thew day</p>
<p>The assets of the ETFs excluding GBTC are now over $28 billion, this is now larger than GBTC&#39;s assets for the first time <a href="https://t.co/5BlBTu4WLn">pic.twitter.com/5BlBTu4WLn</a></p>
<p>&mdash; BitMEX Research (@BitMEXResearch) <a href="https://twitter.com/BitMEXResearch/status/1766359858893262958?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">March 9, 2024</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>Amidst this institutional rally, MicroStrategy continues to fortify its Bitcoin strategy, with plans to raise over $600 million to augment its Bitcoin reserves.</p>
<p>This aggressive accumulation strategy, paired with CEO Michael Saylor&#8217;s steadfast belief in Bitcoin&#8217;s supremacy over traditional assets, underscores a deepening conviction among corporate entities in Bitcoin&#8217;s long-term value.</p>
<p>As institutional players like BlackRock and MicroStrategy jostle for dominance in the Bitcoin space, the question looms: Are institutional investors here to stay, and what does this mean for <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction.htm">Bitcoin&#8217;s price prediction</a> and the future of cryptocurrency investment?</p>
<h2 class="c-message_attachment">Bitcoin Price Update</h2>
<p><span class="replacer"></span><br />
Bitcoin&#8217;s market presence remains formidable, with its price today hitting $72,500, showcasing a notable 4.50% increase over the past 24 hours.</p>
<p>This surge brings its <a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/currencies/bitcoin/">market capitalization</a> to a staggering $1.425 trillion, securing its top position in the cryptocurrency arena.</p>
<p>Currently, Bitcoin&#8217;s circulating supply is at 19,651,543 BTC, edging closer to its 21 million max supply limit.</p>
<h2 class="c-message_attachment">Bitcoin Price Prediction</h2>
<p><span class="replacer"></span><br />
From a technical standpoint, <a href="https://cryptonews.com/coins/bitcoin/">Bitcoin (BTC/USD)</a>&#8216;s pivot point holds at around $70,013 serves as a foundation for its current trajectory.</p>
<p>Resistance levels are identified at $73,824, $76,749, and $79,904, each marking potential hurdles for upward movement. Conversely, support levels at $67,154, $64,861, and $62,192 provide cushions against declines.</p>
<p>The Relative Strength Index (RSI) stands at 72, indicating potential overbought conditions, while the Moving Average Convergence Divergence (MACD) displays a value of 174 with a signal line at 1177, suggesting a bullish momentum as the MACD line overtakes the signal line.</p>
<figure id="attachment_180840" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-180840" style="width: 1730px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-180840" src="https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/11125059/1710161458-image-3.png" alt="Bitcoin Price Prediction" width="1730" height="961" srcset="https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/11125059/1710161458-image-3.png 1730w, https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/11125059/1710161458-image-3-300x167.png 300w, https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/11125059/1710161458-image-3-1024x569.png 1024w, https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/11125059/1710161458-image-3-768x427.png 768w, https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/11125059/1710161458-image-3-1536x853.png 1536w, https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/11125059/1710161458-image-3-150x83.png 150w" sizes="(max-width: 1730px) 100vw, 1730px" /><figcaption id="caption-attachment-180840" class="wp-caption-text">Bitcoin Price Prediction</figcaption></figure>
<p>Notably, Bitcoin&#8217;s breakthrough above the $70,000 threshold and the emergence of bullish engulfing candlesticks signal a potent uptrend, with potential targets at $73,800 or higher.</p>
<p>The 50-day Exponential Moving Average (EMA) at $66,860 underpins this bullish sentiment, offering additional support to Bitcoin&#8217;s price.</p>
<p>In conclusion, the overall trend for Bitcoin appears bullish above the $72,200 mark.</p>
<h2>Eco-Friendly Bitcoin: Revolutionizing Cryptocurrency with Gamified Eco-Staking</h2>
<p><span class="replacer"></span><br />
<a href="https://cryptonews.com/ext/greenbitcoin">Green Bitcoin</a>  is leading a revolutionary shift in the cryptocurrency sphere by blending the urgency of environmental conservation with the innovative landscape of digital currency.</p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Breakdown of Token Distribution:</span></p>
<ul>
<li><span data-preserver-spaces="true"><strong>Initial Offering (40%):</strong> Launches the currency with significant momentum, setting the stage for sustained growth.</span></li>
<li><span data-preserver-spaces="true"><strong>Staking Incentives (27.50%):</strong> Allocates a major share to appreciate the enduring engagement of community members, vital for the ecosystem&#8217;s thriving.</span></li>
<li><span data-preserver-spaces="true"><strong>Promotional Activities (17.50%):</strong> Directs resources towards essential promotional strategies to build and broaden the currency&#8217;s worldwide recognition.</span></li>
<li><span data-preserver-spaces="true"><strong>Trading Fluidity (10%):</strong> Guarantees smooth trading experiences, bolstering the token&#8217;s availability across exchanges.</span></li>
<li><span data-preserver-spaces="true"><strong>Community Engagement Rewards (5%):</strong> Acknowledges and motivates the core community&#8217;s involvement, enhancing participation and dedication.</span></li>
</ul>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The &#8216;Eco Pathway&#8217; charts a definitive course for Eco-Friendly Bitcoin, initiating with a value-centric initial offering and progressing through deliberate actions to energize the community and cement the token&#8217;s standing in the marketplace.</span></p>
<ul>
<li><span data-preserver-spaces="true"><strong>Imminent Price Surge:</strong> Only 4 Days Away</span></li>
<li><span data-preserver-spaces="true"><strong>Current Funding:</strong> $<span class="fw-regular">3,320,984.7</span><span class="fw-regular text-light-grey"> </span>of $3,439,628</span></li>
<li><span data-preserver-spaces="true"><strong>Current Exchange Rate:</strong> 1 $EFCB = $0.8022</span></li>
</ul>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Venture into the world of Eco-Friendly Bitcoin where your investment transcends mere profit to bolster a sustainable financial ecosystem. Invest today and join the movement towards a greener future.</span></p>
<h3><a href="https://cryptonews.com/ext/greenbitcoin"><strong>Get Green Bitcoin Here</strong></a></h3>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-blackrocks-spot-etf-holdings-surpass-microstrategy-are-institutional-investors-here.htm">Bitcoin Price Prediction as BlackRock&#8217;s Spot ETF Holdings Surpass MicroStrategy – Are Institutional Investors Here?</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptonews.com">Cryptonews</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		<enclosure url="https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/11125220/1710161539-11-1.jpg" length="174256" type="image/jpeg" />

			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Trump Flips Stance on Bitcoin: &#8220;I&#8217;m Not Sure If I&#8217;d Want to Take it Away At This Point&#8221;</title>
		<link>https://cryptonews.com/news/trump-flips-stance-on-bitcoin-im-not-sure-if-id-want-to-take-it-away-at-this-point.htm</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Julia Smith]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 18:07:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[spot Bitcoin ETF]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trump]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptonews.com/?p=181033</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Republican presidential frontrunner Donald Trump took to CNBC Monday to reveal he is unsure whether he would want to get rid of bitcoin despite chastizing it in the past, going so far as to say he has “fun” with the cryptocurrency. Trump's comments come amidst a promising bitcoin rally, with the token rallying above $72,000 Monday morning.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/trump-flips-stance-on-bitcoin-im-not-sure-if-id-want-to-take-it-away-at-this-point.htm">Trump Flips Stance on Bitcoin: &#8220;I&#8217;m Not Sure If I&#8217;d Want to Take it Away At This Point&#8221;</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptonews.com">Cryptonews</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Republican presidential frontrunner Donald Trump took to CNBC on Monday to reveal he was unsure whether he would want to get rid of Bitcoin despite criticizing it in the past, going so far as to say he has “fun” with the cryptocurrency.</p>
<p>“There has been a lot of use of that (bitcoin) and I’m not sure that I would want to take it away at this point,” Trump said during his appearance on CNBC&#8217;s Squawk Box.</p>
<h2>Trump is Bullish About Bitcoin</h2>
<p><span class="replacer"></span><br />
“It’s taken [on] its own life,” he continued. “You know, I do little things for fun with it and you know make money with it<b>—</b>and have fun with it, too.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">Trump now sounds bullish on Bitcoin. Personally, I don’t believe him. He and his administration had a shot for supporting Bitcoin. It was hard if not a full stone wall to work with them.</p>
<p>CNBC video recording by: <a href="https://twitter.com/thewallstbulloz?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@thewallstbulloz</a> <a href="https://t.co/SFMPEIcaqC">pic.twitter.com/SFMPEIcaqC</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Gabor Gurbacs (@gaborgurbacs) <a href="https://twitter.com/gaborgurbacs/status/1767157734808392060?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">March 11, 2024</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>The leading GOP candidate’s praise for Bitcoin marks a shift in his <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/trump-calls-cbdc-a-very-dangerous-thing-criticizes-artificial-intelligence.htm">stance towards cryptocurrencies</a> in general, having previously called them “highly volatile” and “based on thin air.”</p>
<p>“Sometimes, we’ll let people pay with Bitcoin,” Trump said about the recently released <a href="https://nymag.com/intelligencer/article/absolutely-everything-we-know-about-the-trump-sneakers.html">American-themed sneaker line</a>. “If you think of it, it&#8217;s an additional form of currency.”</p>
<h2>Trump Doubles Down On USD Stance</h2>
<p><span class="replacer"></span><br />
The former president has previously expressed disdain for cryptocurrencies being used instead of the United States dollar, referring to himself as “not a fan”.</p>
<p>“We have only one real currency in the USA, and it is stronger than ever, both dependable and reliable,” Trump stated in 2019. “It is by far the most dominant currency anywhere in the World, and it will always stay that way.”</p>
<p>During his Monday appearance on Squawk Box, Trump doubled down on his USD-first position, stating replacing USD would be “a hit” to the country.</p>
<p>“I hate when countries go off the dollar,” he continued. “I would not allow countries to go off the dollar because when we lose that standard that will be like losing a revolutionary war.”</p>
<h2>Bitcoin&#8217;s Rally Continues As Price Surges Above $72,000</h2>
<p><span class="replacer"></span><br />
Trump’s comments come amid a feverish rally for Bitcoin, with its <a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/currencies/bitcoin/">price surging above $72,000</a> on Monday morning.</p>
<p>Bitcoin’s latest rally follows the United States Security and Exchange Commission’s (SEC) January 2024 approval of <a href="https://cryptonews.com/guides/a-beginner-s-guide-to-bitcoin-etfs.htm">nine spot bitcoin ETFs</a> in a move that many feel will signal greater mainstream adoption of the cryptocurrency.</p>
<p>As of last week, spot bitcoin ETFs had reached <a href="https://www.theblock.co/post/281339/bitcoin-etf-supply-4-percent">cumulative net inflows of over $9.37 billion</a> since their regulatory debut.</p>
<p>Bloomberg senior ETF analyst Eric Balchunas took to X Monday morning to call the rapid growth of spot bitcoin ETFs “simply absurd.”</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">First two months officially in the books (it&#39;s felt like six) and the ten bitcoin ETFs now have over $55b in assets with exactly double that in volume at $110b. If these were the numbers at the end of year I&#39;d call them a success. To do it in eight weeks is simply absurd. <a href="https://t.co/8YvzQZdYyJ">pic.twitter.com/8YvzQZdYyJ</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Eric Balchunas (@EricBalchunas) <a href="https://twitter.com/EricBalchunas/status/1767156517449400449?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">March 11, 2024</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>Meanwhile, <a href="https://cryptonews.com/cryptocurrency/is-it-too-late-to-buy-bitcoin/">bitcoin&#8217;s price may continue to skyrocket</a> in advance of its quadrennial halving event expected in April 2024.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/trump-flips-stance-on-bitcoin-im-not-sure-if-id-want-to-take-it-away-at-this-point.htm">Trump Flips Stance on Bitcoin: &#8220;I&#8217;m Not Sure If I&#8217;d Want to Take it Away At This Point&#8221;</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptonews.com">Cryptonews</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		<enclosure url="https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/11165041/1710175840-julia_63915_united_states_flage_with_bitcoin_def0b35e-1c80-4fe4-8a63-875bc8aa109b-2.jpg" length="188745" type="image/jpeg" />

			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cathie Wood: ARK Invest Forecasts Bitcoin Price to Surpass $1 Million Sooner than Expected</title>
		<link>https://cryptonews.com/news/cathie-wood-ark-invest-forecasts-bitcoin-price-to-surpass-1-million-sooner-than-expected.htm</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tim Hakki]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 17:34:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ARK Invest]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cathie Wood]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptonews.com/?p=181034</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Crypto friendly American asset manager Ark Invest sees Bitcoin&#8217;s price hitting $1 million before 2030, according to CEO Cathie Wood in a recent interview with the New Zealand Herald. Hard-talking Bitcoin maxi Wood already eyed a projection of $1.5 million earlier this year in an interview with CNBC. At the time, Wood said a &#8220;bear [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/cathie-wood-ark-invest-forecasts-bitcoin-price-to-surpass-1-million-sooner-than-expected.htm">Cathie Wood: ARK Invest Forecasts Bitcoin Price to Surpass $1 Million Sooner than Expected</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptonews.com">Cryptonews</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Crypto friendly American asset manager Ark Invest sees Bitcoin&#8217;s price hitting $1 million before 2030, according to CEO Cathie Wood in a recent <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bDrdpl6epzw">interview</a> with the New Zealand Herald.</p>
<p>Hard-talking Bitcoin maxi Wood already eyed a projection of $1.5 million earlier this year in an interview with CNBC. At the time, Wood said a &#8220;bear case&#8221; would still result in a price rise to around  $258,500.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">Cathie Wood makes her $1.5 million bull case for the price of bitcoin by 2030. <a href="https://t.co/r34iRNA9bG">https://t.co/r34iRNA9bG</a> <a href="https://t.co/chWWDH7ioE">pic.twitter.com/chWWDH7ioE</a></p>
<p>&mdash; CNBC (@CNBC) <a href="https://twitter.com/CNBC/status/1745479111881920808?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">January 11, 2024</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>Wood gave that estimate on January 11, 2024, the day the US Securities and Exchange Commission approved 11 spot Bitcoin exchange-traded funds (ETF) to begin trading.</p>
<p>Wood&#8217;s previous projections had eyed $1 million as a Bitcoin&#8217;s price target and it&#8217;s looking like she has returned to this position.</p>
<p>Still, in her latest interview, Wood implied that $1 million by 2030 might even be a conservative estimate.</p>
<p>“That target — it was before the SEC gave us the green light, and I think that was a major milestone, and it has pulled forward the timeline,” she explained.</p>
<p>She then named Morgan Stanley, Merryl Lynch and Bank of America as financial heavyweights that haven&#8217;t yet started dealing with Bitcoin, implying that it&#8217;s only a matter of time before they join the gravy train: “No platform has approved Bitcoin yet, so all of this price action has happened before they approve it, and so we haven’t even begun,” she said.</p>
<p>“Our target is above that; it’s well above that,&#8221; she teased, declining to give a figure but stating that &#8220;with our new expectations for institutional involvement, the incremental price that we assume for institutions actually has more than doubled.”</p>
<h2>Bitcoin at $1 Million This Year?</h2>
<p><span class="replacer"></span><br />
Considering Cathie Wood helms one of the most crypto-bullish asset managers, and given that Ark Invest already has a spot Bitcoin ETF on exchanges and is <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/spot-ethereum-etf-approval-expected-may-23rd-and-could-surge-in-value-new-report-says.htm">eyeing up</a> a spot Ethereum ETF too, it&#8217;s fair to say she has a pro-crypto bias.</p>
<p>In spite of that, Bitcoin is currently trading at a new all-time high and it looks like there is plenty more mileage left for a potential 2024 bull run.</p>
<p>That&#8217;s because two potentially pivotal price-driving events are coming up. One on April 19, and the other on May 23.</p>
<p>In April is the quadrennial Bitcoin halving. The halving is a pre-determined event in Bitcoin&#8217;s code that cuts miners&#8217; rewards in half leading to a supply squeeze in the issuance of new Bitcoin.</p>
<p>Historically, this has driven rallies.</p>
<p>Then in May, the SEC is expected to give a verdict on VanEck&#8217;s application for a US spot Ethereum ETF. Based on historic precedent with Bitcoin, several analysts, including <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/spot-ethereum-etf-approval-expected-may-23rd-and-could-surge-in-value-new-report-says.htm">Standard Chartered</a>, say that the SEC is likely to approve a round of applications on this date.</p>
<p>The approval of Ethereum ETFs almost looks like a foregone conclusion since Bitcoin ETFs started trading. If the SEC were to reject them, applicants may appeal and win, as Grayscale did with its Bitcoin ETF last year.</p>
<p>Given that Ethereum is crypto&#8217;s most commercially important blockchain, ETFs off the back of Bitcoin&#8217;s halving could drive all leading cryptocurrencies to new heights.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/cathie-wood-ark-invest-forecasts-bitcoin-price-to-surpass-1-million-sooner-than-expected.htm">Cathie Wood: ARK Invest Forecasts Bitcoin Price to Surpass $1 Million Sooner than Expected</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptonews.com">Cryptonews</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		<enclosure url="https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/11163609/1710174968-1710174936464_processed.jpg" length="127859" type="image/jpeg" />

			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Billionaire Michael Saylor Sells $800 Million Convertible Notes to Buy More Bitcoin</title>
		<link>https://cryptonews.com/news/billionaire-michael-saylor-sells-800-million-convertible-notes-to-buy-more-bitcoin.htm</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tim Hakki]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 17:27:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Michael Saylor]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[MicroStrategy]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptonews.com/?p=180822</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>MicroStrategy&#8217;s billionaire executive chairman, founder and former CEO Michael Saylor has just sold $800 million in convertible senior notes to add to his company&#8217;s ~ $13 billion Bitcoin war chest. Saylor made the announcement in a tweet on his X profile. MicroStrategy Completes $800 Million Offering of Convertible Notes at 0.625% Coupon and 42.5% Conversion [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/billionaire-michael-saylor-sells-800-million-convertible-notes-to-buy-more-bitcoin.htm">Billionaire Michael Saylor Sells $800 Million Convertible Notes to Buy More Bitcoin</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptonews.com">Cryptonews</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>MicroStrategy&#8217;s billionaire executive chairman, founder and former CEO Michael Saylor has just sold $800 million in convertible senior notes to add to his company&#8217;s ~ $13 billion Bitcoin war chest.</p>
<p>Saylor made the announcement in a tweet on his X profile.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">MicroStrategy Completes $800 Million Offering of Convertible Notes at 0.625% Coupon and 42.5% Conversion Premium  <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24MSTR&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">$MSTR</a> <a href="https://t.co/c9TEzMqQHq">https://t.co/c9TEzMqQHq</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Michael Saylor<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/26a1.png" alt="⚡" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> (@saylor) <a href="https://twitter.com/saylor/status/1767151492010508566?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">March 11, 2024</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>According to MicroStrategy&#8217;s official <a href="https://www.microstrategy.com/press/microstrategy-completes-800-million-offering-of-0625-convertible-senior-notes-due-2030_03-11-2024">press release</a>, the cloud software company sold the unsecured bonds, which will mature in 2030, to institutional buyers on March 8 this year at a rate of 0.625%.</p>
<p>The sale of the notes generated approximately $782.0 million, after deductions. The company also confirmed that it used the net proceeds &#8220;to obtain additional bitcoins.”</p>
<p class="Paragraph_text-SqIsdNjh0t0- paywall" data-component="paragraph">It also “expects to grant to the initial purchasers of the notes an option to purchase, within a 13-day period beginning on, and including, the date on which the notes are first issued, up to an additional $90 million aggregate principal amount of the notes,” the company said.</p>
<p data-component="paragraph">MicroStrategy shares rallied sharply today. They&#8217;re currently up 13% to $1,550. Since MicroStrategy made buying Bitcoin part of its corporate strategy, many have viewed MicroStrategy shares as a proxy for Bitcoin, since the two tend to rise in tandem.</p>
<p data-component="paragraph">MicroStrategy is easily the largest corporate holder of Bitcoin.</p>
<h2 data-component="paragraph">Bitcoin Trades at an All-Time High</h2>
<p><span class="replacer"></span><br />
Bitcoin maxis are happy <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-27.htm">today</a> as the world&#8217;s favorite cryptocurrency trades at an all-time high of around $72,000. The last time the industry looked this healthy was back in late 2021, when Bitcoin set a former ATH of around $69,000.</p>
<p>The fever pitch around Bitcoin is really concentrated on two overarching narratives that are really helping to drive prices: ETFs and the halving.</p>
<p>See Bitcoin is popular, but it&#8217;s also very volatile and unregulated. Naturally, for investors in more traditional financial products, it can seem like a risky prospect.</p>
<p>Enter exchange-traded funds (ETFs). An ETF is essentially a Bitcoin fund, meaning it&#8217;s an entity that directly buys and stores Bitcoin and uses the asset to create shares, which it then sells on exchanges.</p>
<p>These shares track the price of the underlying asset, but thanks to their regulated status, they have more guardrails to help build confidence in crypto among investors from traditional finance backgrounds.</p>
<p>Many crypto advocates had been pining for a Bitcoin ETF for the last decade. The oldest and most senior Bitcoin Trust, Grayscale, started with an eye to eventually converting to an ETF but the SEC knocked it back last year.</p>
<p>Grayscale took the SEC&#8217;s rejection to an appeals court, where a judge ruled in Grayscale&#8217;s favor, calling the rejection &#8220;arbitrary and capricious&#8221;.</p>
<p>The move forced the SEC to approve eleven spot Bitcoin ETF applications earlier this year. They&#8217;ve already been some of the most hyped and successful ETF launches in history.</p>
<h2>And the Halving&#8230;</h2>
<p><span class="replacer"></span><br />
Finally, the market is also looking towards Bitcoin&#8217;s upcoming halving on April 19 to potentially drive prices beyond $100,000.</p>
<p>On that date, Bitcoin mining block rewards get cut in half, thus &#8220;halving&#8221; the issuance of new Bitcoin. If the current demand for Bitcoin sustains itself till then, the laws of supply and demand could catalyze some very roomy price rises.</p>
<p>It looks like billionaire Saylor believes there&#8217;s a lot more rally left.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/billionaire-michael-saylor-sells-800-million-convertible-notes-to-buy-more-bitcoin.htm">Billionaire Michael Saylor Sells $800 Million Convertible Notes to Buy More Bitcoin</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptonews.com">Cryptonews</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		<enclosure url="https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/11173312/1710178391-1710178356761_processed.jpg" length="230179" type="image/jpeg" />

			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Here’s The Latest NFT News Today</title>
		<link>https://cryptonews.com/news/nft-news-today.htm</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Sead Fadilpašić]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 16:20:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[NFT News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[NFT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptonews.com/?p=170308</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Here's the latest form NFT news today, March 11, 2024:</p>
<ul>
<li><span style="font-weight: 400;">NFT Market Data</span></li>
<li><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Mastercard Artist Accelerator Kicks off Its Second Season With NFT Passes</span></li>
<li><span style="font-weight: 400;">DC Digital Collection Revealed for Batman’s 85</span><span style="font-weight: 400;">th</span><span style="font-weight: 400;"> Birthday</span></li>
<li><span style="font-weight: 400;">Sony Eyes ‘Super-Fungible Tokens’ for Gaming</span></li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/nft-news-today.htm">Here’s The Latest NFT News Today</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptonews.com">Cryptonews</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><em>Get your daily, bite-sized digest of NFT news today – investigating the stories flying under the radar among the latest NFT news.</em></p>
<div class="su-note"  style="border-color:#e0d5e5;border-radius:3px;-moz-border-radius:3px;-webkit-border-radius:3px;"><div class="su-note-inner su-u-clearfix su-u-trim" style="background-color:#FAEFFF;border-color:#ffffff;color:#333333;border-radius:3px;-moz-border-radius:3px;-webkit-border-radius:3px;">
<p>Here&#8217;s the latest form NFT news today, March 11, 2024:</p>
<ul>
<li>NFT Market Data</li>
<li>The Mastercard Artist Accelerator Kicks off Its Second Season With NFT Passes</li>
<li>DC Digital Collection Revealed for Batman’s 85th Birthday</li>
<li>Sony Eyes ‘Super-Fungible Tokens’ for Gaming</li>
</ul>
</div></div>
<h2><b>NFT Market Data</b></h2>
<p><span class="replacer"></span><br />
Over the past 24 hours, the non-fungible token (<a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/jeju-island-south-korea-eyes-nft-powered-growth.htm">NFT</a>) sales volume has dropped nearly 10% to $45,774,268.</p>
<p><a href="https://www.cryptoslam.io/">According</a> to <b>CryptoSlam</b>, buyers are down 10%, sellers 3%, and the number of transactions almost 6%. Among the top 10 collections per sales volume, four have seen an increase and six a decrease.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-ordinals-will-play-a-pivotal-role-in-2024-more-top-nft-news-2.htm"><b>Uncategorized Ordinals</b></a> is in the first place. It’s up 11% to $3.38 million.</p>
<p>However, the best daily performer is <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/cryptopunks-reveals-details-for-its-punk-in-residence-incubator-program-more-nft-news.htm"><b>CryptoPunks</b></a>. This collection went up 268% in 24 hours to $1.5 million, far more than the other green collections.</p>
<p>As for the red projects, the sales volume of <a href="https://opensea.io/collection/peplicator-by-matt-furie"><b>Peplicator</b></a> dropped the most: 63% to $2.98 million.</p>
<figure id="attachment_181043" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-181043" style="width: 1325px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="wp-image-181043 size-full" src="https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/11161938/1710173977-opensea.jpg" alt="" width="1325" height="608" srcset="https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/11161938/1710173977-opensea.jpg 1325w, https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/11161938/1710173977-opensea-300x138.jpg 300w, https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/11161938/1710173977-opensea-1024x470.jpg 1024w, https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/11161938/1710173977-opensea-768x352.jpg 768w, https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/11161938/1710173977-opensea-150x69.jpg 150w" sizes="(max-width: 1325px) 100vw, 1325px" /><figcaption id="caption-attachment-181043" class="wp-caption-text">Peplicator, price low to high. Source: OpenSea</figcaption></figure>
<p>Given that we’ve just started a new week, let’s check out the 7-day situation as well.</p>
<p>And we find that it’s red as well. The sales volume fell 12% in this period to $390,447,550.</p>
<p>At the same time, buyers dropped a whopping 79%. The number of sellers decreased by 77% and transactions by 22%.</p>
<p>Uncategorized Ordinals are again in first place with $30.75 million despite a 32% fall.</p>
<p>Five coins are green in this time frame. Among them, the second-placed CryptoPunks is the best-performing collection in a week. It went up 177% to $26.8 million.</p>
<p>The biggest drop is <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/pandoras-erc-404-token-surges-with-190m-trading-volume-within-a-week-of-launch-nansen.htm"><b>Pandora’s</b></a>: 50% to $9.8 million.</p>
<h2><b>The Mastercard Artist Accelerator Kicks off Its Second Season With NFT Passes</b></h2>
<p><span class="replacer"></span><br />
<b>In the latest NFT news today, </b><a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/mastercard-explores-web3-alliances-metamask-ledger-included.htm"><b>Mastercard</b></a> has revealed the second season of its Artist Accelerator program in partnership with <b>OnesToWatch</b>, a global music discovery platform for emerging artists of all genres.</p>
<p><a href="https://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240307110150/en/The-Mastercard-Artist-Accelerator-Kicks-off-Its-Second-Season-Launches-Live-Touring-Series-With-OnesToWatch">According</a> to the press release, “this year&#8217;s Accelerator is tailored to meet the surging demand for live music seen in 2023.”</p>
<p>The program will start in April when Mastercard and OnesToWatch will launch a live touring series.</p>
<p>The series will give artists various opportunities, including live performances, mentorship from industry experts, and educational bootcamps on technologies like Web3 and Generative AI.</p>
<p>Furthermore, the participants will be able to improve their skills in merchandising, marketing and promoting themselves in digital and physical spaces, and mastering emerging technologies to create, collaborate, and monetize their work.</p>
<p>The first participant in the second season is Asha Imuno, a 22-year-old artist, producer, and songwriter from California, USA. His is a “unique sound that blends nostalgic influences from classic Hip-Hop and R&amp;B with a refreshing take on new age Soul and Funk.”</p>
<p>Fans can collect the second season limited-edition Mastercard Music Pass NFT, which will drop in the coming weeks.</p>
<p>The pass provides access to exclusive content and experiences throughout the year, including concerts for select pass holders, behind-the-scenes content, and a chance to engage with Mastercard’s Pass to Priceless platform.</p>
<p><a href="https://connect.priceless.com/artistaccelerator">Per</a> the FAQ, it will also unlock educational materials, artist content, and tickets to the OnesToWatch and Mastercard concert tours.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, when users create a Mastercard Artist Accelerator account, their digital collectibles are stored in a third-party-owned blockchain custodial wallet.</p>
<p>“The Mastercard Artist Accelerator combines the power of blockchain with the timeless passion for music and a first-of-its-kind curriculum for both artists and fans,” the season 1 press release <a href="https://www.mastercard.com/news/latin-america/en/newsroom/press-releases/pr-en/2023/april/mastercard-drops-nft-that-unlocks-access-to-its-artist-accelerator-supporting-emerging-musicians/">said</a>.</p>
<p><iframe loading="lazy" title="Introducing Mastercard Artist Accelerator Season Two" width="640" height="360" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/MHDMeJ6Oz4s?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" allowfullscreen></iframe></p>
<h2><b>DC Digital Collection Revealed for Batman’s 85th Birthday</b></h2>
<p><span class="replacer"></span><br />
<b>DC Comics Bat Cowls</b> revealed a new DC digital collectible experience to celebrate <b>Batman’s</b> 85th anniversary.</p>
<p><a href="https://medium.com/@DCNFTS/the-legacy-cowls-collection-launches-march-29-2024-29f494d9318a">Per</a> the press release, <b>The Legacy Cowl</b> will be released on Friday, March 29.</p>
<p>This new DC digital collectible “commemorates a milestone in comic book history: the introduction of a new DC Super-Villain,” it added.</p>
<p>The Legacy Cowls Collection features 11,544 3D collectibles, an edition size that mirrors the number of Bat Cowls minted.</p>
<p>Moreover, the complete collection will be released in a series of four separate sales throughout 2024. While the first one is set for March 29, the dates for the other three sales are yet to be announced.</p>
<p>By collecting a Legacy Cowl, holders can unlock experiences that include AR lens, voting opportunities, secrets and puzzles, future access to selected experiences and drops, limited-edition crafting, exclusive crafting opportunities, and physical object opportunities.</p>
<figure id="attachment_181047" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-181047" style="width: 1271px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="wp-image-181047 size-full" src="https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/11162746/1710174466-dcnfts.png" alt="" width="1271" height="716" srcset="https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/11162746/1710174466-dcnfts.png 1271w, https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/11162746/1710174466-dcnfts-300x169.png 300w, https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/11162746/1710174466-dcnfts-1024x577.png 1024w, https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/11162746/1710174466-dcnfts-768x433.png 768w, https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/11162746/1710174466-dcnfts-150x85.png 150w" sizes="(max-width: 1271px) 100vw, 1271px" /><figcaption id="caption-attachment-181047" class="wp-caption-text">Source: medium.com/@DCNFTS</figcaption></figure>
<p>Meanwhile, <b>Batman: The Legacy Cowl</b> is the first original DC comic on the blockchain shaped through community voting, said the announcement.</p>
<p>Moreover, DC Bat Cowl Collection holders voted since June 2022 to create and shape the direction of the series in collaboration with DC artists and writers.</p>
<p>The holders contributed to decisions like titles, dialogues, and character development.</p>
<p>The series comprises 57 votes and 3 chapters, culminating “with the origination of a new DC Super-Villain: The Legacy Cowl.”</p>
<p>Furthermore, the participants of The Legacy Cowls Collection experience will also have the opportunity to shape the next chapter.</p>
<h1><b>Sony Eyes ‘Super-Fungible Tokens’ for Gaming</b></h1>
<p>Japanese conglomerate Sony has recently submitted a patent application discussing super-fungible tokens for gaming.</p>
<p>The application <a href="https://ppubs.uspto.gov/dirsearch-public/print/downloadPdf/20240066408">includes</a> an electronic device and a method for the implementation of these tokens.</p>
<p>The device, it said, tracks a set of gaming assets associated with a player in a gaming application. Examples of assets include an avatar, tools, or a weapon.</p>
<p>Gaming applications could be sports, fighting, athletics, etc.</p>
<p>The device would receive the metadata and create a super-fungible token corresponding to one gaming asset.</p>
<p>The super-fungible token contains a set of non-fungible tokens, wherein each NFT is associated with a corresponding in-game asset.</p>
<p>The super-fungible token itself would be recorded on a distributed ledger connected to that specific gaming app.</p>
<p>For example, said the document, that distributed ledger “may be an <b>Ethereum</b> blockchain which may use accounts as state objects and a state of each account can be tracked by the Ethereum blockchain. […] The distributed ledger may correspond to a <b>Hyperledger</b> blockchain, or a <b>Corda</b> blockchain.”</p>
<figure id="attachment_181046" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-181046" style="width: 1159px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="wp-image-181046 size-full" src="https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/11162402/1710174242-sony.png" alt="" width="1159" height="825" srcset="https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/11162402/1710174242-sony.png 1159w, https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/11162402/1710174242-sony-300x214.png 300w, https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/11162402/1710174242-sony-1024x729.png 1024w, https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/11162402/1710174242-sony-768x547.png 768w, https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/11162402/1710174242-sony-150x107.png 150w" sizes="(max-width: 1159px) 100vw, 1159px" /><figcaption id="caption-attachment-181046" class="wp-caption-text">Source: Sony</figcaption></figure>
<p>The invention would be transformative for the gaming industry, it argues, as it may potentially allow inter-game transfers.</p>
<p>The proposed system would track these gaming assets as they move between game titles.</p>
<p>Moreover, when one NFT is selected, that becomes the active gaming asset, and the others are disabled.</p>
<p>This would theoretically give more control to players over their own assets.</p>
<p>The patent application was filed in August 2022 and published on February 29, 2024.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/nft-news-today.htm">Here’s The Latest NFT News Today</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptonews.com">Cryptonews</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		<enclosure url="https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/02/21134226/1708522945-1708522402870_processed.jpg" length="109619" type="image/jpeg" />

			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Exclusive: Web3 Development-Focused Core Foundation Launches New NFT Marketplace</title>
		<link>https://cryptonews.com/news/exclusive-web3-development-focused-core-foundation-launches-new-nft-marketplace.htm</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Sujha Sundararajan]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 16:19:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exclusives]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Core Foundation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[NFT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[NFT Marketplace]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptonews.com/?p=181028</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Core Foundation will embark an NFT collection drop for the community, dubbed – Core Journey.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/exclusive-web3-development-focused-core-foundation-launches-new-nft-marketplace.htm">Exclusive: Web3 Development-Focused Core Foundation Launches New NFT Marketplace</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptonews.com">Cryptonews</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Core Foundation, which aims to create a secure and decentralized ecosystem for dApps, is launching a <a href="https://cryptonews.com/guides/nft/">non-fungible token</a> (NFT) marketplace.</p>
<p>Announced Monday, the foundation will also embark an NFT collection drop for the community, dubbed – Core Journey. The NFT collection is focused to bring stronger utility to the Core chain, said Core contributor Rich Rines.</p>
<p>Core blockchain leverages the advantages of Bitcoin and the network is also EVM (Ethereum Virtual Machine) compatible so that it can run <a href="https://cryptonews.com/guides/ethereum/">Ethereum</a> smart contracts and dApps.</p>
<p>The announcement comes days after the foundation launched a <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/this-new-5m-fund-aims-to-scale-bitcoin-aligned-projects-in-india-heres-the-latest.htm">$5 million innovation fund</a> to promote India’s Web3 communities. The project also launched a <a href="https://www.coindesk.com/video/core-dao-contributor-explains-why-africa-is-ripe-for-web3-disruption/">$5 million</a> Africa Ecosystem Fund last month to provide resources to help local Web3 builders.</p>
<h2>Core Foundation&#8217;s NFT Marketplace – Wizard Gallery</h2>
<p><span class="replacer"></span><br />
Core’s NFT marketplace – <a href="https://www.wizardgallery.xyz/">Wizard Gallery</a> – aims to provide users with seamless NFT minting and trading, operating on Core Chain. According to the website, the marketplace boasts hosting more than 20,000 NFTs created by over 50 artists.</p>
<p>The Core Journey NFT collection is live on the new marketplace, the release shared by the company to Cryptonews, read. As Bitcoin finance (BTCfi) is booming, “the Core community has crafted a captivating campaign to celebrate its journey with this amazing collection.”</p>
<p>On a further note, Core is also rolling out an incentive program to reward builders. The program, Core Ignition, would recognize developers for their contribution to the network’s growth.</p>
<p>Core Ignition enables users to have opportunities to engage and earn rewards alongside fostering the growth and adoption of Core.</p>
<p>&#8220;The Core network has seen immense growth since its mainnet launch in 2023,” Rines noted.</p>
<p>“It is becoming the most Bitcoin-aligned EVM chain and the go-to chain to build BTCfi and scale Bitcoin with a massive community, which has translated into millions of Core adopters, over 15M unique addresses, and 230M transactions.”</p>
<p>Recently, Core released a paper on ‘Unlocking Bitcoin DeFi,’ and launched the Core Starter Program, backed by over $300,000 in incentives.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/exclusive-web3-development-focused-core-foundation-launches-new-nft-marketplace.htm">Exclusive: Web3 Development-Focused Core Foundation Launches New NFT Marketplace</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptonews.com">Cryptonews</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		<enclosure url="https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/11160651/1710173210-1710173172085_processed.jpg" length="206037" type="image/jpeg" />

			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ethereum Price Prediction as ETH Crosses $4,000 Level – New All-Time High Coming?</title>
		<link>https://cryptonews.com/news/ethereum-price-prediction-as-eth-crosses-4000-level-new-all-time-high-coming.htm</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tim Hakki]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 16:02:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Price Predictions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum ETF]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sponge]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptonews.com/?p=180685</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Ethereum (ETH) is back trading comfortably above $4,000, a level last seen in late 2021. The cryptocurrency underpinning the most commercially important blockchain rallied 14.3% over the last 7 days, outpacing market leader Bitcoin (BTC), which rallied 9.7% this week. Ethereum&#8217;s market cap now hovers at close to half a trillion, although it will need [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/ethereum-price-prediction-as-eth-crosses-4000-level-new-all-time-high-coming.htm">Ethereum Price Prediction as ETH Crosses $4,000 Level – New All-Time High Coming?</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptonews.com">Cryptonews</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Ethereum (ETH) is back trading comfortably above $4,000, a level last seen in late 2021.</p>
<p>The cryptocurrency underpinning the most commercially important blockchain rallied 14.3% over the last 7 days, outpacing market leader Bitcoin (BTC), which rallied 9.7% this week.</p>
<p>Ethereum&#8217;s market cap now hovers at close to half a trillion, although it will need to effectively triple that to catch up with Bitcoin.</p>
<p>Despite Ethereum&#8217;s stronger rally, today is really Bitcoin&#8217;s day, as the world&#8217;s oldest and most popular cryptocurrency is currently changing hands at an all-time high (ATH) of almost $72,000.</p>
<p>While Ethereum&#8217;s smart contracts quickly expanded the horizon of what blockchain was capable of and helped to usher in an alternative financial system, it&#8217;s really Bitcoin that bootstraps the entire market.</p>
<h2>Crypto in the Coming Months</h2>
<p><span class="replacer"></span><br />
There is a lot to look forward to in the near term from both of the market leaders.</p>
<p>Bitcoin is trading at a new ATH off the back of new institutional interest since the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) approved the launch of 11 spot Bitcoin ETFs.</p>
<p>The ETFs have together attracted nearly $10 billion in inflows since they began trading on January 11.</p>
<p>Bitcoiners are also pointing at the quadrennial halving on April 19 as another price driver. The halving is when miners&#8217; block rewards get halved, causing a supply squeeze in the issuance of new Bitcoin.</p>
<p>Historically, halvings have tended to drive the price higher, and this halving looks no different, with institutional demand for Bitcoin currently at an all-time high.</p>
<p>Ethereum fans are also pointing at a potential milestone on May 23. This is the SEC&#8217;s first deadline to return a verdict on the latest round of applications for a spot Ethereum ETF. If Ethereum ETFs are approved, then institutional demand for Ethereum in the US could drive prices to new highs.</p>
<p>Over on the price chart we can see that Ethereum has charted a clear path upwards since the start of February, although with a current Relative Strength Index (RSI) almost at 70, there is heavy buying pressure.</p>
<figure id="attachment_180784" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-180784" style="width: 1006px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-180784" src="https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/11113909/1710157149-ethusd_2024-03-11_11-38-49.png" alt="" width="1006" height="643" srcset="https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/11113909/1710157149-ethusd_2024-03-11_11-38-49.png 1006w, https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/11113909/1710157149-ethusd_2024-03-11_11-38-49-300x192.png 300w, https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/11113909/1710157149-ethusd_2024-03-11_11-38-49-768x491.png 768w, https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/11113909/1710157149-ethusd_2024-03-11_11-38-49-150x96.png 150w" sizes="(max-width: 1006px) 100vw, 1006px" /><figcaption id="caption-attachment-180784" class="wp-caption-text">Source: TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<h2>Ethereum is Great But SPONGE Is Funnier</h2>
<p><span class="replacer"></span><br />
Ethereum and Bitcoin may be where the safe money is at, but a small group of coins posted blistering triple-digit percentage seven-day gains recently: meme coins.</p>
<p>Viral marketing campaigns and the novelty factor typically drive meme coin prices, although two of the largest are now serious projects in the industry: Dogecoin (DOGE), which has a first-mover advantage and originality on its side, and Shiba Inu (SHIB) on Solana is branching out as a network and offering more utility,</p>
<p>One meme token that combines freshness with utility and offers more than laughs is SPONGE. it’s the native token for an exciting new ecosystem.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">GM <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/SPONGERS?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#SPONGERS</a>! <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f9fd.png" alt="🧽" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /><img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f9fd.png" alt="🧽" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /><img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f9fd.png" alt="🧽" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /></p>
<p>Did someone say moon? <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f680.png" alt="🚀" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /></p>
<p>Trade <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24SPONGE&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">$SPONGE</a> on <a href="https://twitter.com/dexscreener?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@dexscreener</a> <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f447.png" alt="👇" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /><a href="https://t.co/mRRzvNqdpm">https://t.co/mRRzvNqdpm</a><a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/MemeCoin?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#MemeCoin</a> <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Crypto?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#Crypto</a> <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Altcoins?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#Altcoins</a> <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Bullish?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#Bullish</a> <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/100x?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#100x</a> <a href="https://t.co/iVOCDTYMVz">pic.twitter.com/iVOCDTYMVz</a></p>
<p>&mdash; $SPONGE (@spongeoneth) <a href="https://twitter.com/spongeoneth/status/1766030733892862080?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">March 8, 2024</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>According to CoinGecko data, SPONGE is up nearly 100% in the last week and 143% in the last fortnight as it trades for $0.003209 at the time of writing.</p>
<p>SPONGE is an ERC-2o standard token on Ethereum. It <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/sponge-v2-launch-on-polygon-sees-56-pump-as-buyers-stake-for-7500-returns.htm">recently upgraded</a> (and migrated) to a V2 on Polygon, an Ethereum Layer 2 scaling solution.</p>
<p>The team also introduced a couple of key improvements with the upgrade, including a new staking model that offers a minimum yield of 40% APY.</p>
<p>This yield currently sits at around <a href="https://spongetoken.vip/en/staking">490%</a>, varying according to the number of stakes and tokens locked up.</p>
<p>SPONGE also powers an upcoming racing game where players compete against each other to earn SPONGE rewards.</p>
<p><strong><a href="https://cryptonews.com/ext/sponge" rel="sponsored nofollow">Buy And Stake SPONGE On The Website</a></strong></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/ethereum-price-prediction-as-eth-crosses-4000-level-new-all-time-high-coming.htm">Ethereum Price Prediction as ETH Crosses $4,000 Level – New All-Time High Coming?</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptonews.com">Cryptonews</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		<enclosure url="https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/02/26120854/1708949333-adobestock_508113570_editorial_use_only.jpeg" length="231094" type="image/jpeg" />

			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Unizen Pledges Reimbursements After $2.1M Loss in Platform Breach</title>
		<link>https://cryptonews.com/news/unizen-security-breach-results-1m-loss-vows-reimbursments.htm</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hassan Shittu]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 15:03:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DeFi]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Security Breach]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Unizen]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptonews.com/?p=180880</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Unizen has taken swift action in response to a recent security breach that resulted in the loss of approximately $2.1 million in user funds.</span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/unizen-security-breach-results-1m-loss-vows-reimbursments.htm">Unizen Pledges Reimbursements After $2.1M Loss in Platform Breach</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptonews.com">Cryptonews</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Decentralized finance (DeFi) protocol Unizen has taken swift action in response to a recent security breach that resulted in the loss of approximately $2.1 million in user funds. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Following the compromise, <a href="https://x.com/unizen_io/status/1767075963475505522?s=20">Unizen pledged to reimburse</a> affected users who lost up to $750,000, aiming to restore confidence in its platform and uphold its commitment to user protection.</span></p>
<h2><strong><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Defi Platform Unizen Faces $2.1 Million Loss in Unauthorized Access Security Breach</span></strong></h2>
<p><span class="replacer"></span></p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">Dear unizen community,</p>
<p>After an arduous weekend, we have made the strategic decision to make over 99% of those affected from our community completely whole with immediate effect. </p>
<p>Our CEO / Founder, Sean Noga, has decided to loan Unizen the majority of the immediate… <a href="https://t.co/d9GyaH3j8Y">pic.twitter.com/d9GyaH3j8Y</a></p>
<p>&mdash; unizen (@unizen_io) <a href="https://twitter.com/unizen_io/status/1767075963475505522?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">March 11, 2024</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">On March 9, the blockchain analytics firm PeckShield </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://x.com/peckshield/status/1766210445415727608?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">identified</span></a> <span data-preserver-spaces="true">an &#8220;approve issue&#8221; within the DeFi platform, signaling unauthorized access and the drainage of over $2 million in funds. Promptly, security advisories were issued, urging users to revoke approvals to mitigate further losses. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Another blockchain security firm, SlowMist, investigated and confirmed that the total losses amounted to around $2.1 million, attributing them to an open external call vulnerability. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The hacker exploited an external call vulnerability within the Ethereum-based contract, converting the stolen USDT to DAI. The funds remain stationary, with users urged to revoke any approvals associated with the hacker’s address to prevent additional losses. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">In response to the breach, <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/unizen-review-a-cedefi-smart-exchange-ecosystem-11471.htm">Unizen</a> acknowledged the incident and assured users that the team was working diligently to enhance platform security and prevent future breaches. The company has established a dedicated form to address concerns from affected users and cautioned against communicating with unofficial Unizen accounts on social media platforms.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">On March 10, Unizen initiated cooperation with law enforcement and forensic experts to identify the perpetrator. Unizen proactively </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://etherscan.io/tx/0x351906b2406282042c7396ea960b7a52d305658097e3f25bae79be4cdbb7c311" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">reached out</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> to the hacker with on-chain messages urging the return of the stolen funds, accompanied by a demonstration of ownership through a transfer from the foundation wallet to the hacker&#8217;s Ethereum wallet.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Unizen emphasized its ongoing collaboration with law enforcement and requested the prompt return of funds to avoid further legal action. As an incentive for cooperation, the company offered a 20% bounty as a token of appreciation for white-hat efforts.</span></p>
<h2><strong><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Unizen’s Reimbursement Plan Following an Unauthorized Access Breach</span></strong></h2>
<p><span class="replacer"></span><br />
<span data-preserver-spaces="true">While bounty discussions continued, Unizen took proactive steps to alleviate the impact on affected users. On March 11, the company announced its intention to reimburse 99% of victims immediately, prioritizing a meticulous, individualized approach to the reimbursement process.</span></p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">Dear unizen community,</p>
<p>After an arduous weekend, we have made the strategic decision to make over 99% of those affected from our community completely whole with immediate effect. </p>
<p>Our CEO / Founder, Sean Noga, has decided to loan Unizen the majority of the immediate… <a href="https://t.co/d9GyaH3j8Y">pic.twitter.com/d9GyaH3j8Y</a></p>
<p>&mdash; unizen (@unizen_io) <a href="https://twitter.com/unizen_io/status/1767075963475505522?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">March 11, 2024</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Sean Noga, the founder and CEO of Unizen, </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://x.com/unizen_io/status/1767075963475505522?s=20" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">extended</span></a> <span data-preserver-spaces="true">personal loans to facilitate the refunds, which commenced on the same day for users who lost less than $750,000.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Beginning on March 11, refunds will be distributed to users who lost amounts below $750,000, facilitated in either USDT or USD Coin (USDC). For users affected by losses exceeding $750,000, Unizen assures a personalized resolution process.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Alongside the reimbursement initiative, the company released a comprehensive video guide to educate users on reviewing and revoking approvals within the platform, minimizing susceptibility to future vulnerabilities.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Unizen&#8217;s chief technology officer, Martin Granström, </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://twitter.com/MartinGranstrom/status/1766898480386101440" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">disclosed</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> on X that Unizen has gathered sufficient evidence for a comprehensive post-mortem report and engaged third-party firms for assistance. Granström assured users that an incident report would be released shortly and also affirmed the company&#8217;s dedication to bolstering security measures, pledging increased investment in safeguarding user assets for the future.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The Unizen exploit joins a string of crypto-related exploits in February, including the recent WOOFi breach, which resulted in losses of approximately $8.75 million. As Unizen prepares to release its post-mortem report, the platform&#8217;s engineering team remains focused on restoring normal operations while bolstering security measures to safeguard user assets.</span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/unizen-security-breach-results-1m-loss-vows-reimbursments.htm">Unizen Pledges Reimbursements After $2.1M Loss in Platform Breach</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptonews.com">Cryptonews</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		<enclosure url="https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/11133738/1710164257-1710164234112_processed.jpg" length="87992" type="image/jpeg" />

			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Best Crypto to Buy Today March 11 – FLOKI, Theta Network, Near Protocol</title>
		<link>https://cryptonews.com/news/best-crypto-to-buy-today-march-11-floki-theta-network-near-protocol.htm</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Joel Frank]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 15:01:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Altcoin News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Best Crypto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptonews.com/?p=180989</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>As Bitcoin (BTC) pushes into the $72,000s for the first time ever and Ether (ETH) rallies to the north of $4,000, crypto investors are assessing which might be the best crypto to buy today.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/best-crypto-to-buy-today-march-11-floki-theta-network-near-protocol.htm">Best Crypto to Buy Today March 11 – FLOKI, Theta Network, Near Protocol</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptonews.com">Cryptonews</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<figure id="attachment_158245" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-158245" style="width: 1280px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-158245" src="https://cryptonews.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/01/1706559006-imgpsh_fullsize_anim__1_.jpeg" alt="Best Crypto to Buy Today" width="1280" height="720" srcset="https://cryptonews.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/01/1706559006-imgpsh_fullsize_anim__1_.jpeg 1280w, https://cryptonews.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/01/1706559006-imgpsh_fullsize_anim__1_-300x169.jpeg 300w, https://cryptonews.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/01/1706559006-imgpsh_fullsize_anim__1_-1024x576.jpeg 1024w, https://cryptonews.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/01/1706559006-imgpsh_fullsize_anim__1_-768x432.jpeg 768w, https://cryptonews.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/01/1706559006-imgpsh_fullsize_anim__1_-150x84.jpeg 150w" sizes="(max-width: 1280px) 100vw, 1280px" /><figcaption id="caption-attachment-158245" class="wp-caption-text">Cryptocurrencies like FLOKI, THETA, NEAR compete for best crypto to buy today <em> Image by cryptonews.com </em></figcaption></figure>
<p>As Bitcoin (BTC) pushes into the $72,000s for the first time ever and Ether (ETH) rallies to the north of $4,000, crypto investors are assessing which might be the best crypto to buy today.</p>
<p>Strong <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/blackrocks-global-allocation-fund-to-invest-in-spot-bitcoin-etfs.htm">spot Bitcoin ETF</a> demand ahead the supply shock of the <a href="https://cryptonews.com/tags/bitcoin-halving/">Bitcoin halving</a> has propelled Bitcoin higher in recent weeks.</p>
<p>This has bled across to other sectors of the crypto market, with major <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/best-meme-coins.htm">meme coins</a> outperforming notably in recent weeks.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptonews.com/coins/bitcoin/">Bitcoin</a> looks to be on course to hit $100,000 in the coming weeks and months.</p>
<p>Some are even betting it could reach six digits before the April halving.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/ethereum-news/">Ether</a>, meanwhile, looks to be on course to soon clinch new record highs.</p>
<p>With the outlook for both cryptocurrencies looking very strong, both BTC and ETH are integral to any crypto investor’s portfolio.</p>
<p>But with BTC and ETH’s potential gains in the 2-3x range, highly risk-tolerant crypto investors often crave greater upside exposure.</p>
<p>That’s why they often turn to <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/altcoin-news/">altcoin</a> markets to hunt for lesser-known but high-potential cryptos.</p>
<p>Here are some of Monday’s best-performing altcoins, each of which could be the best crypto to buy today.</p>
<h2><strong>Best Crypto to Buy Today</strong></h2>
<p><span class="replacer"></span></p>
<h3><strong>Theta Network (THETA)</strong></h3>
<p>Novel “dual network” <a href="https://cryptonews.com/coins/theta/">Theta Network</a> is one of the best-performing cryptos on Monday, <a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/currencies/theta-network/">up 25% in 24 hours</a>.</p>
<p>THETA’s price pumped to as high as $ 3.80 earlier, its highest since April 2022.</p>
<p>It has since retraced to around $3.65 per token.</p>
<p>But since pushing above $2.30 resistance, there is a clear path to resistance at $4.50.</p>
<p>Theta Network combines a <a href="https://cryptonews.com/guides/what-is-a-smart-contract.htm">smart-contract</a>-enabled layer-1 blockchain with a data and storage network.</p>
<p>With a market cap of only around $3.6 billion, THETA has plenty of upside left for this bull market.</p>
<p>That’s why THETA could be the best crypto to buy today.</p>
<h3><strong>Floki (FLOKI)</strong></h3>
<p>FLOKI (FLOKI), the Shiba Inu meme coin that was created in honor of Elon Musk’s pet Shiba Inu dog, is a leading coin on Monday.</p>
<p>As per <a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/currencies/floki-inu/">CoinMarketCap</a>, it was last up 21% in 24 hours, with its market cap surpassing $2.5 billion.</p>
<p>But with Dogecoin and Shiba Inu both valued above $20 billion, it could have a long way higher to run.</p>
<p>That’s why, despite having already pumped a long way, it could be the best crypto to buy today.</p>
<h3><strong>NEAR Protocol (NEAR)</strong></h3>
<p>Layer-1 protocol NEAR Protocol (NEAR) is up around 20% in the past 24 hours, as per <a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/currencies/near-protocol/">CoinMarketCap</a>.</p>
<p>Last just above $7.0, NEAR recently hit its highest-ever levels.</p>
<p>Amid a lack of notable upside resistance levels, the sky is now the limit for NEAR.</p>
<p>With a market cap of currently only slightly above $7 billion, if it continues to garner widespread adoption, NEAR Protocol has the potential to still rally 5-10x from here.</p>
<p>That’s why NEAR could be best crypto to buy today.</p>
<h2><strong>Crypto Alternatives to Consider</strong></h2>
<p><span class="replacer"></span><br />
All of the above coins offer potential investors a great chance to make 10x gains.</p>
<p>But, for those looking for a better probability of near-term gains, an alternative high-risk, high-reward investment strategy to consider is getting involved in <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/new-cryptocurrency.htm">crypto presales</a>.</p>
<p>This is where investors buy the tokens of upstart crypto projects to help fund their development.</p>
<p>These tokens are nearly always sold cheaply, and there is a long history of presales delivering huge exponential gains to early investors.</p>
<p>Many of these projects have fantastic teams behind them and a great vision to deliver a revolutionary crypto application/platform.</p>
<p>If an investor can identify such projects, the risk/reward of their presale investment is very good.</p>
<p>The team at Cryptonews spends a lot of time combing through presale projects to help investors out.</p>
<p>Here is a list of 14 of what the project deems as the best crypto presales of 2023.</p>
<p><strong><a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/new-cryptocurrency.htm">See the 14 Cryptocurrencies</a></strong></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/best-crypto-to-buy-today-march-11-floki-theta-network-near-protocol.htm">Best Crypto to Buy Today March 11 – FLOKI, Theta Network, Near Protocol</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptonews.com">Cryptonews</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		<enclosure url="https://cryptonews.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/01/1706559006-imgpsh_fullsize_anim__1_.jpeg" length="74293" type="image/jpeg" />

			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Mudrex to Offer US Spot Bitcoin ETFs to Indian Investors</title>
		<link>https://cryptonews.com/news/mudrex-to-offer-us-spot-bitcoin-etfs-to-indian-investors.htm</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Hassan Shittu]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 14:53:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blockchain News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[India]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[RBI]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[spot Bitcoin ETF]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptonews.com/?p=180839</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Mudrex, an Indian cryptocurrency investment platform, has announced plans to offer US spot BTC ETFs to institutional and retail investors in India.</span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/mudrex-to-offer-us-spot-bitcoin-etfs-to-indian-investors.htm">Mudrex to Offer US Spot Bitcoin ETFs to Indian Investors</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptonews.com">Cryptonews</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Mudrex, an Indian cryptocurrency investment platform, has announced plans to offer US spot Bitcoin (BTC) exchange-traded funds (ETFs) to institutional and retail investors in India, <a href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2024/03/11/indian-crypto-investment-platform-mudrex-to-offer-us-bitcoin-etfs-to-indian-investors/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines">said</a> CEO and co-founder Edul Patel in a recent interview.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Patel emphasized the significance of this move for institutions, granting them access to spot bitcoin ETFs, previously only accessible to retail investors via US stock investing firms.</span></p>
<h2><strong><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Indian Investors Can Invest in US Spot Bitcoin ETFs</span></strong></h2>
<p><span class="replacer"></span><br />
<span data-preserver-spaces="true">Investment platform Mudrex will be the first to offer this service to institutions in India. Within the first phase of its offering, Mudrex will list the top four BTC ETFs from BlackRock, Fidelity, Vanguard, and Franklin Templeton.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Committed to full compliance with Indian regulatory frameworks, Mudrex is registered with the Financial Intelligence Unit (FIU) of India, ensuring adherence to stringent legal standards. The platform empowers users with access to a diverse array of over 350 cryptocurrencies and crypto baskets, augmented by actionable insights to guide investment decisions effectively.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Edul Patel, CEO and co-founder of Mudrex, emphasized the platform&#8217;s pioneering status in offering this service to Indian investors. In an interview, Patel highlighted the significance of Mudrex&#8217;s robust banking relationships, enabling seamless transactions for users navigating the complexities of the LRS process.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;This is much more valuable to institutions, as this was already available to retailers,&#8221; Patel said, highlighting the strategic significance of the move. While retail clients in India had limited access to spot Bitcoin ETFs through US stock investing companies, Mudrex aims to pioneer this service for institutional investors in the country.</span></p>
<blockquote><p><em><span data-preserver-spaces="true">“We are certainly the first Indian crypto platform to offer this service. The LRS is the tricky part for most people, and over there (in the US), because we also have strong banking relationships, we’re able to help users do these transactions in a very seamless way, and that’s why these services are important.”</span></em></p></blockquote>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Mudrex, headquartered in California and backed by Y-Combinator, operates with a subsidiary registered with the Intelligence Unit of India. Additionally, it holds licenses in Lithuania and Italy within the European Union.</span></p>
<h2><strong><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Mudrex Facilitates Indian Investors&#8217; Access to Crypto ETFs Through the Liberalized Remittance Scheme</span></strong></h2>
<p><span class="replacer"></span><br />
<span data-preserver-spaces="true">Indian investors seeking exposure to crypto ETFs can leverage two avenues: domestic exchanges or the Liberalized Remittance Scheme (LRS), with the latter incurring a 20% tax collected at source (TCS) on remittances. Mudrex intends to leverage the LRS route to facilitate seamless access to spot <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-already-tops-silver-in-u-s-etf-market-after-sec-approvals.htm">Bitcoin</a> ETFs for its clientele.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Patel explained the operational structure, indicating that Mudrex would ensure the processing of actual transactions through broker partners in the US. At the same time, its Indian subsidiary would facilitate the spot Bitcoin ETF service. </span><span data-preserver-spaces="true">This development comes amidst a complex regulatory landscape in India, where the Reserve Bank of India (RBI) and the Finance Ministry hold divergent views on cryptocurrency.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">While <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/rbi-governor-warns-of-crypto-risks-to-emerging-markets.htm">the RBI has expressed skepticism towards crypto</a>, the Finance Ministry&#8217;s Intelligence Unit has registered numerous Indian crypto service providers and imposed stringent taxes on the sector. While the two agree on the need to protect the Indian economy and investors, their regulatory focus can appear to differ.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Patel elucidated the regulatory framework surrounding the venture, highlighting the compatibility of bitcoin spot ETFs with the Liberalized Remittance Scheme (LRS), which </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://economictimes.indiatimes.com/wealth/save/rbi-liberalised-remittance-scheme-how-indians-can-use-lrs-to-invest-remit-money-abroad/articleshow/94365344.cms?utm_source=contentofinterest&amp;utm_medium=text&amp;utm_campaign=cppst" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">simplifies overseas investments for Indians</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true">. Mudrex will enable investments in spot bitcoin ETFs on its platform, with a minimum investment threshold of $5,000 and a maximum limit of $250,000, aligning with the RBI&#8217;s prescribed annual LRS limit.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">In contrast, utilizing domestic crypto exchanges in India subjects investors to a 1% tax deducted at source (TDS) on the transfer of crypto assets, coupled with a hefty 30% tax on profits. </span><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Navigating the intricacies of the LRS, Patel emphasized Mudrex&#8217;s commitment to facilitating seamless transactions and leveraging robust banking relationships to streamline users&#8217; processes. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;The LRS is the tricky part for most people, and over there (in the US), because we also have strong banking relationships, we&#8217;re able to help users do these transactions in a very seamless way, and that&#8217;s why these services are important,&#8221; Patel stated.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Among Mudrex&#8217;s clientele of 350 institutions, Patel revealed that approximately 20 have initiated the process of joining the platform for spot BTC ETF investments, with an anticipated average ticket size of $110,000. </span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/mudrex-to-offer-us-spot-bitcoin-etfs-to-indian-investors.htm">Mudrex to Offer US Spot Bitcoin ETFs to Indian Investors</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptonews.com">Cryptonews</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		<enclosure url="https://cimg.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/11131214/1710162733-1710162716510_processed.jpg" length="103646" type="image/jpeg" />

			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
