<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	 xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" >

<channel>
	<title>Cryptopolitan</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.cryptopolitan.com</link>
	<description>Neutral and Authentic News</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 22:29:36 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/02/cropped-Dark_CP_Symbol-32x32.png</url>
	<title>Cryptopolitan</title>
	<link>https://www.cryptopolitan.com</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Top 10 AI Coins to Buy A Head Of  NVIDIA AI Conference</title>
		<link>https://www.cryptopolitan.com/ai-coins-to-buy-a-head-of-nvidia-ai/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ann Mugoiri]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 22:29:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cryptocurrency trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cryptomarket]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fetch.ai]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.cryptopolitan.com/?p=482608</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[AI Coins to Buy: The upcoming NVIDIA AI Conference, set for March 18th, marks a pivotal moment for cryptocurrency enthusiasts and investors alike. As NVIDIA, a powerhouse in AI technology, gears up to showcase its latest advancements, the spotlight turns to AI-driven cryptocurrencies.  These digital assets, combining cutting-edge blockchain and AI innovations, present unprecedented growth [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>AI Coins to Buy: The upcoming NVIDIA AI Conference, set for March 18th, marks a pivotal moment for cryptocurrency enthusiasts and investors alike. As <a href="https://www.nvidia.com/gtc/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">NVIDIA</a>, a powerhouse in AI technology, gears up to showcase its latest advancements, the spotlight turns to AI-driven cryptocurrencies. </p>



<p>These digital <a href="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/weekly-crypto-price-analysis/">assets</a>, combining cutting-edge blockchain and AI innovations, present unprecedented growth potential in the bullish market trend. The fusion promises to redefine the crypto sphere, highlighting top AI altcoins as key players to watch.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Render Network (RNDR)</h2>



<p>Render Network (RNDR) is at the forefront of decentralized GPU-powered rendering, revolutionizing content creation. It bridges the gap between those in need of rendering services and GPU owners with idle resources, utilizing OctaneRender for its operations.&nbsp;</p>



<p>Over the past week, Render has seen an 8% increase in its value. RNDR current price stands at $11.47, securing the 35th position on <a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/currencies/render/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">CoinMarketCap</a> with a market cap close to $4.33 billion.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Bittensor (TAO)&nbsp;</h2>



<p>Bittensor (TAO) is carving a niche in the decentralized machine-learning network sector, built on a blockchain infrastructure. A noteworthy 7% growth in a week has been observed recently. Now priced at $686, <a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/currencies/bittensor/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">Bittensor&#8217;s</a> market capitalization has reached $4.38 billion. Its emerging prominence in the AI-driven altcoin market signals the potential for further growth, especially with the upcoming NVIDIA AI Conference on the horizon.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Fetch.ai (FET)</h2>



<p>Fetch.ai (FET) is gaining attention in the AI industry with its innovative project. This initiative aims to develop a decentralized machine learning network, employing blockchain technology to streamline online transactions. Fetch.ai&#8217;s market value has soared by 61% over the last week, pushing its trading <a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/currencies/fetch/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">pric</a>e to $2.69. This surge makes it a top contender to watch closely before the NVIDIA AI conference.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Ocean Protocol (OCEAN)</h2>



<p>Ocean Protocol (OCEAN) is spearheading a pivotal shift in data exchange, using blockchain, decentralized networks, and cutting-edge encryption for secure, private communications. In the recent month, the protocol has seen its value increase by 10.9%, reaching a price point of $1.22. With a market cap now at $692 million and ranking 133rd on <a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/currencies/ocean-protocol/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">CoinMarketCap</a>, Ocean Protocol stands out as a top AI cryptocurrency to keep an eye on leading up to the NVIDIA AI conference.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Arkham (AKT)</h2>



<p>Arkham (AKR) is innovating in the crypto space with its intelligence platform, designed to uncover the real influencers behind market movements. It meticulously categorizes crypto trades and transactions by value, token, timing, and involved parties. <img fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" src="https://lh7-us.googleusercontent.com/Cd05beeFGOIcJcYe5BzPh_pjb3yAWoJ0PyzCYjFCQyu9yvdLUjdkvjJdURCFB7wWJ4J0wYqX14DA_Yew_sTqfgxPaP-4GdnRPj2G4ExUj-Zzmk68VhOlchBKr0v1m1fP5I90ZFnwnp14NfEZKj9Sosw" width="624" height="411"></p>



<p>AKT price chart</p>



<p>Over the past week, Arkham has <a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/currencies/akash-network/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">enjoyed</a> a 37% uptick in its value, now priced at $6.20 and has achieved a market capitalization of $1.39 million. This growth highlights Arkham as a noteworthy coin to buy before the NVIDIA AI conference.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">PAAL AI (PAAL)</h2>



<p>PAAL AI (PAAL) is making strides with its AI and machine learning-powered chatbot capabilities, encompassing natural language processing, image recognition, and sophisticated decision-making tools. Currently valued at <a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/currencies/paal-ai/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">$0.8133</a>, with a market cap of just $649, PAAL has seen an impressive 68% surge in value over the past week. This positions PAAL AI as a top AI altcoin for investment consideration.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">0x0.ai (0x0)</h2>



<p>0x0.ai (0x0) is revolutionizing the space of Solidity Smart Contract auditing through AI and machine learning, identifying code vulnerabilities, errors, and issues effectively. With a current price of $0.468211 and a 24-hour trading volume of $4,163,274, 0x0.ai has <a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/currencies/0x0-ai-ai-smart-contract/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">witnessed</a> an 11.72% increase in the last 24 hours. Its market cap stands at $406,671,058, ranking it 223rd on CoinMarketCap, making it an AI project of interest.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">ChainGPT (CGPT)</h2>



<p>ChainGPT (CGPT), a blockchain-based AI solution, is witnessing considerable market traction, evidenced by a 36% increase in its token value over the past week. Currently, its valuation stands at $0.483255. This momentum has elevated its position to the 334th spot on <a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/currencies/chaingpt/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">CoinMarketCap</a>, boasting a market capitalization of $199,888,802.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">NEAR Protocol (NEAR)</h2>



<p>NEAR Protocol (NEAR), this layer-one blockchain, distinguishes itself with a community-driven cloud computing framework. It addresses common blockchain challenges, including sluggish transactions and limited interoperability, setting a new standard for efficiency.&nbsp;</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image"><img decoding="async" width="694" height="455" src="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/image-43.png" alt="" class="wp-image-482621" srcset="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/image-43.png 694w, https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/image-43-300x197.png 300w" sizes="(max-width: 694px) 100vw, 694px" /></figure>



<p>NEAR price chart</p>



<p>The NEAR token has enjoyed a bullish momentum, climbing over 56% in the last week alone. Its price now sits at $6.77, following a 14.42% rise in the past 24 hours, positioning it as a noteworthy asset, especially with the NVIDIA AI conference on the horizon. NEAR&#8217;s market capitalization has reached $7,065,179,426, ranking it 20th on <a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/currencies/near-protocol/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">CoinMarketCap</a>.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Oasis Network (ROSE)</h2>



<p>Oasis Network (ROSE) stands out as a privacy-centric, scalable layer-1 blockchain platform. Its design ensures high throughput and minimal transaction fees without compromising security. This infrastructure supports emerging Web3 technologies, including DeFi and the Metaverse. The current price of ROSE is $0.180692, reflecting a 3.53% increase over the last 24 hours.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Conclusion</h2>



<p>The impending NVIDIA AI Conference serves as a pivotal moment for investors to identify AI cryptocurrencies with <a href="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/4-meme-coin-altcoins-to-buy-in-2024/">significant</a> growth potential. As the market trends upwards, these digital assets, particularly Render, offer a unique investment avenue in the rapidly evolving intersection of AI and blockchain technology.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Top-10-AI-Coins-to-Buy-A-Head-Of-NVIDIA-AI-Conference-1-1.jpeg" medium="image"  type="image/jpeg" /><media:thumbnail url="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Top-10-AI-Coins-to-Buy-A-Head-Of-NVIDIA-AI-Conference-1-1.jpeg"/>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Team Behind Top Lending Protocol Launches Suilend on Sui</title>
		<link>https://www.cryptopolitan.com/team-behind-top-lending-protocol-launches-suilend-on-sui/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chainwire]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 22:08:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blockchain]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DeFi]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[web3]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.cryptopolitan.com/?p=482611</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Grand Cayman, Cayman Islands, March 11th, 2024, Chainwire The Suilend lending protocol is Solend’s first venture outside of the Solana ecosystem underscoring confidence in Sui&#8217;s technology Suilend, Solend’s first expansion outside the Solana ecosystem, officially launched today on the Sui Network. Solend, which boasts over $200 million in total value locked (TVL) across 170,000+ users [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span><strong>Grand Cayman, Cayman Islands, March 11th, 2024, Chainwire</strong></span></p>
<p></p>
<h3>The Suilend lending protocol is Solend’s first venture outside of the Solana ecosystem underscoring confidence in Sui&#8217;s technology</h3>
<p><a href="https://suilend.fi" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">Suilend</a>, Solend’s first expansion outside the Solana ecosystem, officially launched today on the Sui Network. Solend, which boasts over $200 million in total value locked (TVL) across 170,000+ users with support for 70+ assets, now brings its unparalleled DeFi expertise and experience building industry-leading lending protocols to the Sui ecosystem in a move that adds to the quickly expanding depth of the Sui ecosystem. </p>
<blockquote><p>Discussing the launch, Rooter, the pseudonymous Founder of Solend, said, &#8220;Developing on Ethereum and Solana felt like building a cathedral with chisels and hammers. That&#8217;s not to say you can&#8217;t build great things — cathedrals are some of the most beautiful human achievements. But we want to build rocket ships, and for that, you need advanced tools like laser cutters and welders. That&#8217;s what Sui and Move offer with better developer tools.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>The announcement follows hot on the heels of Bluefin, a burgeoning DEX with daily volumes exceeding $100 million, committing exclusively to Sui over Arbitrum for its V2 development and unveiling its roadmap into 2024.</p>
<p>Security is a distinct focus for participants in the DeFi space, and with the launch of Solend on Sui, the protocol is leveraging a network in Sui that has industry-leading security. By launching on Sui, Solend capitalizes on the inherent security features integrated into the Move language, which provides built-in protections for its smart contracts. Additionally, partnerships with leading blockchain security firms, Zellic and Ottersec, entail rigorous audits of projects like Suilend, ensuring adherence to the highest security standards.</p>
<p>Suilend will also benefit from Sui’s parallel processing for most transactions. Sui boasts the lowest levels of latency in the industry and facilitates horizontal scaling, achieving a peak throughput of up to 297,000 transactions per second and a time-to-finality of approximately 480 milliseconds. </p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;We are delighted to welcome a protocol with the background of performance and success of Suilend to the Sui ecosystem,&#8221; said Greg Siourounis, Managing Director of the Sui Foundation. &#8220;Sui&#8217;s blistering transaction speeds, infinite scalability and pervasive efficiency are tailor-made for DeFi projects like Suilend, and we look forward to watching their continued growth and success on Sui.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>This strategic move comes as Sui recently surpassed the $500 million Total Value Locked (TVL) milestone, firmly establishing itself within the top 10 DeFi ecosystems globally. Over the past month alone, a staggering $310 million in assets has migrated from Ethereum to Sui via Wormhole, eclipsing all other blockchain transfers combined, signaling the growing trust in the ecosystem’s DeFi capabilities.</p>
<p></p>
<h5>Contact</h5>
<p><span><strong>Sui Foundation</strong><br /></span><span><strong>media@sui.io</strong><br /></span></p>
<p class="chainwire-disclaimer cp-box cp-box-gray"><i><strong>Disclaimer.</strong> This is a paid press release. Readers should do their own due diligence before taking any actions related to the promoted company or any of its affiliates or services. <a href="https://cryptopolitan.com/">Cryptopolitan.com</a> is not responsible, directly or indirectly, for any damage or loss caused or alleged to be caused by or in connection with the use of or reliance on any content, goods or services mentioned in the press release.</i></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Sui_Header_1710189643mMbVeE9xl8.jpg" medium="image"  type="image/jpeg" /><media:thumbnail url="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Sui_Header_1710189643mMbVeE9xl8.jpg"/>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Avalanche Price Prediction 2024-2033: Time to Buy AVAX?</title>
		<link>https://www.cryptopolitan.com/avalanche-price-prediction/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Brian Koome]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 21:03:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crypto Price Predictions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cryptomarket]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.cryptopolitan.com/?p=127387</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Avalanche Price Prediction 2024-2033 Here’s a thought: The value of an AVAX token is tied to the usefulness of the Avalanche platform. If people want to use the Avalanche platform, AVAX tokens rise in value. Conversely, the AVAX token won’t be as useful for an investment portfolio if the platform becomes obsolete or unpopular. Do [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<h4 class="wp-block-heading">Avalanche Price Prediction 2024-2033</h4>



<ul>
<li><a href="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/avalanche-price-prediction/#Avalanche-Price-Prediction-2024"><u>Avalanche Price Prediction 2024</u></a> – up to $67.77</li>



<li><a href="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/avalanche-price-prediction/#Avalanche-Price-Prediction-2027"><u>Avalanche Price Prediction 2027</u></a>– up to $208.30</li>



<li><a href="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/avalanche-price-prediction/#Avalanche-Price-Prediction-2030"><u>Avalanche Price Prediction 2030</u></a> – up to $681.32</li>



<li><a href="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/avalanche-price-prediction/#Avalanche-Price-Prediction-2033"><u>Avalanche Price Prediction 2033</u></a> – up to $2,098.00</li>
</ul>



<p>Here’s a thought: The value of an AVAX token is tied to the usefulness of the Avalanche platform. If people want to use the Avalanche platform, AVAX tokens rise in value. Conversely, the AVAX token won’t be as useful for an investment portfolio if the platform becomes obsolete or unpopular.</p>



<p>Do you think Avalanche will still be a viable cryptocurrency in 2024 and beyond now that we know more about it? Let’s study the charts in this AVAX price analysis and AVAX price prediction.</p>



<p>Is it time to buy the dip? While some platforms suggest Avalanche can reach $166.17 by 2027, Cryptopolitan estimates AVAX to hit a maximum of $1,465.95 at best in 2033.&nbsp;</p>



<h4 class="wp-block-heading">How much is AVAX worth?</h4>



<p>The current price of Avalanche is $48.90, with a 24-hour trading volume of $1.63 billion. Avalanche is  16.26% in the last 24 hours. The current Market cap ranking is #11, with a live market cap of $18.46 billion. It has a circulating supply of 377,304,616 AVAX coins and a maximum supply of 720,000,000 AVAX coins.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Avalanche price analysis</h2>



<p>TL; DR Breakdown:</p>



<ul>
<li>AVAX is one of the best-performing mega-cap altcoins.</li>



<li>It recently dropped from the top 10 coins by market capitalization.</li>
</ul>



<p>AVAX’s recovery in the last quarter of 2023 pushed it to the top 10 cryptocurrencies by market capitalization. The coin also achieved a new one-year high of $49.96. However, it was corrected and stands at position 11.</p>



<p>It is up 236.01% in the last 12 months and 21.26% over the previous 30 days. The recent run helped it recoup most of 2023’s losses.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading">AVAX price analysis 1-day chart</h3>



<p>The charts show that the AVAX price rose from December 2023, creating multiple bullish daily candlesticks.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image"><img decoding="async" src="https://lh7-us.googleusercontent.com/im-2oAvHRNO2IlGUSOIJ87pLpfylejg0rAa3ar1sArvsesUgpOrSwJ6-D4PM3RearESsnY0dxife6s71CuK_d25EhPMi1c19LQN_yYbf6BY_ZkPii8EfjHHxquZHyxCYuPUSJd21L3dHydqCtUj5OfA" alt=""/></figure>



<p>The RSI is a momentum indicator that evaluates whether a market is overbought or oversold and whether to accumulate or sell an asset.</p>



<p>Readings above 50 and an upward trend suggest that bulls have an advantage, while readings below 50 indicate the opposite. The coin is in neutral territory without divergence. AVAX registered positive momentum for the better part of March.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading">AVAX/USD 4-hour price chart</h3>



<p>The coin registers positive momentum in this time frame, contributing to a bullish price movement in the last 20 hours. The RSI is at 55.75.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image"><img decoding="async" src="https://lh7-us.googleusercontent.com/bZgeWcOgqlVD4wZ3Lj9SoAX1aimQ2uGIbzGM_qVe5126uFkObYFZAUmFVbZQ-h1MTGXDidOZDmcKJXMNxIxBX01pe2Y9gZDj8dUdgn8q5EBja1rYlJUd2tpOhRbx_mI8ywVtqEW_RnJKhgATH4JojX4" alt=""/></figure>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading">What to expect from AVAX price analysis next?</h3>



<p>AVAX’s recent recovery pushed the coin above $45. There are no signs of reversal at current levels.</p>



<p></p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Is AVAX a good investment?</h2>



<p>Avalanche promises to outperform the second-largest <a href="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/news/blockchain/"><u>blockchain</u></a> by market capitalization, <a href="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/news/ethereum-eth/"><u>Ethereum</u></a>. The coin already made it to the top 10 list and is among the best-performing mega-altcoins this year. The AVAX token acts as the basic accounting unit on the Avalanche network. Our CP Price Prediction section will show how the coin will gain value in years to come.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Recent News</h2>



<p>Ava Labs’ introduction of the Vryx for the Avalanche (AVAX) blockchain is pivotal when the coin strives to maintain its #9 market cap position. Scheduled for the second quarter of 2024, this update targets the critical challenge of scaling blockchains for higher transaction volumes without sacrificing security or decentralization. Vryx is set to achieve an impressive 100,000 transactions per second (TPS) by employing a novel approach named Decoupled State Machine Replication (DSMR). Unlike traditional methods where transactions and verification are intertwined, DSMR separates these processes, allowing for faster and more efficient transaction handling. This upgrade will be initially tested on the HyperSDK testnet. While DSMR promises increased throughput, it also raises concerns about the potential spread of invalid transactions, which could congest the network. To mitigate this, Vryx will ensure only transactions that pay fees are circulated, maintaining the network’s efficiency. This advancement, if successful, could significantly enhance Avalanche’s capabilities and influence in the blockchain sector.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Avalanche Price Prediction 2024-2033</h2>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading">Avalanche Price Prediction by Cryptopolitan</h3>



<figure class="wp-block-image"><img decoding="async" src="https://lh7-us.googleusercontent.com/XUipI_wDgIpMiGwstbLPsDuXCy8cumN20fXpzNpYReb2aWXhbPXDFt9XQpE4XoBQohdQ8hjE6Phb7WB8GHGcYHPsIsXoskOzRAXRsSivAYxE79bHyj6Xgae9a0PTG7dQ2PSYbtHx1va4HL6KjaxWP2Q" alt=""/></figure>



<figure class="wp-block-table"><table><tbody><tr><td>Year</td><td>Minimum Price $</td><td>Average Price $</td><td>Maximum Price $</td></tr><tr><td>2024</td><td>$56.28</td><td>$58.01</td><td>$67.77</td></tr><tr><td>2025</td><td>$83.62</td><td>$85.95</td><td>$95.17</td></tr><tr><td>2026</td><td>$120.22</td><td>$123.66</td><td>$143.31</td></tr><tr><td>2027</td><td>$178.80</td><td>$184.98</td><td>$208.30</td></tr><tr><td>2028</td><td>$269.31</td><td>$276.71</td><td>$319.85</td></tr><tr><td>2029</td><td>$384.30</td><td>$398.13</td><td>$459.77</td></tr><tr><td>2030</td><td>$562.57</td><td>$578.50</td><td>$681.32</td></tr><tr><td>2031</td><td>$803.57</td><td>$832.50</td><td>$986.86</td></tr><tr><td>2032</td><td>$1,200.00</td><td>$1,233.00</td><td>$1,401.00</td></tr><tr><td>2033</td><td>$1,696.00</td><td>$1,757.00</td><td>$2,098.00</td></tr></tbody></table></figure>



<h4 class="wp-block-heading">Avalanche Price Prediction 2024</h4>



<p>According to our Avalanche AVAX price prediction for 2024, we expect a minimum price of $56.28&nbsp; and an average price of $58.01. However, If Avalanche AVAX’s growth trajectory persists, we predict its value could reach as high as $67.77 at its peak.</p>



<h4 class="wp-block-heading">Avalanche Price Prediction 2025</h4>



<p>According to our Avalanche AVAX price prediction for 2025, the minimum price of AVAX will be $83.62, while the average price will be around $85.95. There is potential for significant growth in the value of Avalanche AVAX during this period, with the token possibly reaching a maximum price of $95.17 by the end of 2025.</p>



<h4 class="wp-block-heading">Avalanche Price Prediction 2026</h4>



<p>Avalanche’s price prediction for 2026 will be a minimum price of $120.22 and an average predicted value of $123.66. We expect AVAX’s price to surge to a maximum of $143.31 by 2026.</p>



<h4 class="wp-block-heading">Avalanche Price Prediction 2027</h4>



<p>Our Avalanche AVAX price prediction for 2027 is a minimum value of $178.80 with an average trading price of $184.98. Based on the Avalanche AVAX price prediction for 2027, the price could reach a maximum of $208.30 during the year.</p>



<h4 class="wp-block-heading">Avalanche Price Prediction 2028</h4>



<p>Based on our Avalanche AVAX price prediction for 2028, the AVAX token is anticipated to experience a bullish trend with a predicted floor price of $269.31 and an average trading value of $276.71. The highest possible price for 2028 is estimated to reach $319.85, reflecting a significant increase in the token’s valuation.</p>



<h4 class="wp-block-heading">Avalanche Price Prediction 2029</h4>



<p>Our Avalanche AVAX price prediction for 2029 suggests that the minimum price level could be $384.30. The AVAX token will experience significant growth, with a maximum potential price value of $459.77 and an average projected value of $398.13.</p>



<h4 class="wp-block-heading">Avalanche Price Prediction 2030</h4>



<p>According to our Avalanche AVAX price prediction for 2030, the cryptocurrency’s value may drop to a low of $562.57 by year-end. However, we expect the average trading price to be $578.50 and the maximum estimated price to reach as high as $681.32.</p>



<h4 class="wp-block-heading">Avalanche Price Prediction 2031</h4>



<p>Based on our Avalanche AVAX price prediction for 2031, the minimum price of AVAX will be approximately $803.57, while the average price will be around $832.50. The maximum estimated value for AVAX in 2031 will reach $986.86.</p>



<h4 class="wp-block-heading">Avalanche Price Prediction 2032</h4>



<p>In our 2033 Avalanche AVAX price prediction, we anticipate a minimum trading price of $1200 and an average value of $1233 for the token. We expect Avalanche AVAX to experience a surge in value and reach a maximum price of $1401.</p>



<h4 class="wp-block-heading">Avalanche Price Prediction 2033</h4>



<p>According to our Avalanche AVAX price prediction for 2032, the AVAX coin will rise steadily. However, the minimum price of the coin will be $1696. The average trading price is estimated at $1757, indicating steady growth. The maximum estimated price for 2032 is $2098, showing a potential surge in price.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading">Avalanche Price Predictions by Walletinvestor</h3>



<p>Wallet Investor uses technical analysis to provide the AVAX price forecast. The platform indicates Avalanche’s past performance index rating as C; it adds that AVAX would make an ‘good’ one-year investment. The expected average price in 2025 will be $50.017. Avalanche’s return on investment (ROI) will be 14.9% in 2025. In 2026, the ROI will be 32%; in 2027, it will be 48.6%; in 2028, it will be 65.8%. According to the analysis, the Avalanche price is bearish over the entire period.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading">Avalanche Price Predictions by CryptoPredictions</h3>



<p>The site scans a coin’s exchange prices and other historical crypto market data and analyzes it to provide an Avalanche price forecast.</p>



<p>In 2025, the Avalanche cost will be $43.031 in June and $47.498 in December. In 2027, AVAX will sell at an average price of $58.049 in January and $66.631 in December.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading">Avalanche Price Predictions by Digitalcoinprice</h3>



<p>Avalanche will be on a bullish trend from 2024 to 2033; the minimum and maximum prices AVAX for the entire duration will be $37.93 and $834.53, respectively. In 2025, it will trade at a mean price of $106.67. It will reach a maximum price of $111.20 and a minimum of $92.06. In 2027, it will trade at a mean price of $186.15. It will reach a maximum price of $189.26 and a minimum of $165.17. In 2033, it will trade at a mean price of $824.40. It will reach a minimum of $805.21.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading">Avalanche Predictions By Industry Experts</h3>



<p>Avalanche forecast by<a href="https://www.binance.com/en/markets?ref=16863683" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank"><u> Binance</u></a>, the world’s largest exchange by trading volume, indicates a bullish price projection; AVAX will average at $45.64 in 2025, $50.32 in 2027, and $58.25 in 2030.&nbsp;</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Avalanche Overview</h2>



<figure class="wp-block-table"><table><tbody><tr><td>MARKET CAP</td><td>CIRCULATING SUPPLY</td><td>POPULARITY</td><td>ALL-TIME LOW</td><td>ALL-TIME HIGH</td></tr><tr><td>$16.288 Billion</td><td>377,259,824</td><td>#11</td><td>$2.79</td><td>$146.22</td></tr></tbody></table></figure>



<p>Avalanche began as a protocol for solving for consensus in a network of unreliable machines, where failures may be crash-fault or Byzantine. The protocol’s fundamentals were first shared on the InterPlanetary File System (IPFS) in May 2018 by a pseudonymous group of enthusiasts named “Team Rocket.”</p>



<p>Researchers from Cornell University led by Emin Gün Sirer and doctoral students Maofan “Ted” Yin and Kevin Sekniqi later developed Avalanche. Following the research stage, a startup technology company was founded to develop a blockchain network that met finance industry requirements. In March 2020, the AVA codebase (Developer Accelerator Program or AVA DAP) for the Avalanche consensus protocol became publicly available as open-source software.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">AVAX Price History</h2>



<p>In September 2020, Avalanche issued its native token, Avax. On Dec 31, 2020, the coin hit an All Time Low at $2.7888.</p>



<p>In September 2021, the Ava Labs Foundation received a $230 million investment from a Polychain and Three Arrows Capital group by purchasing the AVAX cryptocurrency.</p>



<p>In November 2021, following an agreement with Deloitte to improve U.S. disaster relief funding, the Avalanche blockchain moved into the top 10 cryptocurrencies in capitalization. At that time, AVAX achieved its All-Time High at $146.22.</p>



<p>In August 2022, whistleblower “Crypto Leaks” published a report accusing Ava Labs of secret deals with a law firm aimed at legally destabilizing Avalanche’s competitors. Ava Labs CEO Emin Gün Sirer denies any dirty deal with Roche Freedmen law firm.</p>



<p>In 2023, AVAX maintained a bullish trend between January and May, after which bears overwhelmed the market. It resumed the positive momentum in October, rising to $49.96. It corrected to $40 in 2024.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image"><img decoding="async" src="https://lh7-us.googleusercontent.com/GVN9pOxcZFNZa66ZMCdGsWX-_enz-EJ0-_wYOC4tBIOPuCJ7ez7r4N4WP7Cu5IT3rGq23xjUwBUZcdXjO8JCMPuA_OHvGXB7N852mzBuJB31OOgSUyau3t4zlezAeNXs2RQZ4kfrb12uHlgI7oEb-gQ" alt=""/></figure>



<p>Source:<a href="https://coinstats.app/coins/avalanche-2/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"></a><a href="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/avalanche-price-prediction/#Avalanche-Price-Prediction-2024"><u>https://coinstats.app/coins/avalanche-2/</u></a></p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">More on Avalanche/ AVAX:</h2>



<p>The platform is fast, low-cost, and eco-friendly. Avalanche is fully compatible with<a href="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/news/ethereum-eth/"><u> Ethereum</u></a> assets, apps, and tools with faster speeds, higher throughput, and lower fees. Applications include</p>



<ul>
<li>Asset Issuance,</li>



<li>Borrowing and lending,</li>



<li>Automated Market Makers (AMMs),</li>



<li>Decentralized Exchanges (DEXs).</li>
</ul>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading">What is Avalanche &amp; AVAX?</h3>



<p>Ava Labs believes in the Avalanche protocol’s objective to construct a strong, safe, and power-efficient cryptocurrency network for apps (“dApps”), unique payment primitives, and new interconnecting blockchains. The Avax protocol is developing a new tokenized economy via its revolutionary technological approach, which includes seamless physical &amp; virtual asset trade, modular payment application primitives and derivative products, Web 3.0 private data and social apps, and much more.</p>



<p>Avalanche is one of the<a href="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/news/blockchain/"><u> blockchain</u></a> sector’s fastest smart contracts cryptocurrency networks. The network’s high number of PoS validators ensures efficiency. Furthermore, the Avalanche network is a lightning-fast, low-fee, and environmentally friendly platform. Again, any smart contract-based application might surpass its rivals on Avalanche.</p>



<p>Avalanche’s mainnet went live on September 21, 2021, and ever since, the platform has secured multiple projects, over $23.63 million of AVAX fees burnt, about 1,200 other block-offering validators, and over 958,000 community members on X.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading">What makes Avalanche the best smart contracts platform?</h3>



<ul>
<li>The Web’s Next Generation</li>
</ul>



<p>Avalanche and other cryptocurrency networks are next-generation web app platforms. The web is constantly changing. Web 1.0 PC networks linked us to the web and access to information and electronic online commerce payments. Web 2.0 mobile-first social networks linked us to internet communities, while algorithms enhanced our data user experience. Web 3.0 cryptocurrency networks are trustless community-based protocols such as Avalanche, which offers consumers back control over their information and privacy via natively incorporated<a href="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/news/defi/"><u> DeFi</u></a> apps.</p>



<ul>
<li>The third age of cryptocurrency innovation:</li>
</ul>



<p>Earlier cryptocurrency networks allowed for worldwide, decentralized virtual money. The 2nd wave of platforms expanded on this foundational technology to enable the construction of programmable dApps, enabling<a href="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/news/defi/"><u> DeFi</u></a> devices, NFTs, and other revenue-generating applications. These systems, however, have serviced a restricted range of use cases because of high-cost implications for transactions and slow transaction speeds. The third generation of cryptocurrency networks intends to accommodate a wider variety of decentralized Apps on less expensive and quicker blockchains, ushering in a multi-chain future with many ecosystems competing on speed, safety, and customization.</p>



<ul>
<li>Innovative technological architecture</li>
</ul>



<p>Avalanche uses revolutionary consensus means and a one-of-a-kind feature to provide a quick and scalable solution. Avalanche is a proof-of-stake (“PoS”) network that leverages probabilistic agreement to protect payments while maintaining performance and scalability. Avalanche’s distinctive multi-chain design makes it a blockchain platform, with several “subnets” supporting varied customer demands. This primary feature essential operations native to distinct subnets to interoperate effortlessly, without performance deterioration seen in networks when all activity is piled onto a single chain.</p>



<ul>
<li>Reliable network fulfillment</li>
</ul>



<p>Base-layer decentralized network technology protocols to host various applications and develop a robust digital economy must provide an optimum balance of decentralization, safety, and scalability while charging cheap transaction costs. Avalanche’s main net provides a transaction resolution layer that is highly competitive with the top PoS and PoW cryptocurrency systems in various criteria.</p>



<ul>
<li>Early uptake is encouraging.</li>
</ul>



<p>The capabilities of Avalanche have made it appropriate for many 3rd developers who are quickly launching new<a href="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/news/defi/"><u> DeFi</u></a> solutions on the Avax C-Chain. Decentralized exchanges, liquidity mining, loans, synthetic assets, and other services are available via dApps. Consequently, the network has seen a significant increase in assets, apps, and bespoke execution on subnets targeted to corporations and bodies introduced briefly since the main net went online. This increased use has resulted in a continuous increase in transaction fee income to the network, supporting the tokens’ economic worth. Remember, the Avalanche blockchain was meant to help dApp developers deploy products on active subnets, just like the<a href="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/news/ethereum-eth/"><u> Ethereum</u></a> virtual machine.</p>



<ul>
<li>Risks and uncertainty:</li>
</ul>



<p>Failing to implement its product plan, delayed system governance rollout, declining developer cravings, dApps not acquiring significant demand, rival cryptocurrency networks gaining share, user and transaction cost implication income do not materialize, crypto volatility, and regulatory concerns.</p>



<p>Avalanche provides a new form of consensus and flexibility that other Layer 1.0 protocols do not offer. While the system is still in its early stages, its degree of acceptance indicates that blockchain developers are aware of its potential and expect Avalanche to achieve its vision of a scalable and extensible digital world more than other blockchains.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading">Avalanche Features</h3>



<p>The Platform Chain (P-Chain), the Exchange Chain (X-Chain), and the Contract Chain are all incorporated into Avalanche (C-Chain). All three blockchains are authenticated and secured by Avalanche’s fundamental network.</p>



<ul>
<li>The P-Chain is a network of interconnected nodes (Platform Chain).</li>
</ul>



<p>Avalanche’s metadata blockchain, which controls authenticators and custom subnets, is known as the P-Chain. Validators stake AVAX on the P-Chain to defend the network.</p>



<ul>
<li>The X-Chain is a network of interconnected computers.</li>
</ul>



<p>The X-Chain is Avalanche’s default asset blockchain, allowing asset building and trading. This Avalanche blockchain is designed for transactions requiring high throughput and quick completion (for dApps, use the C-Chain).</p>



<ul>
<li>The C-Chain is a series of links in a chain (Contract Chain).</li>
</ul>



<p>The C-Chain is Avalanche’s default smart contract blockchain, letting developers create<a href="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/news/ethereum-eth/"><u> Ethereum</u></a>-compatible programs and assets at lower prices and quicker transactions.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Conclusion&nbsp;</h2>



<p>The future of Avalanche (AVAX) holds both promise and uncertainty as it continues to establish its position in the blockchain industry. With its focus on scalability, fast transaction processing, and unique features like decentralized governance and fee structures, Avalanche has gained attention as a potential competitor to established platforms like Ethereum.</p>



<p>Looking ahead, the price prediction for AVAX from 2024 to 2033, investment advice, and your research may present a range of possibilities. While it is challenging to accurately forecast the exact trajectory of any cryptocurrency from the current Avalanche price, several factors contribute to its potential growth. These include its expanding ecosystem, increasing adoption of the Avalanche platform, and advancements in technology that improve transaction speeds and scalability.</p>



<p>Additionally, broader market trends, regulatory developments, and investor sentiment toward cryptocurrencies will influence AVAX’s performance. As the blockchain industry continues to evolve, competition among platforms intensifies, and market dynamics shift, it is crucial to consider both the opportunities and risks associated with AVAX. Remember to conduct own research if you intend to invest.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/embed/TmA7L1zhYlA" medium="video" width="1280" height="720">
			<media:player url="https://www.youtube.com/embed/TmA7L1zhYlA" />
			<media:title type="plain">AVAX A +8674% IS COMING?? - AVALANCHE PRICE PREDICTION 2023 &amp; ANALYSES</media:title>
			<media:description type="html"><![CDATA[AVAX A +8674% IS COMING?? - AVALANCHE PRICE PREDICTION 2023 &amp; ANALYSESWarning : The Indications that have been revealed in this video are unique and only for...]]></media:description>
			<media:thumbnail url="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/avax-a-8674-is-coming-avalanche-.jpg" />
			<media:rating scheme="urn:simple">nonadult</media:rating>
		</media:content>
<media:content url="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/CP_Altcoins_-AVAX-_1140x570.png" medium="image"  type="image/png" /><media:thumbnail url="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/CP_Altcoins_-AVAX-_1140x570.png"/>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>ApeCoin Price Prediction 2024-2033: Will APE Break $3 Resistance?</title>
		<link>https://www.cryptopolitan.com/apecoin-price-prediction/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Brian Koome]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 20:50:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crypto Price Predictions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[crypto trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cryptocurrency trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cryptomarket]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.cryptopolitan.com/?p=189466</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[ApeCoin Price Prediction 2024-2033 The NFT industry has been booming for the past few years and is not stopping anytime soon. The NFT project Bored Ape Yacht Club has been one of the most successful in the blockchain industry. However, recent statistics indicate that the project is losing its momentum. Various APE price highlights unfold [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<h3 class="wp-block-heading">ApeCoin Price Prediction 2024-2033</h3>



<ul>
<li><a href="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/apecoin-price-prediction/#ApeCoin-Price-Prediction-2024">ApeCoin Price Prediction 2024</a> – up to $3.65</li>



<li><a href="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/apecoin-price-prediction/#ApeCoin-Price-Prediction-2027">ApeCoin Price Prediction 2027</a> – up to $10.80</li>



<li><a href="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/apecoin-price-prediction/#ApeCoin-Price-Prediction-2030">ApeCoin Price Prediction 2030</a> – up to $33.46</li>



<li><a href="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/apecoin-price-prediction/#ApeCoin-Price-Prediction-2033">ApeCoin Price Prediction 2033</a> – up to $97.86</li>
</ul>



<p>The<a href="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/news/nft/"> NFT</a> industry has been booming for the past few years and is not stopping anytime soon. The<a href="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/news/nft/"> NFT</a> project Bored Ape Yacht Club has been one of the most successful in the<a href="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/news/blockchain/"> blockchain</a> industry. However, recent statistics indicate that the project is losing its momentum. Various APE price highlights unfold in this ApeCoin Price Prediction.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading">How much is ApeCoin (APE) worth?</h3>



<p>The current ApeCoin price is $2.32, with a 24-hour trading volume of $131.70 million. ApeCoin is up 0.88% in the last 24 hours. The current Market capitalization ranking is #83, with a live Apecoin market cap of $1.40 billion. It has a circulating supply of 604,895,833 APE coins and a maximum supply of 1,000,000,000 APE coins.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">ApeCoin price analysis</h2>



<p>TL; DR Breakdown</p>



<ul>
<li>APE is down 39.16% in the last 12 months and up 61.50% over the previous 30 days.</li>



<li>This month, it broke the $2 resistance.</li>
</ul>



<p>In 2023, APE’s decline accelerated in June, forcing it to trade below $2 multiple times. Positive market sentiment helped it hit the $1.434 mark in October; it continued rising this year, reaching a high of $2.5.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading">APE price analysis 1-day chart</h3>



<p>APE turned bullish in October 2023. It is down 39.16% in the last 12 months and up 61.50% over the previous 30 days.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image"><img decoding="async" src="https://lh7-us.googleusercontent.com/oDU4i3lUzijTOt3kisfaqljSKz5UAr-Jauexcn9-yIjTiSob4W1YcexnCBehex7oxGPee9Fe4u4_Plg9CNPQfGcXnUNYUDJ0eR1C0L8LpTIPqMLJ1UIYHtqtFp1_trusQaL-tyCkU0ZzVNTavE49tNE" alt=""/></figure>



<p>APE registered positive momentum this week amidst high volatility. Currently, the RSI is within the 30-70 neutral zone, which indicates the price is trending neutral; however, it’s pacing towards overbought territory.</p>



<p>There is no bearish divergence within the last four candles, which is no signal for price reversal from current areas.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading">APE/USD 4-hour price chart</h3>



<p>The 4-hour chart highlights ApeCoin’s movement and ‘choppiness’ through 2024.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image"><img decoding="async" src="https://lh7-us.googleusercontent.com/vpplUR9cpLpSPYI2B1oha9Z1Tc9lFZ_FVO6D4-1KdejrhgneavLSa_GkO89cH3cGjCzjRGbcaShvuu_b3BQfMiF1CVWZWmNuBULBXfAQuyHBQO--zV6VtS4ZCEKLpK957jImr5TJDmcTbc1XG6IW36Y" alt=""/></figure>



<p>The MACD indicator shows the coin registers little momentum.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading">What to expect from APE price analysis next?</h3>



<p>The charts show APE has turned bullish. The green candles and positive momentum gave a clear advantage to the bulls, and the run helped the coin break the $2 resistance. It faces resistance at $2.5.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Is ApeCoin a good investment?</h2>



<p>ApeCoin is a payment-ready cryptocurrency with a design that is identical to any other Web3 coin. Since ApeCoin is a widely used ERC-20 token, most retailers consider it acceptable.</p>



<p>Additionally, the coin is already being used as <a href="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/news/nft/">NFT</a> rewards; holders with the BAYC can immediately cash in their free APE. Our CP Price Prediction section will show how the coin will gain value in years to come.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Recent News</h2>



<p>Yuga Labs, a leading force in the NFT industry, has expanded its portfolio by acquiring Proof, known for its Moonbirds collection, further cementing its status as a dominant player. Yuga Labs CEO Daniel Alegre expressed enthusiasm for integrating Proof into the Yuga ecosystem, highlighting the move to enhance art, culture, and community engagement on the <a href="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/news/blockchain/">blockchain</a>. Although the financial details of the acquisition were not disclosed, the union is notable, considering Moonbirds’ once-celebrated status and its potential collaboration with Yuga Labs’ Otherside metaverse project. This strategic acquisition may positively influence the price of APE, Yuga Labs’ associated cryptocurrency, by boosting overall brand value, expanding the community, and integrating Moonbirds’ assets into high-profile projects like Otherside. However, the impact on APE’s price will also depend on broader NFT market trends, which have seen fluctuations in trading volumes compared to the peaks in previous years.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">ApeCoin Price Prediction 2024-2033</h2>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading">ApeCoin Price Prediction by Cryptopolitan</h3>



<figure class="wp-block-image"><img decoding="async" src="https://lh7-us.googleusercontent.com/tZvi0RaiNLekUymcaKH52f3ukKxVchId7FYbwR6aCT7z2-qC-jfwKf0kwrGIxKJr8giGKOmgZ7WKYO8qM2VBIwSE7U1Y9A9zQklCXEukCsZac2SpfnSosXZz0R-K9Oj0hY6sNbUf762A7eTCl-84Tyg" alt=""/></figure>



<figure class="wp-block-table"><table><tbody><tr><td>Year</td><td>Minimum Price $</td><td>Average Price $</td><td>Maximum Price $</td></tr><tr><td>2024</td><td>$3.12</td><td>$3.21</td><td>$3.65</td></tr><tr><td>2025</td><td>$4.54</td><td>$4.66</td><td>$5.36</td></tr><tr><td>2026</td><td>$6.22</td><td>$6.45</td><td>$7.63</td></tr><tr><td>2027</td><td>$9.12</td><td>$9.38</td><td>$10.80</td></tr><tr><td>2028</td><td>$13.03</td><td>$13.50</td><td>$15.87</td></tr><tr><td>2029</td><td>$19.51</td><td>$20.19</td><td>$22.79</td></tr><tr><td>2030</td><td>$26.93</td><td>$27.94</td><td>$33.46</td></tr><tr><td>2031</td><td>$38.70</td><td>$39.81</td><td>$46.57</td></tr><tr><td>2032</td><td>$55.14</td><td>$56.73</td><td>$66.30</td></tr><tr><td>2033</td><td>$82.60</td><td>$84.87</td><td>$97.86</td></tr></tbody></table></figure>



<h4 class="wp-block-heading">ApeCoin Price Prediction 2024</h4>



<p>According to our ApeCoin APE price prediction for 2024, we expect a minimum price of $3.12 and an average price of $3.21. However, if ApeCoin APE’s growth trajectory persists, we predict its value could reach as high as $3.65 at its peak.</p>



<h4 class="wp-block-heading">ApeCoin Price Prediction 2025</h4>



<p>According to our ApeCoin APE price prediction for 2025, the minimum price of APE will be $4.54, while the average price will be around $4.66. There is potential for significant growth in the value of ApeCoin APE during this period, with the token possibly reaching a maximum price of $5.36 by the end of 2025.</p>



<h4 class="wp-block-heading">ApeCoin Price Prediction 2026</h4>



<p>According to price prediction for 2026, we expect the minimum price of the coin to be $6.22 and an average predicted value of $6.45. We expect APE’s price to surge to a maximum of $7.63 by 2026.</p>



<h4 class="wp-block-heading">ApeCoin Price Prediction 2027</h4>



<p>Our ApeCoin APE price prediction for 2027 is a minimum value of $9.12 with an average trading price of $9.38. Based on the ApeCoin APE price prediction for 2027, the price could reach a maximum of $10.80 during the year.</p>



<h4 class="wp-block-heading">ApeCoin Price Prediction 2028</h4>



<p>Based on our ApeCoin APE price predictions for 2028, the APE token is anticipated to experience a bullish trend with a predicted floor price of $13.03 and an average trading value of $13.50. The highest possible price for 2028 is estimated to reach $15.87, reflecting a significant increase in the token’s valuation.</p>



<h4 class="wp-block-heading">ApeCoin Price Prediction 2029</h4>



<p>Our ApeCoin APE price prediction for 2029 suggests that the minimum price level could be $19.51. The APE token will experience significant growth, with a maximum potential price value of $22.79 and an average projected value of $20.19.</p>



<h4 class="wp-block-heading">ApeCoin Price Prediction 2030</h4>



<p>According to our ApeCoin APE price prediction for 2030, the cryptocurrency’s value may drop to a low of $26.93 by year-end. However, we expect the average trading price to be $27.94 and the maximum estimated price to reach as high as $33.46.</p>



<h4 class="wp-block-heading">ApeCoin Price Prediction 2031</h4>



<p>Based on our ApeCoin price prediction for 2031, the minimum price of APE will be approximately $38.70, while the average price will be around $39.81. The maximum estimated value for APE in 2031 will reach $46.57.</p>



<h4 class="wp-block-heading">ApeCoin Price Prediction 2032</h4>



<p>According to our ApeCoin price prediction for 2032, the APE coin will rise steadily. However, the minimum price of the coin will be $55.14. The average trading price is estimated at $56.73, indicating steady growth. The maximum estimated price for 2032 is $66.30, showing a potential surge in price.</p>



<h4 class="wp-block-heading">ApeCoin Price Prediction 2033</h4>



<p>In our 2033 ApeCoin price prediction, we anticipate a minimum trading price of $82.60 and an average value of $84.87 for the token. With several scheduled ecosystem upgrades, we expect ApeCoin APE to experience a surge in value and reach a maximum price of $97.86.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading">ApeCoin Price Predictions by WalletInvestor</h3>



<p>Wallet Investor uses technical analysis to provide a detailed Apecoin price forecast. The platform indicates. ApeCoin’s past performance index rating of C and adds that APE would make a bad one-year investment. The expected average price in 2025 is $0.2080. ApeCoin’s return on investment (ROI) will be -91.00% in 2025. In 2026, the ROI will be -91.22%; in 2027, it will be -88.67%; in 2028, it will be -86.47%. According to the analysis, the ApeCoin price is bearish over the entire period.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading">ApeCoin Price Predictions by CryptoPredictions</h3>



<p>The site scans a coin’s exchange prices and other historical market data and analyses it to provide APE coin price prediction.</p>



<p>In 2024, APE will trade at an average price of $2.621 in June and $2.314 in December. In 2026, APE will sell at an average price of $3.215 in January and $3.848 in December.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading">ApeCoin Price Predictions by Digitalcoin Price</h3>



<p>ApeCoin will be on a bullish trend from 2024 to 2033; the maximum value of APE for the entire duration will be $45.59. In 2025, it will trade at a mean price of $5.61. It will reach a maximum price of $6.07 and a minimum of $5.03. In 2027, it will trade at a mean price of $10.56. It will reach a maximum price of $10.69 and a minimum of $8.99. In 2033, it will trade at a mean price of $45.10. It will reach a minimum of $43.84.&nbsp;</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading">ApeCoin Predictions By Industry Experts</h3>



<p>ApeCoin price predictions by <a href="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/news/binance-bnb/">Binance</a>, the world’s largest exchange by trading volume, indicate a bullish price projection; APE will average at $2.446577 in 2025, $2.697351 in 2027, and $3.122521 in 2030.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">ApeCoin Overview</h2>



<figure class="wp-block-table"><table><tbody><tr><td>MARKETCAP</td><td>CIRCULATING SUPPLY</td><td>ALL-TIME LOW</td><td>POPULARITY</td><td>ALL-TIME HIGH</td></tr><tr><td>$1.418 billion</td><td>604,895,833</td><td>$1.00</td><td>#75</td><td>$39.40</td></tr></tbody></table></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">ApeCoin Price History</h2>



<p>When Yuga Labs debuted the Bored Ape and Mutant Ape <a href="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/news/nft/">NFT</a> collections, they became the most popular NFT brand. Yuga Labs founded<a href="https://apecoin.com/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank"> Apecoin</a> to power the entire operation of their apps and services offered for them to be improved. APE price fell to a low of $6.48 within an hour, and it remained in a sideways range between that figure and $9.35 for the rest of the afternoon. Many investors were concerned by the huge gaps in APE’s value, with several centralized exchanges claiming that ApeCoin had dropped 80% within a few hours of its launch.</p>



<p>The ApeCoin team knows the project’s high risk and price volatility but believes the long-term potential rewards justify these risks. On the minute of the airdrop,<a href="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/news/binance-bnb/"> Binance</a> recorded a high of $28 on its one-minute chart, <a href="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/apecoin-price-prediction/#ApeCoin-Price-Prediction-2024">whileGate.io</a> recorded an incredibly large $214.</p>



<p>In late March 2022, VC powerhouse Andreessen Horowitz led a funding round of $450 million, bringing the company’s valuation to an astounding $4 billion.&nbsp;</p>



<p>Later, when Yuga Labs said it was working on an “Otherside metaverse,” there were a lot of positive developments. On 28 April, the price was $26.91, setting a new all-time high. Since then, however, it has dropped significantly.</p>



<p>The floor price of the Bored Ape Yacht Club NFT collection reached all-time lows, an 84.3% decline from its peak in 2022.&nbsp; In 2023, the coin was in a bear run until October, when it started recovering, rising from a low of $1 to a high of $1.8. The coin extended the run this year as it rose above $2.0.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image"><img decoding="async" src="https://lh7-us.googleusercontent.com/rzZR0LF0frISlaxibdUphIdH-Lf7mIB0grk-V0rGU8sjDq_4JOMmWCjC-ACPQ8XR4jeQeVSherSOTB8Oh8ntkUgRw5GCvy6o-eEFcvw7ZRs3v1I0QUVSrj2bGsqaEyAhY51it-wUPuZpGyrFfEmNDpA" alt=""/></figure>



<p>Source: <a href="https://coinstats.app/coins/apecoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">https://coinstats.app/coins/apecoin/</a></p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">More on the Apecoin Network</h2>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading">What is ApeCoin?</h3>



<p>ApeCoin (APE) is a digital asset that allows users to send and receive payments securely and efficiently. ApeCoin is built on<a href="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/news/blockchain/"> blockchain</a> technology and utilizes a peer-to-peer network to facilitate transactions. APE is used in the ApeEcosystem to encourage a decentralized community that advances Web3. The cryptocurrency was created and launched by ApeCoin DAO, a decentralized autonomous organization dedicated to promoting the coin in the future years. Hosted on the <a href="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/news/ethereum-eth/">Ethereum</a> <a href="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/news/blockchain/">blockchain</a>, ApeCoin is an ERC-20 token for governance and utility.&nbsp;</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading">How does ApeCoin Work?</h3>



<p>The Bored Ape Yacht Club, long renowned for its satire and humor in trading circles, was the basis for ApeCoin, a cryptocurrency named after a well-known animal. The APE token is a governance mechanism in the APE ecosystem.APE powers the community that is cryptocurrency development at the forefront of web3.</p>



<p>ApeCoin cryptocurrency holders can choose the ecosystem’s path and how the DAO spends its funds.&nbsp;</p>



<p>Many consider ApeCoin a meme token if not an excessively hyped currency. Some investors/ whales are firmly behind ApeCoin, while others believe its bubble will burst in months.</p>



<p>You can buy ApeCoin on popular exchanges like <a href="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/news/binance-bnb/">Binance</a>, Coinbase, and Kraken.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading">Team Behind ApeCoin</h3>



<p>The ApeCoin team comprises experienced professionals from various backgrounds. Yuga Sato leads the team. Other members of the team include Daisuke Tanaka, who is the CTO of ApeCoin, and Kenta Suzuki, who is the Head of Business Development.&nbsp;</p>



<p>A group advises the ApeCoin team of experienced individuals from the blockchain and cryptocurrency industry. These advisors include Vitalik Buterin, the founder of <a href="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/news/ethereum-eth/">Ethereum</a>, and Daico Takahashi, the co-founder of OmiseGO.&nbsp;</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading">What Is The ApeCoin Foundation?</h3>



<p>The ApeCoin Foundation is a decentralized autonomous organization responsible for developing and adopting the ApeCoin token. It’s not like a regulator; it’s more of a foundation layer on which holders of ApeCoin in the ApeCoin DAO may build.&nbsp;</p>



<h4 class="wp-block-heading">Mission</h4>



<p>The Foundation’s objective is to provide decentralized and community-led governance, and it aims to become more decentralized over time. It is in charge of the ApeCoin DAO’s decisions and responsible for day-to-day management, accounting, project management, and other duties that ensure the DAO community’s ideas receive the support they require to come to reality.</p>



<p>The APE Foundation’s mission is to promote and protect the APE ecosystem fairly and inclusively. The ApeCoin Foundation’s primary objective is to utilize the Ecosystem Fund, which is governed by a multisig wallet, to pay its costs as directed by the ApeCoin DAO while providing an infrastructure for ApeCoin owners to collaborate via open and free governance procedures.</p>



<h4 class="wp-block-heading">Vision</h4>



<p>ApeCoin’s vision is to create a decentralized future where everyone has an equal say. The project aspires to build a global community of ApeCoin holders who can shape the future of the APE ecosystem.&nbsp;</p>



<p>The ApeCoin Foundation’s vision is to provide an infrastructure for ApeCoin owners to collaborate via open and free governance procedures.</p>



<p>ApeCoin also plans to use the APE ecosystem to create digital gaming, entertainment, and art.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Conclusion&nbsp;</h2>



<p>The APE ecosystem has continued to draw investors who use the platform to explore opportunities its ecosystem presents, including<a href="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/news/defi/"> Defi</a>, DAO, and NFTs. A quick look at the Apecoins roadmap and recent developments show compelling reasons to invest in the coin.</p>



<p>There is a lot of hype around the Bored Ape Yacht Club NFTs. With celebrity backing and connection to that project, there is potential for the price of ApeCoin to rise during another Bitcoin bull run. However, the coin has a limited utility, and community members have criticized its staking mechanics. The ApeCoin team is working hard to meet the community’s expectations and continue adding utility to the coin.</p>



<p>Given the current macroeconomic conditions plaguing all coins, the ApeCoin price prediction may reach over $3 by year’s end.</p>



<p>Overall, ApeCoin has a lot of hype and community support behind it right now, which will probably drive the price of APE. If you’re interested in investing in the token, conduct own research and follow current APE news before deciding when to buy, hold, or sell. Investing in ApeCoin is safe as a cryptocurrency but also carries volatility risks. Investing in cryptocurrencies such as ApeCoin on a regulated platform like Coinbase or eToro is also highly advisable.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://www.youtube.com/embed/TWgm5CUnXow" medium="video" width="1280" height="720">
			<media:player url="https://www.youtube.com/embed/TWgm5CUnXow" />
			<media:title type="plain">APE Coin Realistic Price Prediction... Time To Face Reality</media:title>
			<media:description type="html"><![CDATA[APE Coin Price prediction and analysis APE Coin Price Prediction and technical analysis#ape #apecoin #crypto #bitcoin 🔸My Fairdesk referral link ($5040 Bonu...]]></media:description>
			<media:thumbnail url="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/ape-coin-realistic-price-predict.jpg" />
			<media:rating scheme="urn:simple">nonadult</media:rating>
		</media:content>
<media:content url="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/cpn-2022-06-21T042531.306.png" medium="image"  type="image/png" /><media:thumbnail url="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/cpn-2022-06-21T042531.306.png"/>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Revolutionizing Memory Care: Sensay Unveils AI-Powered Digital Replicas for Dementia Support and Beyond</title>
		<link>https://www.cryptopolitan.com/revolutionizing-memory-care-sensay-unveils-ai-powered-digital-replicas-for-dementia-support-and-beyond/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chainwire]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 19:42:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blockchain]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Token]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[web3]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.cryptopolitan.com/?p=482603</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[London, UK, March 11th, 2024, Chainwire Sensay, a pioneering technology company at the intersection of AI and blockchain, today announced the imminent launch of its innovative platform designed to create autonomous lifelike AI Digital Replicas on-chain, marking a significant leap towards digital immortality. Leveraging cutting-edge technology, Sensay offers limitless potential in the digital age, empowering [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span><strong>London, UK, March 11th, 2024, Chainwire</strong></span></p>
<p></p>
<p><a href="https://www.snsy.ai" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">Sensay</a>, a pioneering technology company at the intersection of AI and blockchain, today announced the imminent launch of its innovative platform designed to create autonomous lifelike AI Digital Replicas on-chain, marking a significant leap towards digital immortality. Leveraging cutting-edge technology, Sensay offers limitless potential in the digital age, empowering users to retain ownership and monetize their digital twins.</p>
<p><strong>A Bold Step for Dementia Patients and Beyond</strong></p>
<p>Starting with a focus on dementia patients and their families, Sensay aims to provide immediate social impact by offering lifelike digital replicas for memory preservation and companionship. This groundbreaking approach addresses the urgent needs of over 55 million individuals worldwide affected by dementia, providing comfort and continuity for patients and their loved ones. Sensay has over 25,000 beta users on its platform with more joining every day. </p>
<p><strong>Endless Possibilities with Digital Twins</strong></p>
<p>Beyond dementia care, Sensay&#8217;s technology opens up a world of possibilities across various sectors, including education, healthcare, entertainment, and personal development. From preserving personal stories for generations to personalized learning and expert consultancy on demand, the potential applications are limitless. The team aims to revolutionize digital interaction by introducing a digital copy that can engage with gamers around the world 24/7 as a non-playable character (NPC), share skills and expertise with clients in any language, or serve as the ultimate personal assistant. This digital counterpart is designed to handle tasks such as taking introductory calls, booking restaurants, organizing travel, job hunting, and matchmaking, enhancing efficiency and connectivity in various aspects of life.</p>
<p><strong>Empowerment Through Tokenization</strong></p>
<p>As part of its mission to democratize technology, Sensay introduces the $SNSY token, enabling users to participate in the platform&#8217;s economy. Token holders will have access to exclusive rewards, early access to developments, and the ability to use tokens within the Sensay ecosystem.</p>
<p>The $SNSY token itself will act as a token of exchange between the Sensay Data Marketplace, its decentralized storage, and the autonomous Digital Replicas, therefore enabling users and owners of these Replicas to retain ownership and monetisation of their data. </p>
<p>The $SNSY token is on the Ethereum Network, audited by Hacken and Hashlock, with a LayerZero OFT (Omnichain Fungible Token) for ease of deployment to L2s like Arbitrum in the near future.</p>
<p><strong>Partnerships and Public Sale Announcement</strong></p>
<p>Sensay is proud to announce upcoming partnerships with leading organizations like HypersignID, Fetch AI, Banyan (Filecoin), AIOZ, LayerZero, Solv.Care, HeyGen, ElevenLabs, NowPayments, and SingularityNET. These collaborations will further enhance the platform&#8217;s capabilities and reach.</p>
<p>The public sale of $SNSY tokens is scheduled to start on 19th March, running approximately for three weeks unless sold out sooner. To date, the Sensay project has been bootstrapped by its founders, meaning no VCs, Pre or Private Sales to affect the public sale price. The public sale will be conducted in collaboration with Gempad, Enjinstarter, Poolz Finance and Fjord Foundry. This marks an exciting phase of Sensay&#8217;s journey, inviting investors and users to be part of a future where digital and physical realities converge.</p>
<p><strong>Digital Replication in Safe Hands</strong></p>
<p>Dan Thomson, Founder and CEO of Sensay, is at the forefront of the Digital Immortality movement, blending his visionary insights on digital replication with over seven years of experience in Web3 technology. An accomplished author on the subject, Thomson&#8217;s entrepreneurial journey includes the foundation of multiple startups, showcasing his unwavering commitment to leveraging technology for the greater good. Under his leadership, Sensay embarks on a mission to unlock the limitless potential of humanity globally, harnessing the power of AI and blockchain to create meaningful and lasting legacies.</p>
<blockquote><p>Dan Thomson shares, &#8220;At Sensay, we&#8217;re not just creating technology; we&#8217;re weaving the fabric of a new digital era where every individual has the power to leave an indelible mark on the world. Our platform is a testament to the boundless possibilities that emerge when we envision our digital futures with empathy, innovation, and a deep commitment to societal impact.&#8221; </p></blockquote>
<p>Sensay bridges the gap between Web2 and Web3, using decentralized infrastructure to power the next generation of AI Digital Replicas, keeping the power and opportunities of this amazing technology firmly in users&#8217; hands. Whilst in Beta, Sensay remains free to use and create replicas. </p>
<p><strong>About Sensay</strong></p>
<p>Sensay is revolutionizing the way we think about digital identity and legacy in the digital era. By creating on-chain verified autonomous digital replicas, Sensay is not just creating a technological solution; it&#8217;s crafting a new paradigm for personal presence and legacy in the digital age. For more information, visit <a href="https://snsy.ai" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">https://snsy.ai</a> and engage with us on <a href="https://twitter.com/asksensay" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">https://twitter.com/asksensay</a>, <a href="https://t.me/asksensay" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">https://t.me/asksensay</a> and <a href="https://discord.gg/Rwhxny8TbP" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">https://discord.gg/Rwhxny8TbP</a> </p>
<p><strong>Contact Sensay:</strong></p>
<p>&#8211; Website: <a href="https://snsy.ai" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">https://snsy.ai</a> </p>
<p>&#8211; Email: <a href="mailto:info@sensay.io" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">info@sensay.io</a> </p>
<p>&#8211; Documentation: <a href="https://docs.snsy.ai" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">https://docs.snsy.ai</a></p>
<p>&#8211; Brand And Media Kit: <a href="https://docs.snsy.ai/branding-and-media" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">https://docs.snsy.ai/branding-and-media</a> </p>
<p>&#8211; Social Media: @asksensay </p>
<p>Users can try talking to Dan Thomson’s Digital Replica Today: <a href="https://sensay.io/replicas/dan" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">https://sensay.io/replicas/dan</a> </p>
<p>Users can join Sensay in embracing the future of digital identity and legacy.</p>
<p></p>
<h5>Contact</h5>
<p><span><strong>CEO</strong><br /></span><span><strong>Dan Thomson</strong><br /></span><span><strong>Sensay</strong><br /></span><span><strong>dan@sensay.io</strong><br /></span></p>
<p class="chainwire-disclaimer cp-box cp-box-gray"><i><strong>Disclaimer.</strong> This is a paid press release. Readers should do their own due diligence before taking any actions related to the promoted company or any of its affiliates or services. <a href="https://cryptopolitan.com/">Cryptopolitan.com</a> is not responsible, directly or indirectly, for any damage or loss caused or alleged to be caused by or in connection with the use of or reliance on any content, goods or services mentioned in the press release.</i></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Sensay_Launch_1710180129S06KVPpxWb.jpg" medium="image"  type="image/jpeg" /><media:thumbnail url="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Sensay_Launch_1710180129S06KVPpxWb.jpg"/>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Elon Musk announce plans to make xAI Grok open-source</title>
		<link>https://www.cryptopolitan.com/elon-musk-announce-make-xai-grok-open-source/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Owotunse Adebayo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 19:05:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Industry News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cryptomarket]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.cryptopolitan.com/?p=482595</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Elon Musk, the tech mogul behind companies like Tesla and SpaceX, has announced plans to make xAI’s artificial intelligence (AI) model Grok open source. This decision comes amidst a lawsuit filed by Musk against rival AI chatbot developer OpenAI. In a recent post on the X social media platform dated March 11th, Musk revealed that [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Elon Musk, the tech mogul behind companies like Tesla and SpaceX, has <a href="https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/1767108624038449405" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">announced</a> plans to make xAI’s artificial intelligence (AI) model Grok open source. This decision comes amidst a lawsuit filed by Musk against rival AI chatbot developer OpenAI. In a recent post on the X social media platform dated March 11th, Musk revealed that Grok would be available as open-source software starting from this week.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Elon Musk set to make Grok open-source</h2>



<p>The move to make Grok open source has received largely positive responses from users, with many praising Musk for the decision. This announcement comes in the wake of a lawsuit Musk filed against OpenAI on February 29th, alleging a breach of agreement made when OpenAI was established as a nonprofit organization.</p>



<p>Musk contends that OpenAI’s recent partnership with Microsoft contradicts the founding principles of the nonprofit agreement, which aimed to advance open-source artificial general intelligence (AGI) for the betterment of humanity. According to Elon Musk, Microsoft’s investment of nearly $3 billion in OpenAI by the end of 2023 further complicates matters, as it suggests a shift away from OpenAI’s original mission towards more profit-driven objectives.</p>



<p>In his lawsuit, Elon Musk calls for OpenAI to return to its initial open-source principles and seeks an injunction to halt the for-profit exploitation of AGI technology. However, following the filing of the lawsuit, OpenAI executives released a joint statement revealing emails from Elon Musk that seemed to support the company’s transition into a for-profit entity. This revelation has added layers of complexity to the legal battle between Musk and OpenAI.</p>



<p>Since the initiation of the lawsuit, there have been organizational changes within OpenAI, including the reinstatement of CEO Sam Altman as a member of the board. Altman had been fired and subsequently re-hired in November 2023, with the board admitting that his departure had destabilized the company more than anticipated.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Musk’s intention for Grok and the OpenAI lawsuit</h2>



<p>Musk’s decision to release Grok as open source aligns with his stated goals in the lawsuit to promote open-source AGI for the benefit of humanity. Grok, developed by Musk’s company xAI, is an AI chatbot similar to OpenAI’s ChatGPT, but with the added capability to access real-time information via the X social media platform.</p>



<p>Unlike ChatGPT, Grok can tackle more contentious issues that other AI systems might avoid. However, access to Grok requires users to have a verified X account. In terms of performance, Grok AI, powered by the Grok-1 large language model, has been compared favorably to ChatGPT-3.5 but falls short of OpenAI’s latest model, ChatGPT-4, according to some assessments.</p>



<p>Elon Musk’s decision to make Grok open source represents a significant development in the ongoing debate over the future of AI development and its implications for society. By making Grok freely available to the public, Musk aims to foster greater collaboration and innovation in the field of artificial intelligence while also challenging the direction taken by organizations like OpenAI.</p>



<p>As the lawsuit between Musk and <a href="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/sam-altman-resumes-role-at-openai-board/" data-type="post" data-id="480756">OpenAI</a> continues to unfold, it raises important questions about the responsibilities of tech companies in advancing AI technologies and the ethical considerations surrounding their use. The outcome of this legal battle could have far-reaching implications for the future of AI development and the role of open-source principles in shaping its trajectory.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/IMG_7231.jpeg" medium="image"  type="image/jpeg" /><media:thumbnail url="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/IMG_7231.jpeg"/>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Defi protocol Unizen to reimburse users after its recent hack</title>
		<link>https://www.cryptopolitan.com/defi-protocol-unizen-to-reimburse-users-hack/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Owotunse Adebayo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 18:54:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Industry News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cryptomarket]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.cryptopolitan.com/?p=482588</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Following a security breach resulting in the loss of approximately $2.1 million in user funds, decentralized finance (DeFi) protocol Unizen has taken swift action to address the situation. The platform announced plans to reimburse users who lost up to 750,000 units, aiming to restore 99% of affected users’ funds as quickly as possible. Unizen to [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Following a security breach resulting in the loss of approximately $2.1 million in user funds, decentralized finance (DeFi) protocol Unizen has taken swift action to address the situation. The platform announced plans to reimburse users who lost up to 750,000 units, aiming to restore 99% of affected users’ funds as quickly as possible.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Unizen to reimburse 99% of affected users’ funds</h2>



<p>The <a href="https://twitter.com/peckshield/status/1766210445415727608" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">incident</a> came to light on March 9 when blockchain analytics firm PeckShield identified an “approve issue” with the DeFi platform, signaling that over $2 million had been drained. Users were urged to revoke approvals from the trade aggregator to prevent further losses.</p>



<p>Security company SlowMist estimated the exploit losses at $2.1 million, revealing that the attacker had exchanged Tether for the stablecoin Dai. Unizen wasted no time in responding to the breach. Within a day, the DeFi protocol reached out to the hacker via an on-chain message, offering a 20% bounty in exchange for returning the remaining stolen funds.</p>



<p>Simultaneously, the company initiated collaboration with law enforcement and forensic experts to identify the hacker. While negotiations for the bounty continued, Unizen prioritized refunding victims of the hack. On March 11, the company announced its plan to reimburse 99% of the affected users, starting with those who lost less than $750,000.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Addressing the hack and prioritizing user reimbursement</h2>



<p>Founder and CEO Sean Noga stepped in, loaning funds to the company to facilitate the refunds. Reimbursements will be provided in either USDT or USD Coin, with the process beginning immediately for eligible users. However, for those who incurred losses exceeding $750,000, the DeFi protocol stated that each case would be addressed individually.</p>



<p>Accompanying the reimbursement announcement was a video guide instructing users on how to review and revoke approvals within the platform to mitigate further losses. Unizen’s chief technology officer, Martin Granström, assured stakeholders that evidence had been gathered for a post-mortem report, and the company was collaborating with third-party firms to investigate the breach thoroughly.</p>



<p>Granström emphasized Unizen’s commitment to transparency, promising to share an incident report and invest more in security measures moving forward. By taking decisive action and demonstrating accountability, Unizen aims to restore user confidence in its platform and safeguard against future security threats.</p>



<p>As the DeFi space continues to evolve, incidents like these underscore the importance of robust security measures and proactive risk management strategies. While no system can guarantee absolute protection against cyber threats, <a href="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/decentralised-energy-the-branch-of-depin-that-is-evolving-rapidly/" data-type="post" data-id="482477">DeFi</a> protocols must remain vigilant and responsive to safeguard user assets and uphold the integrity of the ecosystem.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/IMG_7230.jpeg" medium="image"  type="image/jpeg" /><media:thumbnail url="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/IMG_7230.jpeg"/>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Gaming tokens hit the roof amid Bitcoin’s surge</title>
		<link>https://www.cryptopolitan.com/gaming-tokens-hit-roof-amid-bitcoins-surge/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Owotunse Adebayo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 18:43:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Industry News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cryptomarket]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.cryptopolitan.com/?p=482581</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Over the past weekend, the crypto market witnessed a significant surge in the value of tokens associated with video games and gaming chains, coinciding with Bitcoin briefly touching the $70,000 mark once again. Notably, the GALA token within the Gala ecosystem experienced a remarkable 42% increase in value over the last 24 hours, reaching nearly [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Over the past weekend, the crypto market witnessed a significant <a href="https://www.coingecko.com/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">surge</a> in the value of tokens associated with video games and gaming chains, coinciding with Bitcoin briefly touching the $70,000 mark once again. Notably, the GALA token within the Gala ecosystem experienced a remarkable 42% increase in value over the last 24 hours, reaching nearly $0.08 at present.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Gaming tokens experience weekend surge</h2>



<p>This surge represents a staggering 77% rise over the week and an impressive 230% increase over the past month, propelling GALA into the top 50 cryptocurrencies by market capitalization. While the exact catalyst behind this sudden surge remains unclear, Gala has been actively involved in recent developments, including the launch of its GalaSwap decentralized exchange (DEX) on the GalaChain network and its sponsorship of a $1 million hackathon at the Game Developers Conference.</p>



<p>Long-term holders have eagerly awaited such a breakout, contributing to the momentum. Despite this surge, GALA still lingers over 90% below its all-time high price of $0.82 recorded in November 2021. In tandem with GALA’s rise, other gaming-related tokens also experienced significant gains. The PIXEL token, associated with the crypto farming game Pixels and its underlying network Ethereumscaler Ronin, soared to a new all-time high above $0.94 before settling at $0.88, marking a remarkable 63% increase over the week.</p>



<p>This surge coincided with a surge in daily active users, surpassing 500,000, indicating a growing interest in the game. Additionally, Ronin network’s RON token reached a more than two-year high price of $4.05, though it slightly retreated to $3.70, still reflecting a 24% increase over the past week. Yield Guild Games’ YGG token, announced as the game’s guilds infrastructure partner, also saw a 64% surge in value.</p>



<p>Another notable token that experienced a surge to a new all-time high was PRIME, the token associated with the NFT card battler game Parallel. PRIME peaked at $19.78 before settling, reflecting a remarkable 132% increase over the past 30 days. This surge followed the game’s beta opening to all players and a promotional giveaway by major crypto exchange Coinbase.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">GALA leads the GameFi weekend rally</h2>



<p>Similarly, the BEAM token of the Beam gaming network reached an all-time high of $0.044, while Immutable’s IMX token spiked to a two-year high of $3.62. Within the GameFi ecosystem, various tokens demonstrated substantial gains, often surpassing those of Bitcoin, the leading cryptocurrency.</p>



<p>Axie Infinity’s AXS governance token rose by 75% over the past 30 days, reaching a current price of $13, while Iluvium’s ILV token spiked to $155, its highest value since June 2022. Across CoinGecko’s list of GameFi tokens, significant gains were evident, underlining the growing prominence of gaming-related cryptocurrencies within the broader crypto market.</p>



<p>While gaming tokens experienced a surge, Bitcoin itself continued its upward trajectory, briefly surpassing $70,000 before settling just below $69,500 at the time of writing. This marks an 11% increase over the past week, reaffirming Bitcoin’s dominance within the crypto space despite the remarkable gains observed in gaming-related tokens.</p>



<p>The weekend’s surge in gaming and metaverse coins highlights the growing intersection between cryptocurrencies and the gaming industry. As <a href="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/uae-adopts-cardano-blockchain/" data-type="post" data-id="482340">blockchain</a> technology continues to permeate various sectors, including gaming, investors and enthusiasts alike are increasingly turning their attention to tokens associated with virtual worlds and gaming ecosystems. While the exact triggers behind these surges may vary, the broader trend underscores the evolving landscape of digital assets and the diverse opportunities they present within the rapidly evolving crypto market.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/IMG_7229.jpeg" medium="image"  type="image/jpeg" /><media:thumbnail url="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/IMG_7229.jpeg"/>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>BlockFi’s Zac Prince transitions into Real Estate tech</title>
		<link>https://www.cryptopolitan.com/blockfis-zac-prince-real-estate-tech/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Owotunse Adebayo]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 18:32:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Industry News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cryptomarket]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.cryptopolitan.com/?p=482572</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Former BlockFi CEO, Zac Prince, is embarking on a new journey, transitioning from the unpredictable world of cryptocurrency to the more stable realm of real estate technology. Following BlockFi’s settlement with the estates of FTX and Alameda Research, which may result in a full recovery for the crypto lender’s users, Prince has decided to leave [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Former BlockFi CEO, Zac Prince, is embarking on a new journey, transitioning from the unpredictable world of cryptocurrency to the more stable realm of real estate technology. Following BlockFi’s settlement with the estates of FTX and Alameda Research, which may result in a full recovery for the crypto lender’s users, Prince has decided to leave both BlockFi and the crypto industry altogether.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">BlockFi’s Zac Prince leaves crypto</h2>



<p>His next endeavor is joining a real estate tech <a href="https://www.recostseg.com/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">startup</a> called Re Cost Seg, where he will play a pivotal role in the company’s leadership team. Prince’s departure from the crypto space comes as a result of his wife’s advice to seek a less tumultuous career path. Despite bidding farewell to crypto, Prince remains deeply passionate about the industry and its potential for innovation.</p>



<p>He draws parallels between the firm’s mission of providing tax-efficient crypto services and Re Cost Seg’s goal of democratizing access to cost segregation studies for real estate investors. These studies enable investors to accelerate property depreciation and ultimately save money on taxes.</p>



<p>One aspect of Re Cost Seg that resonates strongly with Prince is its commitment to making cost segregation studies accessible to smaller-scale landlords, not just large institutional investors. This mirrors his former firm’s efforts to democratize access to financial services within the crypto space.</p>



<p>Prince sees both companies as aligned in their mission to empower individuals to optimize their financial strategies and save money. Reflecting on his time at BlockFi, Prince emphasizes the importance of customer service and efficient product development. He acknowledges the significance of building a strong and dedicated team, a lesson learned from his experience at BlockFi.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Lessons learned and future endeavors</h2>



<p>Despite his departure, Prince remains committed to ensuring that all of the firm’s former clients are fully compensated. He has pledged to keep his crypto assets on the platform until all clients have been made whole. Prince explains that BlockFi’s bankruptcy was a result of loans extended to FTX and its affiliates, which were not repaid. However, BlockFi ultimately prevailed in the legal proceedings, securing a favorable outcome for its clients.</p>



<p>Prince expresses pride in the resilience of BlockFi’s team and their unwavering dedication to serving clients during challenging times. Looking ahead, Prince sees opportunities to apply lessons learned from BlockFi to his new venture at Re Cost Seg. He plans to leverage his experience with fast-paced product development and innovative marketing strategies honed in the crypto industry.</p>



<p>Despite the challenges faced by BlockFi during the <a href="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/white-house-proposes-strict-crypto-regulations/" data-type="post" data-id="482541">crypto</a> winter, Prince remains optimistic about the future of both the crypto and real estate sectors. Zac Prince’s transition from the crypto industry to real estate technology marks a new chapter in his career. His decision to join Re Cost Seg reflects his belief in the company’s mission to democratize access to cost segregation studies.</p>



<p>Prince’s experience at BlockFi has equipped him with valuable insights and skills that he intends to apply to his new role. As he embarks on this new journey, Prince remains committed to ensuring that BlockFi’s former clients receive the compensation they deserve.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<media:content url="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/IMG_7228.jpeg" medium="image"  type="image/jpeg" /><media:thumbnail url="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/IMG_7228.jpeg"/>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Polygon Price Prediction 2024-2033: Is MATIC Going Past $10 Soon?</title>
		<link>https://www.cryptopolitan.com/polygon-price-prediction/</link>
					<comments>https://www.cryptopolitan.com/polygon-price-prediction/#comments</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Shayan Chowdhury]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 17:32:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crypto Price Predictions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cryptocurrency]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cryptocurrency trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cryptomarket]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.cryptopolitan.com/?p=115640</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Polygon Price Prediction 2024-2033 How much is MATIC worth? Today, the price of Polygon (MATIC) stands at $1.2, experiencing a 24-hour trading volume of $133 million. The cryptocurrency has a market capitalization of $5.8 billion and accounts for 0.41% of the market dominance. Over the past 24 hours, MATIC’s price has decreased by 1.08%. Currently, [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<h4 class="wp-block-heading">Polygon Price Prediction 2024-2033</h4>



<ul>
<li><a href="#Polygon-Price-Prediction-2024">Polygon Price Prediction 2024 &#8211; up to <strong>$1.8</strong></a><gwmw style="display:none;"></gwmw><gwmw style="display:none;"></gwmw></li>



<li><a href="#Polygon-Price-Prediction-2027">Polygon Price Prediction 2027 &#8211; up to <strong>$4.27</strong></a></li>



<li><a href="#Polygon-Price-Prediction-2030">Polygon Price Prediction 2030 &#8211; up to <strong>$12.35</strong></a></li>



<li><a href="#Polygon-Price-Prediction-2033">Polygon Price Prediction 2033 &#8211; up to <strong>$35.66</strong></a></li>
</ul>



<h4 class="wp-block-heading">How much is MATIC worth?</h4>



<p>Today, the price of Polygon (MATIC) stands at $1.2, experiencing a 24-hour trading volume of $133 million. The cryptocurrency has a market capitalization of $5.8 billion and accounts for 0.41% of the market dominance. Over the past 24 hours, MATIC’s price has decreased by 1.08%. Currently, 8.01 billion MATIC tokens are in circulation, out of a maximum supply of 10 billion.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">MATIC price analysis: MATIC price triggers intense buying pressure, holds above $1.2</h2>



<ul>
<li>MATIC price analysis shows a bullish pattern after witnessing a surge above $1</li>



<li>Resistance for MATIC is present at $1.25</li>



<li>Support for MATIC/USD is present at $1.1</li>
</ul>



<p>The MATIC price analysis for 19 February confirms that MATIC witnessed a bullish pressure as it faced accumulation at $0.92. As a result, the price broke above the $1 milestone.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading">MATIC price analysis 1-day chart: Polygon meets buyers’ demand</h3>



<p>Analyzing the daily price chart of Polygon, MATIC’s price witnessed a bullish rally after bulls were successful to push the <a href="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/news/altcoin/">altcoin</a> above $1. Over the last 24 hours, MATIC price has been on a bullish recovery as bulls continue to accumulate, sending the price above $1.2 mark. The 24-hour volume surged to $194 million, showing an increased interest in trading activity today. MATIC price is currently trading at $1.2, decreasing by over 1.08% in the last 24 hours.</p>





<p>The RSI-14 trend line has surged from its previous level and currently hovers around 64-level, showing that bulls are slowly gaining the momentum of the price. The SMA-14 level suggests upward volatility in the next few hours.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading">MATIC/USD 4-hour price chart: Bears aim for a decline below EMA20</h3>



<p>The 4-hour MATIC price chart suggests MATIC price continues to experience bullish activity above EMA lines, creating a positive sentiment on the price chart. As the price continues to face resistance near immediate Fib level, bears are gaining confidence to trigger a downward correction.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img decoding="async" width="1200" height="531" src="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/MATICUSDT_2024-03-11_22-55-25-1-1200x531.png" alt="" class="wp-image-482570" srcset="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/MATICUSDT_2024-03-11_22-55-25-1-1200x531.png 1200w, https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/MATICUSDT_2024-03-11_22-55-25-1-300x133.png 300w, https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/MATICUSDT_2024-03-11_22-55-25-1-768x340.png 768w, https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/MATICUSDT_2024-03-11_22-55-25-1-1536x679.png 1536w, https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/MATICUSDT_2024-03-11_22-55-25-1.png 1814w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></figure>



<p>The BoP indicator is trading in a bullish region at 0.27, hinting that buyers are trying to build pressure near resistance levels and boost an upward correction.</p>



<p>Additionally, the MACD trend line has formed green candles above the signal line and the indicator aims for a positive momentum, strengthening bullish positions.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading">What to expect from MATIC price analysis next?</h3>



<p>The hourly price chart confirms bears are making efforts to prevent the MATIC price from an immediate surge. However, if MATIC price successfully breaks above $1.25, it may surge higher and touch the resistance at $1.5.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img decoding="async" width="1200" height="531" src="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/MATICUSDT_2024-03-11_21-32-19-1-1200x531.png" alt="" class="wp-image-482569" srcset="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/MATICUSDT_2024-03-11_21-32-19-1-1200x531.png 1200w, https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/MATICUSDT_2024-03-11_21-32-19-1-300x133.png 300w, https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/MATICUSDT_2024-03-11_21-32-19-1-768x340.png 768w, https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/MATICUSDT_2024-03-11_21-32-19-1-1536x679.png 1536w, https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/MATICUSDT_2024-03-11_21-32-19-1.png 1814w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></figure>



<p>If bulls cannot initiate a surge, MATIC price may drop below the immediate support line at $1.1, resulting in a correction to $0.9.&nbsp;</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Recent News/Opinions on MATIC</h2>



<p><strong>Controversy: </strong>The Polygon ecosystem has faced recent controversies, with the latest focusing on the Polygon Foundation. Accusations suggest it misused and sold off large amounts of MATIC, impacting holders.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-embed is-type-rich is-provider-twitter wp-block-embed-twitter"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">1/ Polygon allocation problems and suspicious flows to exchanges.<br><br>Let&#39;s look at a very large project and explore how the allocations were not done in line with the publicly stated plan. And show some, um, suspicious flows to an exchange.<br><br>This has been part of our demo for quite…</p>&mdash; ChainArgos (@ChainArgos) <a href="https://twitter.com/ChainArgos/status/1746737284924440724?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">January 15, 2024</a></blockquote><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script>
</div></figure>



<p><strong>Partnership:</strong> Fox Corporation has introduced the Verify platform, a blockchain-based system for companies to monitor their content&#8217;s online usage. Developed in collaboration with Polygon Labs, this platform aims to track the origin and history of media used by AI firms.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Polygon Price Predictions 2024-2033</h2>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading">Price Prediction By Cryptopolitan&nbsp;</h3>



<figure class="wp-block-image"><img decoding="async" src="https://lh7-us.googleusercontent.com/Mll4H9Xucb-mkwui8j3CxTWOcMvXUxqKTp1qBNfZMTvyD2rUV0SWepYODjJo_CZRdMljGudpwx9MpugI9Nb2Kwp_FLI7cO3NIoODD0hDP8JnSP0KuzPUs_9-wuk07OWqfHO4YO3FbXv7w1AGahUWkhE" alt=""/></figure>



<figure class="wp-block-table"><table><tbody><tr><td>Year</td><td>Minimum ($)</td><td>Average ($)</td><td>Maximum ($)</td></tr><tr><td>2024</td><td>1.08</td><td>1.11</td><td>1.8</td></tr><tr><td>2025</td><td>1.62</td><td>1.67</td><td>2.41</td></tr><tr><td>2026</td><td>2.43</td><td>2.52</td><td>2.80</td></tr><tr><td>2027</td><td>3.42</td><td>3.52</td><td>4.27</td></tr><tr><td>2028</td><td>4.98</td><td>5.16</td><td>6.00</td></tr><tr><td>2029</td><td>7.02</td><td>7.28</td><td>8.47</td></tr><tr><td>2030</td><td>10.39</td><td>10.68</td><td>12.35</td></tr><tr><td>2031</td><td>14.65</td><td>15.08</td><td>17.85</td></tr><tr><td>2032</td><td>21.09</td><td>21.70</td><td>25.73</td></tr><tr><td>2033</td><td>29.83</td><td>30.91</td><td>35.66</td></tr></tbody></table></figure>



<h4 class="wp-block-heading">Polygon Price Prediction 2024</h4>



<p>The price of Polygon is predicted to reach a minimum value of $1.08 in 2024. The Polygon price could reach a maximum value of $1.8 with the average trading price of $1.11 throughout 2024.</p>



<h4 class="wp-block-heading">Polygon Price Prediction 2025</h4>



<p>The price of 1 Polygon is expected to reach a minimum level of $1.62 in 2025. The MATIC price can reach a maximum level of $2.41 with the average price of $1.67 throughout 2025.</p>



<h4 class="wp-block-heading">MATIC Price Forecast for 2026</h4>



<p>Polygon price is forecast to reach a lowest possible level of $2.43 in 2026. As per our findings, the MATIC price could reach a maximum possible level of $2.80 with the average forecast price of $2.52.</p>



<h4 class="wp-block-heading">Polygon (MATIC) Price Prediction 2027</h4>



<p>As per the forecast and technical analysis, in 2027 the price of Polygon is expected to reach a minimum price value of $3.42. The MATIC price can reach a maximum price value of $4.27 with the average value of $3.52.</p>



<h4 class="wp-block-heading">Polygon Price Prediction 2028</h4>



<p>As per the forecast price and technical analysis, in 2028 the price of Polygon is predicted to reach a minimum level of $4.98. The MATIC price can reach a maximum level of $6.00 with the average trading price of $5.16.</p>



<h4 class="wp-block-heading">Polygon Price Prediction 2029</h4>



<p>Polygon price is forecast to reach a lowest possible level of $7.02 in 2029. As per our findings, the MATIC price could reach a maximum possible level of $8.47 with the average forecast price of $7.28.</p>



<h4 class="wp-block-heading">Polygon (MATIC) Price Prediction 2030</h4>



<p>The price of Polygon is predicted to reach a minimum value of $10.39 in 2030. The Polygon price could reach a maximum value of $12.35 with the average trading price of $10.68 throughout 2030.</p>



<h4 class="wp-block-heading">Polygon Price Forecast 2031</h4>



<p>According to our deep technical analysis on past price data of MATIC, in 2031 the price of Polygon is predicted to reach a minimum level of $14.65. The MATIC price can reach a maximum level of $17.85 with the average trading price of $15.08.</p>



<h4 class="wp-block-heading">Polygon (MATIC) Price Prediction 2032</h4>



<p>The price of Polygon is predicted to reach a minimum level of $21.09 in 2032. The Polygon price can reach a maximum level of $25.73 with the average price of $21.70 throughout 2032.</p>



<h4 class="wp-block-heading">Polygon Price Prediction 2033</h4>



<p>According to our deep technical analysis on past price data of MATIC, in 2033 the price of Polygon is forecasted to be at around a minimum value of $29.83. The Polygon price value can reach a maximum of $35.66 with the average trading value of $30.91.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading">Polygon Price Prediction By Coincodex</h3>



<p>According to Coincodex&#8217;s current Polygon price prediction, Polygon&#8217;s price is expected to increase by 14.63%, reaching $1.159450 by March 10, 2024. Coincodex&#8217;s technical indicators suggest that the market sentiment is currently Bullish, with the Fear &amp; Greed Index indicating a score of 90 (Extreme Greed).</p>



<p>Over the past 30 days, Polygon has seen 17 out of 30 (57%) days of price increase, with a volatility of 10.05%. Based on Coincodex&#8217;s forecast, this period is considered an opportune time to invest in Polygon. Further analysis of Polygon&#8217;s historical price trends and the impact of Bitcoin halving cycles leads to a prediction of a yearly low for Polygon at $1.011490 in 2025, while its price could soar to as high as $3.66 in the following year.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading">Polygon Price Forecast By Digital Coin Price</h3>



<p>According to projections from Digital Coin Price, analysts and experts anticipate that by 2026, MATIC will commence the year with a value of $3.01 and fluctuate around $3.60. This projection suggests a significant increase from the previous year, marking a considerable growth for Polygon.</p>



<p>Looking ahead to 2033, Litecoin is expected to attempt reaching a low of $1,558.64. Efforts might be made to achieve a maximum and ascend to the next premium tier of $1,614.05, with an average forecast price set at $1,605.31. There is potential for Litecoin to surpass its previous high and advance to a new level. While there&#8217;s optimism for progress to its subsequent stage, it&#8217;s also acknowledged that there could be a downturn.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading">Polygon Price Prediction By CryptoPredictions.com</h3>



<p>According to CryptoPredictions.com’s Polygon prediction, Polygon is forecasted to begin April 2024 with a value of $1.280 and close the month at $1.542. Throughout April, the highest predicted price for MATIC is $1.827, while the lowest anticipated price stands at $1.242.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Polygon Overview</h2>



<p>Polygon serves as a multi-layered protocol suite aimed at resolving the scalability challenges associated with the Ethereum network. By operating a separate but compatible blockchain, Polygon efficiently processes transactions before syncing them back to the main Ethereum chain. This method alleviates the strain on the Ethereum network, enabling faster transaction speeds and reducing costs to a fraction of a cent.</p>



<p>Previously known as Matic Network, Polygon offers a user-friendly framework that allows both new and existing blockchain projects to operate on the Ethereum platform without worrying about scalability constraints.</p>



<p>With Polygon, users can seamlessly engage with decentralized applications (DApps) without concerns over network bottlenecks. The company is led by CEO Jaynti Kanani, who co-founded the project with Sandeep Nailwal, the Chief Operating Officer, and Anurag Arjun, the Chief Product Officer. The team initially launched the project as Matic Network in 2017.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Polygon Price History</h2>



<p>According to Polygon&#8217;s plan, all Matic coins will be released by December 2022, which is good news for long-term investors because it guarantees significant future gains.</p>



<p>Since its inception in 2017, Matic tokens have had an incredible run that has withstood the test of unforgiving crypto market turmoil that usually ends up wiping out invalid tokens.</p>



<p>Despite the prevailing bearish trend currently experienced in the crypto market, experts are convinced by Matic’s crypto price prognosis and price forecast data that indicate an overall bullish trend for the long-term investment horizon.</p>



<p>Based on Coingecko&#8217;s data, Polygon has recorded impressive gains since its launch back in 2017. The crypto token has recorded incredible gains of up to 44157.6%, and the rally is expected to continue in the following years.</p>



<p>Matic recorded its all-time low price of $0.003143 in May 2019 during the famous bearish run. However, since then, the coin has continued to make significant gains until May 2021, when it recorded a new all-time high price of $2.62. It seems then that May is the month of Polygon, after all.</p>



<p>Polygon&#8217;s price has been on the rise since it hit a high of $1 at the end of July, and experts are predicting that as Polygon&#8217;s network continues to grow with new partnerships and adoption, the value of its token could go even higher. In August, Polygon&#8217;s price hovered around the $0.80 mark, but many believe that this is just the beginning of this promising project.</p>



<p>Recently, in November, Polygon saw a significant surge after the bullish news that the social media giant Meta is teaming up with the blockchain to deliver its journey into the world of Web3 and NFTs.</p>



<p>Stephane Kasriel, head of commerce and financial technologies at Meta, revealed that Instagram businesses will soon be able to create and sell their own NFTs (non-fungible tokens). This service would first launch on the Polygon blockchain before expanding to others, including Solana. MATIC rocketed after this news and hit a high of $1.29 on 7 November.&nbsp; After peaking and later announcing multiple partnerships, including an NFT marketplace deal with Nike, MATIC eventually fell below the $1 barrier.</p>



<p>Just this past year, Polygon (@0xPolygon) has rolled out some incredible features on Twitter. From the launch of a new Token List service to mobile burning capabilities for MATIC tokens, they have allowed users to interact with MATIC in an efficient and secure manner. This means you can now access the MATIC burn console through your mobile wallet with a simplified interface that is easy to use.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full is-resized"><img decoding="async" width="1114" height="404" src="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/05/Screenshot_1241.png" alt="Screenshot 1241" class="wp-image-179749" style="width:1016px;height:368px" srcset="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/05/Screenshot_1241.png 1114w, https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/05/Screenshot_1241-300x109.png 300w, https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/05/Screenshot_1241-768x279.png 768w, https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/05/Screenshot_1241-24x9.png 24w, https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/05/Screenshot_1241-36x13.png 36w, https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/05/Screenshot_1241-48x17.png 48w" sizes="(max-width: 1114px) 100vw, 1114px" /></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">More on Polygon (MATIC)</h2>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading">What&#8217;s Polygon (MATIC)?</h3>



<p>Polygon is the leading platform for Ethereum scaling and infrastructure development. Its growing suite of products offers developers easy access to all major scaling and infrastructure solutions: L2 solutions, sidechains, hybrid solutions, stand-alone and enterprise chains, data availability solutions, and more. Polygon’s scaling solutions have widespread adoption with 3000+ applications hosted, 1B+ total transactions processed, ~100M+ unique user addresses, and $5B+ in assets secured.</p>



<p>Mina Protocol&nbsp;and&nbsp;<a href="https://polygon.technology/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">Polygon</a>&nbsp;are working towards implementing support for Mina on Polygon PoS. This bridge will enable developers building applications on Polygon to leverage privacy and verifiability via Mina’s zero knowledge-SNARK-based protocol.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading">Polygon Use Cases</h3>



<p>Ethereum-based Polygon hopes to solve fundamental issues the Ethereum blockchain faces, such as interoperability and scalability. It is the first project on the Ethereum blockchain to launch an adequately structured tool that addresses the Ethereum scaling problem. Consequently, many have termed Polygon as an<strong> Ethereum scaling solution.</strong></p>



<p>Rather than running on its own blockchain, MATIC tokens are traded on the&nbsp;Ethereum&nbsp;blockchain. That’s because&nbsp;Polygon&nbsp;was developed to help scale Ethereum through side chains.&nbsp;MATIC allows you to stake on the Ethereum&nbsp;<a href="https://www.gobankingrates.com/investing/crypto/what-is-blockchain-technology/?utm_campaign=1177634&amp;utm_source=nasdaq.com&amp;utm_content=5&amp;utm_medium=rss" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">blockchain</a>&nbsp;and pay for currency transactions. This has helped reduce the high transaction costs inherent in the Ethereum blockchain, helping promote widespread adoption.&nbsp;</p>



<p>Another thing, Ethereum is home to several <strong>DeFi projects</strong> like the Polygon, formerly known as the Matic network. Since the Matic network has brought numerous functionalities to the entire Ethereum blockchain, several developers have taken an interest in the project, which has, in turn, led to steady growth of Matic price. </p>



<p>Major cryptocurrencies such as Bitcoin, Ethereum, Ripple, etc., witnessed a slump on the 1st week of June, and yet, the value of Polygon(MATIC) rose nearly 35% in the same period. Investors saw Polygon (MATIC) as the next big thing, and in a short period, it surged past other cryptos to rank among the <a href="https://economictimes.indiatimes.com/markets/cryptocurrency/heres-how-india-based-polygonmatic-outperformed-other-major-cryptos/articleshow/83329658.cms" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">top 15 biggest cryptos</a> globally. Polygon successfully converts the limited Ethereum blockchain into an open blockchain network usable by many. In essence, it makes Ethereum steady as the internet of blockchains.</p>



<p>In turn, Polygon (Matic) project benefits immensely from the already-established Ethereum blockchain in several ways. Firstly, every blockchain project needs a secure security infrastructure; the Matic network benefits from Ethereum&#8217;s array of qualities, such as an active and vibrant community, established security systems, and transparency.</p>



<p>Within the Polygon network, transactions are settled using the Matic coin. Matic price has risen over the years, sparking interest from cryptocurrency enthusiasts. Polygon technology has improved efficiency within the Ethereum blockchain. Today, Polygon boasts of handling up to 65,000 transactions per second on its single sidechain. Similarly, it has averaged an impressive block confirmation time of two seconds per transaction.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading">Pros and cons of investing in Polygon (Matic)</h3>



<p>Polygon, formerly Matic network, has been considered a stable investment by crypto enthusiasts. Anyone interested in Ethereum and its bundle of projects likely has an affinity for Matic.</p>



<p>It is a well-structured organization with clear goals of extending the scalability of the Ethereum blockchain and making cryptocurrency more accessible to the public. If the project continues to push forward strides, its success is inevitable, and consequently, Matic holders will benefit significantly.</p>



<p>Investing is a full-time activity that requires individuals to analyze potential risks and returns before committing. However, within the crypto world, numerous uncertainties shape the prices of crypto coins. Therefore, even for a seasoned professional, it is challenging to make precise predictions on the price of a coin based on historical price actions alone.</p>



<p>However, for an individual to earn impressive returns on their investments, they must take risks. Here, we&#8217;ll discuss some of the benefits of investing in the Polygon ecosystem.</p>



<h4 class="wp-block-heading">Pros of investing in Matic</h4>



<p>Since Matic is a scaling solution on the Ethereum blockchain, it is difficult to foresee its downfall. Therefore, most forecasts are convinced that Polygon will be in existence for years to come. So what are some of the pros of investing in this token?</p>



<ul>
<li>It provides new scaling solutions to the Ethereum ecosystem, ensuring a bright future and allowing investors to make long-term investments.</li>



<li>Since 67% of the tokens are already in circulation, and the maximum supply is expected to be realized by December 2022, the coin offers immense growth potential in 2022 and beyond, allowing investors to reap more profits.</li>



<li>Matic allows for the interconnection of blockchain networks, a scaling solution that assures investors of Matic&#8217;s future performance.</li>



<li>Polygon is supported by a strong community of developers that ensures the project performs well and consequently maintains and increases Matic&#8217;s price level.</li>
</ul>



<h4 class="wp-block-heading">Cons of investing in Matic</h4>



<p>It is indeed public knowledge that investments always come with a degree of risk. Investing in Matic may result in losses if careful considerations of the involved risks aren&#8217;t well conducted. Below are some possible shortcomings of investment in Matic.</p>



<ul>
<li>Recently, the Polygon network was hacked, and the perpetrators made away with millions worth of Matic tokens. The hacking was a huge red flag for investors since it indicates that the network isn&#8217;t as secure as it should be.</li>



<li>Price volatility. Every cryptocurrency experiences volatility; however, when dealing, sometimes crypto coins experience extreme price drops that may hurt an individual&#8217;s portfolio. Since Matic already competes with Avalance, Polkadot, and Cosmos, it is unclear who will win the race. Therefore, for a long time horizon, investors should keep tabs and know when to exit.</li>
</ul>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="Conclusion">Conclusion</h2>



<p>Despite the short-term volatility, Polygon&#8217;s investors remain confident that it can reach double digits in no time. For instance, Lark Davis (@TheCryptoLark) confidently tweeted about his MATIC holdings expecting it to hit $10 soon.</p>



<p>Polygon has been actively forging relationships with various companies in the crypto space and staying abreast of current blockchain technology trends. Here are some recent updates, as announced by Polygon:</p>



<ul>
<li>The Polygon Mainnet is now live in Alpha and Beta versions.</li>



<li>Support for deposits and withdrawals of all Ethereum-based assets</li>



<li>Support of ERC721 to ERC20, ERC20 to ERC20, and ERC721 to ERC721 transactions enabled</li>



<li>Increasing the number and capabilities of Proof-of-Stake validators</li>



<li>Offering the API and SDK toolkit for dApp infrastructure development</li>



<li>Supernets, a new blockchain network, is ready to skyrocket with Polygon&#8217;s $100 million investment toward businesses taking advantage of its powerful technology.</li>
</ul>



<p>With partnerships and increased adoption, MATIC prices are expected to continue to surge. If investors and traders can take advantage of these bullish signs, they could enjoy significant profits. However, it is important to keep in mind that the cryptocurrency space is highly volatile and risky so always do your own research before investing.</p>



<p>There are many factors influencing the future of MATIC coin, from global economic conditions to the level of adoption of cryptocurrencies. The partnership with Meta and the latest breakout on the platform appear to be positive indicators for the coin&#8217;s future price, according to predictions from algorithm-based forecasting sites.</p>



<p>Overall, scaling solutions like Polygon are expected to gain momentum as network congestion on the Ethereum blockchain remains an issue. Polygon&#8217;s multi-layer technology allows it to authenticate transactions in a matter of seconds while still uploading them to the Ethereum blockchain, combining scalability and security. </p>



<p>Polygon&#8217;s powerful Dapp architecture makes it simple to build new apps on-chain and port current Ethereum projects. However, MATIC is projected to continue <strong>dipping by a few cents before beginning another price increase soon. Before making any investment decisions, do your </strong>research.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.cryptopolitan.com/polygon-price-prediction/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>5</slash:comments>
		
		
		<media:content url="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/CP_Altcoins_-MATIC-_1140x570.png" medium="image"  type="image/png" /><media:thumbnail url="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/CP_Altcoins_-MATIC-_1140x570.png"/>	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
